You're
breeze
blow
ing
through
When
you
close
your
eyes,
sun
light
starts
fade
tell
what
you
might
be
thin
king
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
Once
your
eyes
once
a
gain
are
o
pen
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
zing
out
head,
clear
as
orbs
of
glass
Some
where
deep
wi
thin,
I
can
sense
the
clouds
clea
ring
blue
reign
and
ba
nish
gray
Buds
are
bloo
ming
storms
will
calm
as
the
fog
rolls
wer's
mist
I'll
take
con
trol
of
this
bea
ting
wi
thin
boku
We'll
be
one
with
the
wind
Let's
reach
the
clouds
yond
ring
end
less
ly
in
the
dawn
Episode 18: First-Rank Mage Selection Exam
So, that's the Northern Lands'
largest city of magic, Äußerst.
29 years after the death
of Himmel the Hero
Northern Lands,
Kühl Region
29 years after the death
There's still a lot of road ahead of us.
We should catch a carriage on the way.
29 years after the death
Once you get certified as a first-rank mage,
we can enter the Northern Plateau.
I don't think I need to be the one
to get the certification, though.
It'll only last me a short time, anyway.
You can be the one to get it.
Don't you know, Lady Frieren?
First-rank mages are a select few
of the most seasoned mages around.
I'm not good enough for that.
Is that so?
You seem disinterested.
It's a bit late to ask this,
but why do we need such an amazing mage
to enter the Northern Plateau?
There's always been a lot of monsters there
that use tricky magic, like the Einsam.
Even in the past, you would need a priest
and an excellent mage to get through it.
That said,
if valuable seasoned mages are required to pass,
there must be quite some trouble brewing there.
We'll have to gather information
on the exam in Äußerst.
Based on what Fern said,
it seems there'll be actual combat.
So we'll need some countermeasures.
Isn't any kind of exam going to be easy
with your mana pool, Lady Frieren?
Even when you're regulating it,
you radiate the mana of a seasoned elder mage.
Don't call me an elder.
Come on, now she's sulking.
Isn't "elder mage" going too far?
I'm sorry.
And I haven't forgotten that you
called me a damn hag, you know?
That was ages ago.
Whatever. I'm going to sleep.
Wake me when we get to Äußerst.
Geez.
Actually, never mind.
Huh? What's wrong?
I could only see half the sky.
Just so you know, Fern,
the strength of a mage isn't
determined by just their mana.
There's technique and experience,
the magic they use and their control over it,
and their hard work and guts.
You mixed some real warrior words in there.
And also, talent.
So far, I've lost to mages with less mana
than me eleven times in my life.
Four of those were demons.
Like Qual.
One was an elf, like me.
And the other six were humans, like you.
The city should come into sight soon.
The road to Äußerst sure is rough.
Northern Lands,
Granat Earldom Outlands
Time to take a breather.
Hey, Miss, that's a nice staff you've got there.
What's this? More bandits?
We finally got some peace with Aura defeated.
But now people like you show up more often, huh?
Who said you could talk?
Pack up your belongings and—
You bastard!
If you value your lives, get out of here. Immediately.
Let's scram.
Thanks, you saved me.
I'm Übel the Mage.
I'm Kraft the Monk.
Oh, are you an elf?
That's rare, you're the first I've met.
You have the eyes of a murderer.
I didn't save you.
I found some butchered
bandits in the forest nearby.
It was the work of a mage.
And an awfully proficient one, at that.
I see.
Did you come here to lecture me or something?
No, I'm an adventurer too.
I'm not so naïve that I'd complain
about killing someone in self-defense.
I'd like to prevent it if I can, though.
Perceptive old man. How boring.
Are you headed for Äußerst?
Yeah, to take the first-rank mage exam.
Frieren was also talking about that.
I'll have another story for the next time we meet.
Continental Magic Association
Northern Branch
The exam will take place in two months.
Take note that the first-rank exam
is only held once every three years.
Additionally, at least a fifth-rank
certification is required to take it.
You've got this, Fern.
Lady Frieren, there's no way I can do this by myself.
You'll be fine.
What if I fail?
The exam is only held once every three years!
Then we'll either hire a first-rank mage or go by sea.
That would be incredibly expensive.
We'd be back to skipping snacktime every day.
Sure, but I don't have a certification.
This mark of the holy staff...
isn't gonna work, is it?
What's with that relic again?
Hey, you.
Could you let me see that?
Do you intend to take the first-rank exam?
Looks like I'll be able to participate.
I didn't think anyone still knew about these.
Is having that mark impressive?
It's supposed to be.
So, you're not in the mage's guild?
The institutions governing mages change frequently.
I can't be bothered to join each new one.
Besides, I have this.
The mark of the holy staff. Impressive, isn't it?
What's this rusted necklace? You recognize it?
Not at all.
I see.
This is the one thing
proving that I'm a mage, though...
Frieren, it's true we don't know about that necklace.
But we do know you're an amazing mage.
Isn't that enough?
You guys don't even live that long.
Lady Frieren.
We know well that you're an amazing mage.
Yeah.
According to the Continental Magic Association,
fifth-rank mages and above
are considered full-fledged.
Why did you get the third-rank certification?
It had the closest exam date.
The total number of mages
at or above fifth-rank is six hundred.
If you include apprentices from ranks
six through nine, it's a total of two thousand.
Forty-five of those are first-rank.
The first-rank exam is every three years
and is held in the northern branch
in Äußerst and the main branch in Strahl.
There are frequently years where no one passes.
Casualties are taken for granted.
It's quite a difficult exam.
The number of mages in the world
sure has decreased, though.
Were there more mages in the past?
It was normal to pass mages
on the street a hundred years ago,
when the demon king's army
was intensifying its offensive.
Now you barely meet any unless
you come to a city of magic.
Well, let's put these two months to good use
by buckling down for some training.
We will now commence
the First-Rank Mage Selection Exam.
First Exam — Examiner
Genau — First-Rank Mage
The first-rank certification is granted
We've got quite the lineup this year.
There's the second-rank mage, Wirbel,
the captain of the Northern Mage Corps,
to only the most exceptional of mages.
It is a title only a select few can earn.
who's fought against the remnants
of the demon king's army for many years.
The exam is naturally quite dangerous,
The second-rank mage, Denken,
but the Association will not help you
should you find yourself in danger.
a cunning old fox who prevailed in
the bloody struggle for the seat of Imperial Mage.
Third-rank mage, Fern,
the youngest mage to have passed
the third-rank exam, and with top marks at that.
We do have some problem children as well, though.
Like the third-rank mage, Übel,
who took the second-rank exam two years ago,
killed the first-rank examiner, and was disqualified.
Who else looks promising?
There's someone radiating
the mana of a seasoned elder mage.
Who's that?
No idea.
I will now announce the contents
of the first stage of the exam.
It's a team battle.
The fifty-seven of you will form
teams of three to take the exam.
We will now form the teams.
A bracelet?
It has a number on it.
I guess that means I'm in Team Two.
By infusing it with mana, I can tell where
the other bracelets for my team are.
So that's how we discern our teams.
This is an interesting setup.
A normal party is one thing,
but an impromptu team of eclectic mages
will have a hard time working well together.
First impressions are important
with this kind of thing.
I gotta be careful not to cause trouble.
The bracelet's reaction is over here...
They're gonna come off!
Screw you! I'll end you!
You can try.
They're already fighting...
Nice to meetcha.
Nice to meet you, too.
Northern Lands, Grob Basin
First Exam Area
I will now explain the detailed
rules for the first stage.
This exam area is home to a bird called the Stille.
I have handed out one cage to each team.
There are two conditions for passing the first stage.
You must possess a cage containing
a Stille by sundown tomorrow.
Stay away from me!
All team members must be present at that time.
You're generally free to do as you please,
but if any team member exits the exam area,
the whole team will be disqualified immediately.
That's rich, coming from
the people who covered the entire area
with an absolutely impassable barrier.
There's no way we can get out.
So you are listening, huh?
The first stage begins now.
We should figure out a plan first!
Idiot!
How are we gonna plan before finding one?
They're still fighting...
For now, let's introduce ourselves while we walk.
And decide who holds the cage
with rock-paper-scissors.
I'm Frieren. Nice to meet you.
I'm Lawine, a third-rank mage.
I'm Kanne, also third-rank.
I go way back with Lawine.
We both graduated from the same magic school.
Do either of you know anything about the Stille?
No.
Nope.
I do know about it, but I've never seen one myself.
We should start by finding one
and observing it for a while.
I'm tired.
Show some grit.
Let's take a break.
I can still move, so I'll go look ahead.
It's safer if we move together.
So what? That's inefficient.
Are you strong, Lawine?
Stronger than her.
Wanna put that to the test?
And compared to me?
I wouldn't wanna fight you.
I see.
Alright, go look ahead.
Turn back if it seems dangerous.
Okay.
Oh, and be careful of the sky.
I know.
Is this team gonna be okay?
You're like a teacher, Frieren.
I think you should be the leader.
It's just because the two of you are always fighting.
I don't really want to be leading.
Sorry, we've always been like this.
By the way, what did you mean
by "be careful of the sky"?
I mean just what I said.
Are you bad at detecting mana?
Why?
Hey.
That was fast.
I found a Stille.
Good job, Lawine. Let's carefully observe—
I told you to observe it...
It's getting away.
No, good work, Kanne.
Oh, not bad.
But you should really get down now.
Huh, why...
Stille are incredibly tough,
and can fly faster than sound.
That level of restraint isn't going to work.
Seriously? I already lost sight of it.
We were so close.
It'll take a lot of observation to capture one.
We'll dedicate the rest of today to observation.
Kanne controlled the water, and Lawine froze it.
They were in perfect harmony.
That's quite impressive coordination.
You don't just learn that overnight.
I was worried for a bit there, but maybe we'll be fine.
Let's chase it.
No, we should check around the perimeter.
Why? The quicker we chase it, the better.
Never mind, they're fighting again...
What's that sound?
Huh?
Frieren's not here.
It's faint, but this is the sound of rain.
It's not raining, so why...
Oh, that's why.
So does that mean—
A monster!
My staff.
La-Lawine!
I told you to be careful of the sky, didn't I?
Have you calmed down?
Yeah.
You called Lawine's name.
Don't you hate her?
Yeah...
That's what I thought.
So why are you two so good at coordinating?
I don't get it.
You know, I'm pretty cowardly.
I often find myself helpless
when push comes to shove.
Like the first time we were supposed
to put our flight magic to the test.
The others have already made it way over there.
There's water down there, so it's not like you'll die.
If you can't muster the courage,
do you want me to kick you off?
I hate you, Lawine.
I know.
You're always so mean to me.
I do better when I'm praised, you know.
You've gotta be joking.
This is the result of being coddled by your parents.
If that's all you need to fly, I'll be as nice as you need.
Then tell me what good points I have.
Come on, are you serious?
The way you try your best,
even though you're scared...
That's a good point.
Tell me more.
What?! Why?!
The way you put in a lot of effort in secret.
The way you're considerate
to the people around you.
More.
The way you're cute when you smile.
What? Gross.
That was close.
Look at that, you can fly just fine.
I'm never gonna be nice to you again.
Lawine can be abrasive,
but she's always pushed me along.
Thanks to her, I've noticed
that if I don't let myself stop,
scary things are more manageable than they seem.
By the way, Frieren.
I noticed something interesting.
Could this be useful somehow?
I see.
We might be able to catch a Stille quite easily.
And
I'm
al
right
I'll
be
al
right
Yeah,
I
hear
you
I
care
a
bout
ling
the
wind
u
pon
my
hair
and
loo
king
back
a
gain
have
come
days
that
you
spent
with
Each
mo
ment
had
pur
pose
and
you
knew
it
all
those
years
with
all
the
pain
that
it
might
bring
thank
ful
for
all
I've
been
through
These
fee
lings
are
my
proof
I'm
live
I'll
ne
ver
beg
or
pray
That
gain
nee
kyou
da
ke
wa
So
just
dashi
think
back
on
you,
my
friend
found
you
gain
Some
where
long
the
win
ding
road
woul
dn't
he
si
tate
stay
by
your
side
'til
the
end
A
ny
time,
a
where
place
that
I
go
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'll
al
ways
have
your
smi
le
A
ny
time,
a
where
itsu
mo
When
I
close
my
eyes,
see
you
ze
ttai
nan
te
naku
mo
There's
so
much
we'll
ne
ver
know
A
ny
time,
a
where
when
you're
al
ways
here
wi
thin
my
heart
A
ny
time,
a
where
know
my
tears
are
bound
ning
sky
is
sure
glow
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'm
whis
come
back
home
That's insane.
Let's do this.
You say that like
we can take it easy now.
They're rookies.
Someone's detected us.
It's time for some
Shut up.
inter-team fights.
Then there's
no more need
This is an elaborate plan that Team Two came up with.
for words.
Episode 19
An Elaborate Plan