That's pretty scary.
It's probably a spell that severs objects.
It's on the simpler side of spells, but it's invisible.
I can't block it all.
But...
What happened? Not gonna go for the kill?
I guess I got a little carried away.
You sure did.
Your spell has a range
of about five meters, doesn't it?
Spot-on. So, what are you gonna do about it?
Duke it out with basic spells, like before?
No, that won't be necessary.
He uses utterly unscrupulous, cowardly magic,
and does whatever it takes to win.
The girl that's fighting him right now,
she's probably going to get killed.
Well then...
A saturation attack?
She can use this many
offensive spells simultaneously?
This kind of brute-force attack is absurd.
There's not a scrap of dignity.
I can't fend them all off.
You're
breeze
blow
ing
through
When
you
close
your
eyes,
sun
light
starts
fade
tell
what
you
might
be
thin
king
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
Once
your
eyes
once
a
gain
are
o
pen
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
zing
out
head,
clear
as
orbs
of
glass
Some
where
deep
wi
thin,
I
can
sense
the
clouds
clea
ring
blue
reign
and
ba
nish
gray
Buds
are
bloo
ming
storms
will
calm
as
the
fog
rolls
wer's
mist
I'll
take
con
trol
of
this
bea
ting
wi
thin
boku
We'll
be
one
with
the
wind
Let's
reach
the
clouds
yond
ring
end
less
ly
in
the
dawn
Episode 20: Necessary Killings
Solganiel.
I can't move.
I can't use my mana, either.
A powerful binding spell, huh?
If he had this, he could have
just caught a Stille himself.
I guess it doesn't do him
any good if he can't find one.
My spell lets me immobilize
anything within my field of view.
As long as I don't look away,
you won't be able to move.
I can easily kill you in that state.
This guy was holding back, huh?
If he was really trying to kill us,
he would have immobilized us during that ambush.
Alright, last chance.
Leave the Stille and get out of here.
How boring.
And here I thought we would be fighting to the death.
But he just wanted to get the Stille by threatening us.
Wait.
Why do you need to order me to do that?
You could just take it
from me while I'm immobilized.
So, it doesn't work if you can't see my entire body.
No wonder you didn't use it against us earlier.
You went for my eyes, didn't you?
The logical choice, isn't it?
Nah, in your shoes,
I'd aim for the neck in order to kill.
That would end the fight.
You could have done that.
I've seen people act like you on the battlefield.
They were all sickos who enjoyed killing.
I should kill you here and now.
Have you killed women and children before?
You think I haven't?
Hm? What kind of hell did you experience?
Stalling for time?
Fine. I'll play along.
The Northern Mage Corps are mercenaries specialized in fighting demons, but in times of need,
we're called on to fight
against other countries as well.
People are well aware of others' weaknesses.
Inhuman acts like sending women and children
out to war are entirely commonplace.
It's no hell.
In the far north, it's our everyday life.
Yeah?
Oh well.
Aren't you going to kill me?
You know, I believe the spells people
are proficient in reflect their life and character.
This immobilizing spell feels like you
want time to prepare yourself for the kill.
I guess that's why you went along with my stalling.
I'm surprised.
You still want to be human, even though
your hands are already stained with blood.
That's right. I need the time
to gather the resolve to kill.
But you see, girl.
I may hesitate, but I've always killed when necessary.
See ya, girl.
Please don't move.
You've got to be kidding.
Ehre lost to you?
I didn't notice her at all.
I'm surprised. You can completely hide your mana?
You must be the one who caught the Stille.
We were just lucky.
We happened to find the Stille's nest,
and her master had taught her
the Spell That Catches Birds.
Since you can trap anything,
you must've been really unlucky.
You can say that again.
You were fighting Ehre, right?
What happened to her?
I killed her.
The conditions for passing the first-stage exam
are being in possession of a Stille by sunset,
and all team members being present.
We've lost. I'm going to withdraw.
Weren't you going to kill me?
I've already been disqualified.
Killing you is no longer necessary.
See you.
You can aim for my back if you want.
That unnecessary killing
will simply become necessary again.
Lady Übel.
I know.
Good lie.
Let's take the chance to go help Sir Land.
I'm sure he's fine.
That four-eyes is a real sandbagger.
This fight is over.
This is impressive.
You turned countless petals into steel, and slipped
through my defenses with incredible precision.
But you're self-taught, aren't you?
Self-taught people often neglect their fundamentals.
When fighting someone for the first time,
I make it a point to wait and see how they fight first.
I've grasped your weak points well.
I've probably won.
You talk a lot.
How are you going to win
without your dominant arm?
If you won't surrender, I'll sever your head next.
I told you, I'm just analyzing
how you fight beforehand.
You're bad at mana detection, aren't you?
Illusionary magic.
It's tangible, so a clone, to be precise.
When did you—
From the start. Since the exam started.
I trust no one but myself.
"Killed her" my ass.
That damn woman, lying through her teeth.
Hey, Ehre, wake up.
You ran out of mana? Lame.
Weren't you top of your class?
She overwhelmed me with standard offensive magic.
I couldn't fend it all off.
Don't believe me?
I do.
Fighting fair and square like an idiot.
That was a fight you could've won.
If she can do this with just
standard offensive magic, though,
that woman's a real monster.
Let's go. We gotta meet up with Scharf.
Wait, I can't walk.
Fine, whatever.
Wait, don't carry me like an object.
Carry me piggyback!
Why am I stuck doing this...
Is Scharf close?
He's behind those bushes.
Hey, Scharf, help me carry Ehre...
Wirbel, give me a piggyback ride.
I'm paralyzed and can't move.
Damn it.
What the hell is going on?
What's that sound?
It's the rain.
It started falling outside the barrier.
It's really reflecting how I feel.
Two or three more hours until sunset.
The first-stage exam's almost over.
With the two of you out of commission,
we won't be able to steal a Stille at this point.
There's no way we're going to pass.
But you're still carrying us. How kind.
I could drop and leave you here, you know?
Please don't.
Stop crying, you're a man, aren't you?
Is that kindness why you fight demons?
You once saved my village.
Idiot.
Like I'm gonna put my life on the line for kindness.
People fight for greed.
I have an ulterior motive, too.
There was a girl I liked in my hometown.
Around 29 years ago, demon activity
increased in the Northern Lands.
Her family decided to flee to the Central Lands.
I was a dumb brat.
I tried to act cool for her.
I'll kill all those shitty demons.
So come back to this village once I do.
That was when I was four or five.
I don't remember her face or her name anymore.
That is pretty stupid.
Yeah, it is.
I guess I'll be going home by boat again.
I get really seasick...
I can introduce you to my grandpa.
He's a first-rank mage, so you could go by land...
Hey, Wirbel.
What's up?
Look.
What a joke.
What was all that trouble for?
Now we get lucky?
Frieren, that girl isn't doing anything.
An elf, huh?
She's a skilled mage.
Laufen's magic will probably only work on her once.
But that one time will be enough.
This is no battle to the death.
She disappeared.
Frieren, the Stille!
She took it.
An interesting spell.
Within the barrier,
it's comfortable even in the rain, huh?
Oh yeah, you're the examiner for
the second-stage exam, aren't you, Sense?
Looks like you've once again let several
promising examinees die, Genau.
Don't make me laugh.
The promising ones won't die here.
Besides, the first rank is just that valuable.
You should understand that.
Still, picking a target that you can't detect
with mana for a mage exam is quite ill-natured.
Catching one is dependent on luck.
This is a battle royale disguised as a hunt.
Luck is a skill, too.
Besides, it looks like some have
caught a Stille without relying on luck.
The sun sets in three hours.
The fighting is going to get more intense.
Who do you think is going to win?
Probably about a third will last.
Denken is guaranteed to be among them.
His skill is on par with that of a first-rank mage.
Why is an old man, with eyes
for nothing but wealth and power,
taking the exam at this point?
You think it's for the special privilege?
Who knows.
He's quite old already.
He must have his reasons.
Say, the spell that girl just used is Silwehr, isn't it?
A folk spell passed on amongst
a mountain tribe in the Southern Lands.
Yeah, it is.
Silwehr?
The Spell for High-Speed Movement.
Then shouldn't the two of you have stayed hidden?
You could've let that girl run away with the Stille.
Laufen is still inexperienced.
She leaves too many traces of mana.
You could easily track her, Frieren.
You think of us as nothing more than a nuisance.
Pretty much.
So, you know of me.
No mage of my generation doesn't know your name.
Though this is my first time meeting you in person.
I was sure of it the moment I saw you.
You're the mage from the heroes' party—Frieren.
She's famous?
She's a legendary mage.
I was wondering if she was who I thought she was.
Elves really don't age, do they?
So, you're challenging us openly, huh?
You've been scoping us out
this whole time, haven't you?
I thought you would do something more cowardly.
No, we're plenty cowardly.
While Denken stalls you,
I'm going to kill one of these two brats.
I see.
If we lose a party member and are disqualified,
I'll be forced to give up.
Bring it on. Try your best.
Lawine, this guy's strong.
I know.
Stop that, Richter. We just need to stall for time.
We can win.
Denken, I thought you were more
cold-hearted and ruthless than that.
You're an Imperial Mage, aren't you?
You must've gotten rid of political
enemies more than a few times.
I just don't think becoming a first-rank mage
is worth killing someone over.
That I agree with.
First-rank is just a title.
I don't believe it has that much worth.
I'm shocked.
You're taking the exam without
even knowing about the privilege?
The privilege?
The founder of the Continental Magic Association
who suddenly appeared in public half a century ago,
and reigns as the master of human magic.
The Great Mage Serie.
She's still pursuing tempered mages,
like those of the age of war with the demon king's army.
That's why she's promised those who
become first-rank mage a special privilege.
She grants them one spell of their choosing.
Serie is a living grimoire encompassing
almost all spells from throughout history.
She's the closest mage on earth
to the all-seeing, all-powerful Goddess.
You could obtain immense wealth,
or cure serious illnesses,
or obtain enormous power.
To receive a spell of your wish
is to be granted a mage's greatest desire.
People are simple.
Thanks to that, first-rank mages are now
a bunch of monsters, barely even human anymore.
That's how valuable it is.
I see.
Ridiculous.
Denken, not many have
no interest in the special privilege.
Let's begin.
Denken, stall her for one minute.
That's all I need to kill them both.
Don't make me repeat myself, Richter.
They're just a pair of brats.
You just need to put them to sleep for three hours.
You can babysit some kids, can't you?
Denken.
I'll crush her.
That's good enough, isn't it?
Senile old man.
Balgland.
The young ones are too hot-blooded, aren't they?
And
I'm
al
right
I'll
be
al
right
Yeah,
I
hear
you
I
care
a
bout
ling
the
wind
u
pon
my
hair
and
loo
king
back
a
gain
have
come
days
that
you
spent
with
Each
mo
ment
had
pur
pose
and
you
knew
it
all
those
years
with
all
the
pain
that
it
might
bring
thank
ful
for
all
I've
been
through
These
fee
lings
are
my
proof
I'm
live
I'll
ne
ver
beg
or
pray
That
gain
nee
kyou
da
ke
wa
So
just
dashi
think
back
on
you,
my
friend
found
you
gain
Some
where
long
the
win
ding
road
woul
dn't
he
si
tate
stay
by
your
side
'til
the
end
A
ny
time,
a
where
place
that
I
go
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'll
al
ways
have
your
smi
le
A
ny
time,
a
where
itsu
mo
When
I
close
my
eyes,
see
you
ze
ttai
nan
te
naku
mo
There's
so
much
we'll
ne
ver
know
A
ny
time,
a
where
when
you're
al
ways
here
wi
thin
my
heart
A
ny
time,
a
where
know
my
tears
are
bound
ning
sky
is
sure
glow
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'm
whis
come
back
home
Damn greenhorn.
The gap in mana is too large.
What spell I desire?
But she's let her guard down.
Give me a break.
That old man's
I know!
This is Frieren.
sure going at it.
In the world of magic, hell does sometimes freeze over.
Episode 21
The World of Magic