We will now commence
the First-Rank Mage Selection Exam.
It's a team battle.
The fifty-seven of you will form
teams of three to take the exam.
You're
breeze
blow
ing
through
When
you
close
your
eyes,
sun
light
starts
fade
tell
what
you
might
be
thin
king
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
Once
your
eyes
once
a
gain
are
o
pen
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
zing
out
head,
clear
as
orbs
of
glass
Some
where
deep
wi
thin,
I
can
sense
the
clouds
clea
ring
blue
reign
and
ba
nish
gray
Buds
are
bloo
ming
storms
will
calm
as
the
fog
rolls
wer's
mist
I'll
take
con
trol
of
this
bea
ting
wi
thin
boku
We'll
be
one
with
the
wind
Let's
reach
the
clouds
yond
ring
end
less
ly
in
the
dawn
Episode 19: An Elaborate Plan
See, you can do it if you try.
Hehe, you think?
Lawine can be abrasive,
but she's always pushed me along.
We'll finally be fighting our first dragon tomorrow.
Are you scared, Eisen?
You're trembling.
Yeah.
I see, then—
Huh? You're scared?
Yeah.
I see. I'm scared, too.
What's with this conversation?
I was trying to raise morale
by imitating other adventurers.
I'm sorry, that didn't pan out as I expected.
No, you helped ease my nerves.
Himmel, you're fine as you are.
I'm sure these things are different for every group.
Probably.
I see, they really are different for every group.
We finally managed to catch a Stille.
That's a relief.
You say that like we can take it easy now.
What comes next is the real trouble.
We need to protect the Stille
from being stolen by the other teams.
It's time for some real combat.
Alright, let's go over what we've learned
while observing the Stille.
First of all, as you said, it can
fly faster than the speed of sound.
There's no way we can catch it at that speed.
It's also as tough as a dragon,
and doesn't even flinch when hit
with an average offensive spell.
It can also break restraints.
What's more, it's incredibly sensitive to mana.
Even if we suppress our mana
when approaching it, it quickly flies away.
But the biggest problem is that we can't
use mana detection to find one,
since it has almost none.
Which is why we have no idea
where any are right now,
or even how many there are.
We haven't seen any since
the three from yesterday morning.
They've probably gotten cautious
from all the examinees walking around.
If we're unlucky, we might not see another one.
Not that we'd have any ideas for how
to catch one if we do find it.
That'll be fine.
I was experimenting with a spell
that might help us catch one last night.
Oh yeah, you did go out.
What kind of spell is it?
You've already seen it.
The Spell That Catches Birds.
It's a folk spell that a tribe of hunters invented
back when there were far more mages,
and magic was more commonplace.
Oh yeah, you did immobilize that thing with magic.
But that was a monster, not a bird...
Yeah, it's a folk spell.
It seems it can catch anything
that's vaguely like a bird.
It's a powerful binding spell.
I think it'll work on the Stille.
Why didn't you tell us?
We could have caught one yesterday with that.
It's not that easy.
The spell has a range of fifty centimeters.
That's how close I need to get.
Fifty centimeters?
How close have we gotten so far?
At best, three meters.
And they seem to notice us
starting at about twenty meters.
We're one step away from catching one, huh?
That's a pretty big step.
Just to confirm, you two don't have
any spells that can slow it down, right?
If I could freeze it properly, that would work,
but besides being sensitive to mana,
it's a tough fighter, and hard to freeze.
It would probably get away before I could freeze it.
I could easily slow it down
if I had a large amount of water,
but the magic I use can only manipulate water.
I'm not capable of creating it myself.
So, I can't use it if there's no water,
and large bodies of water don't conduct mana well,
so it's hard to do without imbuing
them with mana beforehand.
If it's dispersed, like with rain,
I can manipulate large amounts immediately.
But if I imbue the water with mana,
the sensitive Stille will definitely stay away.
It'll stay away...
I see. It'll stay away from it.
I have a plan that might work.
That's not a bad idea, but it's risky.
We'd be picking a fight with every other team.
But we probably won't
be able to catch one otherwise.
Are you scared, Lawine?
Graa! They're gonna come off!
Fine.
Let's do this.
Team 4
Land — Second-Rank Mage
For now, we should try to hide
until the end of the exam.
Team 4
Übel — Third-Rank Mage
What? That's so boring.
Mages should fight with pride and dignity.
Team 4
Fern — Third-Rank Mage
Mages also avoid needless fights.
Getting more water comes first, though.
I believe there was a lake
in the center of the exam site.
I'm glad we managed to capture
a Stille early on, though.
If we can hide until sundown,
we'll have passed the first stage.
What's up?
Looks like it's not going to be that easy.
You know, I thought this was a path,
but it's a dried-up river.
This isn't the first we've come across, either.
There's a barrier covering the exam area, right?
Yeah, it's standard for exams.
It's a completely impassable physical barrier.
Does it not let water through, either?
Judging by how dried out things are,
they must've set up the barrier about a week ago.
Most of the water will have collected
in the lake at the center of the basin, then.
We examinees are living beings,
so we need a certain amount of water to function.
That doesn't mean examinees
are going to gather around the lake.
That's true.
We can carry water around with us.
But the Stille is a living creature too, and it can't.
Oh, I see.
So those who've noticed this are going
to be camped around the largest watering hole—the lake.
Alright, I've decided.
Give up on the water.
Come on, that's gonna be rough. I'm already parched!
We can find a small pond somewhere.
That doesn't seem sanitary.
It should be fine if we boil it.
Team 8
Scharf — Third-Rank Mage
Ehre — Second-Rank Mage
Team 8
Wirbel — Second-Rank Mage
What a pain. I shoot to kill, you know?
You managed to react to that, huh?
Oh well. Hand over the cage with the Stille.
And if we refuse?
Then there's no more need for words.
That came from the lake.
She froze the whole lake!
What's the big idea?
This is no laughing matter.
That mana was from Team Two.
What are they thinking?
Do they plan on making
enemies of every other team?
What are you doing?
Melt it! Quickly!
Denken, what should we do?
This is a waste of time and effort.
Team 13
Denken — Second-Rank Mage
There's no point in melting it.
Team 13
Richter — Second-Rank Mage
Now that they've used magic that flashy,
the Stille won't go near the lake anymore.
Team 13
Laufen — Third-Rank Mage
We'll steal the Stille from Team Two.
If they're making this much of a scene,
they must have a plan to catch one.
Lady Frieren, what are you trying to do?
Let's split up for now.
Hurry up and melt the frozen lake!
How foolish.
If they use that much magic to melt the ice,
the lake will become truly unusable.
The Stille won't come here again.
Let's go!
Yeah.
Over there.
Those who've noticed that seem
to be looking for other watering holes,
but their mana detection is lacking.
They won't be able to handle the threats of the skies.
They're naïve.
Team Two apparently froze the lake!
Are they trying to ruin the exam?
Ruin the exam?
They've got it wrong.
This is an elaborate plan that Team Two came up with.
There's nothing to be done about it
if we don't unravel their scheme.
They were done in by monsters.
They're already dead.
Let's go.
Gramps, let's at least get them down.
It's not like you don't see them, right?
They're circling above us.
And not just one or two, either.
They've cast magic on the corpses.
If we try to get them down, we'll be detected.
They're Geisel. That's how
they lure in and hunt their next prey.
That team completely fell for it, and was annihilated.
That's insane.
Why would they choose a place
with monsters like that for the exam?
It's like they don't even care if the examinees die.
This is your first time
taking the first-rank exam, isn't it?
There's an extremely simple reason.
They don't need anyone who
would die to this as a first-rank mage.
The Continental Magic Association
is particular about the caliber of first-rank mages.
There are people still dreaming
of the strong and proud mages from the era
of the war with the demon king's army.
How ridiculously behind the times.
That's surprising, Denken.
I thought you would support those ideals.
Mages don't need caliber.
First-rank should just be
a straightforward symbol of authority.
If a mage cannot win over the hearts of the people,
then no matter their skill,
they might as well be powerless.
I've seen countless mages
far more brilliant than myself
fall from power and be oppressed.
Great power is feared. And authority
gained through fear doesn't last long.
Besides, magic isn't proud
or noble or anything like that.
I see. So, you're just the right level of weak?
Big words, young boy.
Against you, I could win with my eyes closed.
We're not detecting Team Two at all.
They must be lying low and concealing their mana.
This place, too. Every watering hole we've seen.
They've been imbued with a tiny amount of mana.
I can't tell at all.
Can you?
No, me neither. Team Two's handiwork?
Even the person behind it probably can't sense it.
That's how minuscule it is.
But the Stille can sense it.
They won't come to this watering hole anymore.
What's the point...
Oh! There's a watering hole
without mana somewhere.
Team Two is guaranteed to be near that one.
How are we gonna find it?
I'm going to rest for a while.
Denken.
The exam area is vast.
There's no way we can find mages
who are seriously hiding themselves.
We'll wait.
They're going to tell us their location anyway.
I've imbued mana into all
the ponds and lakes I could find.
There's a chance there are some I missed, though.
Limiting the ones the Stille can use is plenty.
Well then, I'm going to lie in wait for the Stille here.
No way, I didn't think
it was possible to erase your mana.
It's not complete.
If I move, some mana
will leak out, no matter what. See?
I can't tell at all.
We'll be the look-outs.
Don't drag us down.
Shut up.
I'd be more useful if only we had some rain.
Yeah, the barrier's repelling all of it.
Frieren, did you get it?
It was worth picking a fight with the other teams.
We cleared the first-stage exam!
No.
Found them.
As expected, they finally used magic.
No matter how skilled they may be,
this is the one moment they can't cover up.
We've been detected.
We need to move...
before... it's too late.
Jubelade.
Dolagat.
It's like artillery.
She backed away again.
The way she fights is refined and leaves
no openings, but it's an old one.
I feel like I'm fighting my grandpa.
Standard offensive and defensive magic.
You're only using basic spells.
You don't intend to show your hand yet?
I've been instructed to only use
basic magic in combat.
So it's your master's policy.
Yes. She said this is sufficient for the modern age.
I see.
It's happening again. What is this weird feeling?
It's almost like I'm fighting a seasoned mage.
You've got it rough.
If you were facing Wirbel instead of me,
you'd already be dead with that kind of fighting style.
That doesn't make sense.
You're the strongest on your team, aren't you?
Wirbel has fought the remnants
of the demon king's army.
He's the captain of the Northern Mage Corps.
He has far more combat experience than me.
He uses utterly unscrupulous,
cowardly magic, and does whatever it takes to win.
The girl that's fighting him right now,
she's probably going to get killed.
Is that so?
And
I'm
al
right
I'll
be
al
right
Yeah,
I
hear
you
I
care
a
bout
ling
the
wind
u
pon
my
hair
and
loo
king
back
a
gain
have
come
days
that
you
spent
with
Each
mo
ment
had
pur
pose
and
you
knew
it
all
those
years
with
all
the
pain
that
it
might
bring
thank
ful
for
all
I've
been
through
These
fee
lings
are
my
proof
I'm
live
I'll
ne
ver
beg
or
pray
That
gain
nee
kyou
da
ke
wa
So
just
dashi
think
back
on
you,
my
friend
found
you
gain
Some
where
long
the
win
ding
road
woul
dn't
he
si
tate
stay
by
your
side
'til
the
end
A
ny
time,
a
where
place
that
I
go
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'll
al
ways
have
your
smi
le
A
ny
time,
a
where
itsu
mo
When
I
close
my
eyes,
see
you
ze
ttai
nan
te
naku
mo
There's
so
much
we'll
ne
ver
know
A
ny
time,
a
where
when
you're
al
ways
here
wi
thin
my
heart
A
ny
time,
a
where
know
my
tears
are
bound
ning
sky
is
sure
glow
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'm
whis
come
back
home
What kind of hell
Next,
did you experience?
I'll sever your head.
I'll crush her.
This guy's strong.
Bring it on.
This is impressive.
What's this sound?
Senile old man.
I've always killed when necessary.
Episode 20
Necessary Killings