I'm Lady Frieren's apprentice.
Pass.
Next.
You're
breeze
blow
ing
through
When
you
close
your
eyes,
sun
light
starts
fade
tell
what
you
might
be
thin
king
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
Once
your
eyes
once
a
gain
are
o
pen
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
zing
out
head,
clear
as
orbs
of
glass
Some
where
deep
wi
thin,
I
can
sense
the
clouds
clea
ring
blue
reign
and
ba
nish
gray
Buds
are
bloo
ming
storms
will
calm
as
the
fog
rolls
wer's
mist
I'll
take
con
trol
of
this
bea
ting
wi
thin
boku
We'll
be
one
with
the
wind
Let's
reach
the
clouds
yond
ring
end
less
ly
in
the
dawn
I know you well, Imperial Mage Denken.
Well, that's an honor.
Having worked your way up
from serving with the army,
you're now the most influential
mage in the Northern Lands.
It's a tale I often hear of.
To be honest, I would have liked
to meet you when you were young.
Your young days, back when
you were passionate and ambitious.
I have no interest in cinders.
Or so I thought.
You've changed your mind?
When you saw me, you thought
about how you'd fight me, didn't you?
Just for a moment. I immediately gave up.
Pass.
Your fire hasn't gone out.
Most people won't even consider fighting me.
Next.
Pass.
We haven't talked about anything yet, though?
Is a conversation necessary?
I guess not.
Next.
You think this is a joke?
What is?
This is the first-rank exam.
What kind of idiot doesn't show up to the venue?
For what it's worth, my real body is also at the venue.
Otherwise, I'd be disqualified—
Your real body hasn't left your hometown
at any point during the exam, has it?
Enjoying your afternoon tea right now?
I'm surprised.
Even Übel didn't notice.
You've got guts.
Pass.
Next.
The captain of the Northern Mage Corps, Wirbel.
The most combat-oriented
of the second-rank mages I know.
You realized you couldn't beat me at first glance.
But that wasn't a judgment born from fear.
I wouldn't even be second-rank
if I picked fights I couldn't win, would I?
I suppose that's true.
Tell me your favorite spell.
Magic is a tool for killing.
There's no liking or disliking it.
Pass.
Next.
What... did you think, looking at me?
Um, I thought you looked small and cute.
What is going on with this year's examinees?
Pass.
Sense.
I should apologize.
We did have a lot of good examinees this year.
I failed.
There's always next time.
Would you stop following me already?
Three years, huh?
Lady Frieren, I passed.
Good job.
Frieren.
It's thanks to you I managed to get this far.
Now I can go to my hometown and pay my respects.
I see.
Hey, Fern...
Can we go already?
Let's get this—
Gramps, this—
Hrm.
Eat as much as you like.
I seldom got to eat sweets when I was young.
Thank you very much.
What is this situation?
You have some too, boy.
Thanks, old man.
Who is this?
This is Denken, the Imperial Mage.
Huh, Imperial Mage.
Wait, he's a noble?!
Um, apologies for speaking rudely.
I don't mind.
I came to this city as a mage.
But you're treating me to all this
even though you don't know me...
It's not like I have a use for all my money.
That can't be true.
He's right, what about your grandchildren?
I have no children, nor grandchildren.
My wife passed away during my mid-twenties.
She always had a weak constitution.
She was the daughter of a remote
noble family that lost a power struggle.
While she languished, I sought out wealth and power.
I knew of no other way to save her.
She passed away shortly before Serie
started advertising the special privilege
and created the Continental Magic Association.
I've never felt as powerless as then.
How ironic that now, entire nations would march on my command.
Fern.
Magic was only a tool for politics to me.
Could you tell Frieren that she allowed me
to remember how fun magic used to be to me?
I became a mage out of admiration
for Frieren of the heroes' party.
Please tell her yourself.
I'm sure she'll be happy to hear it.
You're right.
I'll do that.
As expected from the city of magic, Äußerst.
I found lots of good grimoires.
Hey, granny.
They go in this basket, right?
I can't believe you just ignored that.
I thought about it for a moment, you know.
Just a moment, huh?
Pretty surprising, for a comrade of Himmel the Hero.
For a comrade of Himmel the Hero?
I'm the one who's surprised.
I heard you tried to kill Fern
and her team in the first-stage exam.
Fern was complaining.
She said you looked like the kind of guy who'd kick a dog.
I get told that a lot.
It's just an intimidation tactic.
Well, there was someone the world
might have been better off without.
I'll do anything to protect my hometown.
The reason I wanted to be a first-rank mage
was for the privilege of getting any spell I asked for.
If I obtain a strong spell, it'll make
it that much easier to slaughter demons.
But separately from that,
I try to help out people when I can.
Why?
My hometown is a remote village in the north.
There are still many
legends of Himmel the Hero there.
Conquering the Tower of a Thousand Mirrors.
Fighting Böse the Immortal,
or the Hell Emperor Dragon.
I loved those tales as a kid.
But the elders never talked about those stories.
It was always about defeating
some aggressive monster,
escorting some merchant,
or in the worst cases,
even about carrying some crates.
Nothing amazing at all.
Boring stories.
That's what I thought.
But the elders all so happily
kept talking about those stories.
After Himmel the Hero died,
and the remaining demons started
rampaging, it got real clear to me.
It was true—the Tower of a Thousand Mirrors,
Böse, the Hell Emperor Dragon...
even the demon king himself
didn't have much to do with my village.
Everyone had their hands full
protecting their own livelihoods.
I'm sure if Himmel the Hero
hadn't come to my village,
it wouldn't be around today,
even if the world had found peace.
I see. What are you trying to say?
What got me this far are those
stupid tales of Himmel the Hero.
That's all I was trying to say.
I guess I lost track of time.
I'm going home with those guys, in the end.
Frieren.
Treasure your encounters.
Death isn't the only thing
that can part people forever.
But I guess you're well aware of that.
Frieren, can't you float
us over with magic one by one?
If I do that, I'll be left on this side by myself.
Himmel, we need to defeat
the demon king as quickly as possible.
What point is there in this minor errand?
You're right, it is a minor errand.
I'm sure the world won't change because of this.
But if someone in front of me is in need of help,
I have no intention of turning my back on them.
It's alright, Himmel.
The world did change.
The special privileges are being awarded tonight,
and we can bring people with us.
It's a rare opportunity, so let's all go together.
She's making a really unhappy face.
I heard we could bring people with us.
I'm terribly sorry.
On Lady Serie's orders, Lady Frieren is banned.
You're not to enter the Continental Magic
Association's buildings for a thousand years.
Lady Frieren hasn't even done anything.
That's how it is.
I upset Serie, after all.
She's really such a child.
Well, it's not like I came because I wanted to.
I'll wait outside.
I'll wait outside, too.
Hey!
It's the evening bell.
The conferment should be finished soon.
Yeah.
A first-rank mage.
The pinnacle of mages, of which
there are less than fifty in the world.
Fern really has come far.
I'm sure Fern will become
a more famous mage than me in this age.
Frieren.
It feels good.
Yeah, it does.
Lady Frieren.
Who's that?
He's from the Continental Magic Association.
I'm Lernen, a first-rank mage.
One of Lady Serie's apprentices.
It seems Lady Serie has caused you trouble.
I don't mind.
She's always been like this.
What's up, Frieren?
You can see them, can't you?
The fluctuations in my mana.
What an incredibly powerful mage.
You're out of place in this age of peace.
Indeed, I'm an outdated mage
who knows nothing but combat.
Lady Serie tells me this, too.
If I'd been born during
the war with the demon king's army,
I would have carved my name into
history alongside the legendary champions.
I see.
So, what are you here for?
The only one of Lady Serie's
apprentices to leave her mark on history
is the Great Mage Flamme, who has passed into myth.
Once I die, another testament
of Lady Serie's life will disappear.
I don't want to leave her all alone in the future.
Even if that is by the infamy of having
taken down the legendary mage, Frieren.
I would like to request a duel, Lady Frieren.
We will not have a duel.
It's a waste of time.
Jeez.
Mages who know nothing
but combat sure tend to be bad with words.
There's no need for you
to leave your mark on history.
Serie will remember you.
One last thing before I leave.
These flowers were made with magic.
What of it?
It's the spell Master liked.
Didn't you say it was a stupid spell?
Flamme was a failure, to be honest.
Even as talented as she was,
she couldn't reach my heights.
I took many more apprentices after her.
Most of them passed away
without even coming close to my power.
But it's strange.
Even though I took those apprentices on a whim,
I still vividly remember both the personality
and favorite spells of each and every one of them.
Frieren, for some reason,
I've never regretted taking an apprentice.
Even if they didn't leave their mark on history.
She can't even honestly convey
her feelings to her apprentices.
She really is a child.
Lady Frieren.
The conferment is over.
Alright, let's go.
Lady Frieren, what happened to your shoulder?
I need to get that healed at the church.
I hope it's still open.
Bad with words, indeed.
Both you and me.
Stark, what are we gonna play today?
Sorry, I can't play with you today.
Stark, have you had breakfast?
Yeah, I have.
Stark, have a cup before you go.
Oh, thanks.
The journey of a warrior is long and fraught.
Take care of yourself.
Yeah.
Our time in Äußerst is finally over, huh?
You sure are beloved
no matter where we go, Sir Stark.
Am I?
By the way, Fern, what spell did you get yesterday?
Can you tell?
Your clothes are clean.
And they have a bit of a floral scent.
Could it be?
It's the Spell That Makes Clothes Clean and Fresh.
Doing laundry is going to be easy now.
As expected from the living grimoire, Serie.
That's a legendary spell,
said to have existed in the age of myth.
I'm proud of you, Fern.
That's my apprentice for you.
Of course, Lady Frieren.
Lady Serie seemed really unhappy about it, though.
Are you insane?
I can imagine.
Serves her right.
They're here.
Frieren.
Thanks a lot.
We failed this time, but we're
going to try again in three years.
I see, that's good.
It was fun.
Take care of yourself.
See you.
Yeah, see you.
This also happened with Sir Sein,
but you really do goodbyes casually.
Same with Kraft.
Himmel, you really do goodbyes casually, don't you?
Is that weird?
It does seem a little unlike you.
Even if it was just a job,
we did travel with him for two whole weeks.
And we had such a good time
drinking with him every night, too!
Sorry excuse for a priest.
That's true.
But as we continue our journey,
we may meet him again.
A tearful goodbye wouldn't suit us.
I mean, it would be embarrassing the next time we met.
It would be embarrassing the next time we met.
What's that about?
Episode 28: It Would Be Embarrassing the Next Time We Met