Indeed, the journey of a warrior knows no end.
You're one step closer
to grasping the secrets of the art.
There is nothing more for me to teach you.
You've been telling me that every day...
Oh, Fern?
She's totally pissed! What happened?!
I'm scared.
You're
breeze
blow
ing
through
When
you
close
your
eyes,
sun
light
starts
fade
tell
what
you
might
be
thin
king
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
Once
your
eyes
once
a
gain
are
o
pen
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
zing
out
head,
clear
as
orbs
of
glass
Some
where
deep
wi
thin,
I
can
sense
the
clouds
clea
ring
blue
reign
and
ba
nish
gray
Buds
are
bloo
ming
storms
will
calm
as
the
fog
rolls
wer's
mist
I'll
take
con
trol
of
this
bea
ting
wi
thin
boku
We'll
be
one
with
the
wind
Let's
reach
the
clouds
yond
ring
end
less
ly
in
the
dawn
Episode 27: Age of Humans
I had a fight with Lady Frieren.
Again?
Isn't this happening a lot lately?
The next stage is the last, right?
This doesn't seem like the time...
She was much worse this time.
My staff broke during the fight
in the Ruined King's Tomb,
so I wanted to go with Lady Frieren and get it fixed.
She said I would be better off throwing
my old staff away and getting a new one.
The one that broke into a thousand pieces, right?
She was saying it was beyond repair.
Even so, I received that staff from Sir Heiter.
It's been with me since I was little.
This is Frieren, after all.
I don't think she meant any harm.
I can't believe she would even suggest that.
Three years until the next first-rank exam, huh?
Three years is a long time, isn't it?
Go on, make fun of me, like always.
Do you want me to?
No.
Then would you like some head pats, Lawine?
You wanna fight?
Hurry up.
You're really bummed, huh?
Oh, it's Frieren.
What's in that bag?
Hey, how long are you gonna loiter around here?
I've failed the exam.
We're strangers now.
You're obstructing business, get a move on.
I'm here as a customer.
Then buy something already.
You can have one.
Don't want it.
You were unlucky this time.
You drew the short end of the stick.
It could have happened to any of us.
A loss is a loss.
I wasn't good enough.
But never talk to me about that again.
I may not look it, but I feel awful right now.
But you're still opening your shop, huh?
Denken, you may not know this,
but people need to work to provide
for themselves, no matter how awful they feel.
I see.
Well, it's probably for the best
that I'm the one who failed.
The first-rank mage exam is once every three years.
Denken, there might not be another three years
for an old geezer like you, after all.
True enough.
Don't just take it like that.
Richter, you really are a cocky whippersnapper.
You deride authority and have no qualms
about trampling over the weak for your goals.
One can hardly call that admirable behavior.
And yet, I don't dislike you at all.
I'm sure that's because I myself
used to be that kind of cocky whippersnapper.
But now I hold the position of Imperial Mage.
What are you trying to say?
Don't be so pessimistic.
You'll be much stronger
in three years than you are now.
Laufen, let's go home.
Sorry, Gramps is pretty awkward.
Just what are you to Denken?
Old geezer.
He didn't even buy anything in the end.
Is it my unlucky day or something?
I asked around; is it true you can
fix any staff, no matter how broken it is?
Show me.
What is this pile of scrap?
Are you trying to tell me this is a staff?
Garbage like this is just a nuisance.
It's not garbage.
Probably.
I was feeling a bit better, but thanks to you,
I'm back to feeling absolutely awful.
I have the right to deny requests.
Give up on this staff.
I see.
If you can't fix it, that's fine.
Frieren.
You really get under my skin.
When did I say I couldn't fix it?
Think you can finish it today?
I'd like to make it in time for the third-stage exam.
A lot of tall orders...
Frieren.
What?
Sorry for calling it garbage.
It's a good, well-maintained staff.
I'm sure it's been held quite dearly.
Fern, let's go home.
Lady Frieren just doesn't understand me at all.
I don't really understand you, either.
Stop it! Don't take it out on me!
I was trying to say I think
it's important to try understanding.
I think Frieren is doing the best she can.
Oh, you're Frieren's...
Apprentice?
Am I wrong?
No, she is.
Well, either way, I had one hell
of a day thanks to your master.
A man just can't catch a break around here, can he?
I would have made more
if you'd just gotten a new one, too.
Take care of it.
My staff.
Frieren isn't very emotional or empathetic.
You're sure to have fights and misunderstandings.
But there's a good side to that, too.
Frieren will spend all the more time
worrying over what she can do for you.
You'll have a hard time
finding a better master than her.
Lady Frieren, about yesterday...
What?
No, actually, never mind.
I see.
The third-stage exam begins now.
Do you know why
I've come all the way out here, Sense?
Silent, huh?
You're always like this
when put in a bad position.
Twelve have passed the second-stage exam.
That is an abnormal number. It's too many.
Exams where everyone
has to cooperate are entirely fine.
Apparently cooperation flies
above the heads of the current first-ranks.
I'm sorry.
But there was someone more powerful
than there should've been in that exam.
You mean Lady Frieren.
Thanks to her, many who weren't worthy passed.
If the third-stage exam was held
as planned, they would all die.
Sense, that isn't something you wish for, is it?
Besides, even I don't desire
for that many lives to be wasted.
Lady Serie.
You don't need to apologize.
It's all Frieren's fault.
Extraordinary times
call for extraordinary measures.
I will take charge of the third-stage exam.
I'll select them peacefully.
You were the examiner, right, Lernen?
I take it you don't have any objections?
This isn't the first time
I've borne your whims, Lady Serie.
Besides, I am not capable of testing Lady Frieren.
I noticed she was restricting
her mana the moment I saw her.
Her mana is immense.
Enough to rival yours, Lady Serie.
Falsch, did you notice?
No, I don't know what you're talking about.
I witnessed her mana at the exam venue.
I cannot imagine it was being restricted.
There were none of the characteristic fluctuations.
No creature possessing mana
can hide those fluctuations.
Even if it were possible, it would require
an unfathomable amount of time.
It does not at all seem like a practical technique.
Frieren has dedicated her life
to that impractical technique.
To deceive demons.
Demons are much more sensitive to mana than us.
One or two hundred years of restricting your mana
will not deceive them without a born talent for it.
It's truly a waste of time.
If you used that time for other training,
you could become many times stronger.
It's about as inefficient as can be.
But that inefficiency
can sometimes create an opening.
In a fight among experienced mages,
misjudging your opponent's mana often means death.
Frieren is, in fact, rather
unskilled relative to her age,
yet has continued to win against demons.
That's just how much Frieren
has refined her mana restriction.
As far as I know, the only one to see through it
at first sight was the demon king himself.
That is, until just now, Lernen.
It was a coincidence.
I just happened to see a slight fluctuation.
That is all.
How very modest of you.
It's been half a century since
you were the first to become a first-rank mage.
You're still the same cowardly boy, huh?
All the more a shame.
You've come this far,
and yet you haven't got long left.
You will probably never fight Frieren.
Even if that was a fight you could win.
I really shouldn't take humans as apprentices.
It truly is a shame.
I guess he wasn't able to notice, either.
The fluctuations in my mana.
The third-stage exam is
an interview with the Great Mage Serie.
So that's how it's going to be.
You will be called in order
once preparations are complete.
Serie has no intention of letting either of us pass.
Please wait here until then.
Do you know her?
From long ago, yeah.
She's probably going to pass people based on instinct.
Serie's instinct is always right.
I have, in fact, not reached
the heights of magic Serie desires of me.
Excuse me.
Fail.
Leave.
Can I ask why?
You're intimidated by my mana as we speak.
You understand well where you stand.
You can't visualize yourself
as a first-rank mage, can you?
In the world of magic, you cannot
realize what you cannot visualize.
That's the most basic of fundamentals. Leave.
Fail.
Frieren.
You too cannot visualize
yourself as a first-rank mage.
But for a different reason than the other examinees.
You don't think there's
any chance I'm going to pass you.
It's a fact, isn't it?
I'll give you one chance.
Tell me your favorite spell.
The Spell That Creates a Field of Flowers.
A spell you learned from Flamme.
Truly stupid.
Fail.
I see.
I insulted you, and you're
just going to take it?
I really can't imagine how
a mage like you defeated the demon king.
It wasn't my power alone.
Himmel, Eisen, Heiter, and I.
We couldn't have won
if any one of us had been missing.
You were blessed with good comrades.
You got lucky.
That's right.
I was lucky.
Say, Himmel, why did you recruit me to your party?
We were searching for a strong mage.
There are plenty of those in the royal capital.
It didn't have to be me.
I wanted you.
Why?
Frieren, you probably don't remember this,
but I've met you once before.
Yeah, I don't remember at all.
Yeah, you wouldn't.
When I was a kid, I went into
the forest to gather herbs, and got lost.
I wandered the forest at night for a long time,
and tasted solitude for the first time.
I thought I might never
find my way back to the village.
That's when an elf told me
the way to the nearest village.
She really only told me the direction,
with not a word of comfort.
Child that I was, I thought
you were a really cold-hearted person.
I don't know if you noticed
my unease, or if it was just a whim...
But you showed me the Spell That Creates a Field of Flowers.
I thought it was beautiful.
For the first time in my life,
I saw beauty in magic.
I'm sure this is nothing more than a coincidence,
but what led me to meet Himmel and the others
was that stupid spell Master taught me.
Also, Serie.
I'm sure you intend to fail Fern the same way,
but I don't think you'll be able to.
She's going to exceed your expectations.
The age of humans has come.
Exceed my expectations?
She's paralyzed just seeing my mana.
She's no different than the other examinees.
Wait.
What do you see?
It's fluctuating.
You said your name was Fern?
Become my apprentice.
What? I'd rather not.
You won't regret it.
I'll guide you to even greater heights.
To heights no mage has ever seen before.
Is this related to passing the exam?
It might be related.
I see.
Lady Serie.
Fern.
I'm sure Serie will tell you all sorts of things,
but you don't have to give in to her requests.
Much like I'm going to fail, no matter what I say,
you're going to pass, no matter what you say.
Serie's instincts are always right, after all.
I'm Lady Frieren's apprentice.
Frieren told you what to say, didn't she?
I'm not so stupid I'd let a promising mage go by.
Pass.
Next.
And
I'm
al
right
I'll
be
al
right
Yeah,
I
hear
you
I
care
a
bout
ling
the
wind
u
pon
my
hair
and
loo
king
back
a
gain
have
come
days
that
you
spent
with
Each
mo
ment
had
pur
pose
and
you
knew
it
all
those
years
with
all
the
pain
that
it
might
bring
thank
ful
for
all
I've
been
through
These
fee
lings
are
my
proof
I'm
live
I'll
ne
ver
beg
or
pray
That
gain
nee
kyou
da
ke
wa
So
just
dashi
think
back
on
you,
my
friend
found
you
gain
Some
where
long
the
win
ding
road
woul
dn't
he
si
tate
stay
by
your
side
'til
the
end
A
ny
time,
a
where
place
that
I
go
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'll
al
ways
have
your
smi
le
A
ny
time,
a
where
itsu
mo
When
I
close
my
eyes,
see
you
ze
ttai
nan
te
naku
mo
There's
so
much
we'll
ne
ver
know
A
ny
time,
a
where
when
you're
al
ways
here
wi
thin
my
heart
A
ny
time,
a
where
know
my
tears
are
bound
ning
sky
is
sure
glow
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'm
whis
come
back
home
Episode 28
It Would Be Embarrassing the Next Time We Met
Alright, see you.