This is the goal of my journey.
To meet up with my best friend
who set out ten years ago.
Did you find out where Gorilla was going?
Tür.
It's a trading city in the center of the Northern Lands.
Far to the east from here.
The opposite direction of Äußerst.
Yeah.
Frieren, I set out on this journey
to follow in Gorilla's footsteps.
I know.
The sun's about to set,
so why don't we figure everything out tomorrow?
I asked them if we could use the cabin in the village.
They said we're free to use it.
Thanks.
You're
breeze
blow
ing
through
When
you
close
your
eyes,
sun
light
starts
fade
tell
what
you
might
be
thin
king
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
Once
your
eyes
once
a
gain
are
o
pen
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
zing
out
head,
clear
as
orbs
of
glass
Some
where
deep
wi
thin,
I
can
sense
the
clouds
clea
ring
blue
reign
and
ba
nish
gray
Buds
are
bloo
ming
storms
will
calm
as
the
fog
rolls
wer's
mist
I'll
take
con
trol
of
this
bea
ting
wi
thin
boku
We'll
be
one
with
the
wind
Let's
reach
the
clouds
yond
ring
end
less
ly
in
the
dawn
Episode 17: Take Care
I got some firewood.
I bought ingredients for dinner.
My hands are freezing.
It's gotten pretty cold, after all.
Wow, you're right.
This might be a new record, even.
Lemme see, too.
You're right, they're really cold.
Right?
Stop!
A new record, isn't it?
Yeah, it's stupid cold.
These kids...
It's snowing.
Will we need to hunker down
through the winter again?
We're not trying to cross any
steep mountains this time,
so it'll be fine as long as we don't get hit by a blizzard.
We got hit by one.
We sure did.
Yep.
Cold fronts around here last for around a month.
I'd recommend you stay here for the time being.
You're free to use the cabin for a while.
What are you going to do, Sein? Will you leave?
You need to ask that?
I guess you can't leave until the cold front passes.
Exactly.
That said, there's a pub and a store here,
and the cabin is pretty spacious.
We've got it a lot better than
we did in the mountains last time.
And best of all, there's a magic store
run by a shady old man in this village.
Based on my previous experiences, that's
the best kind of place for finding legendary magic.
Having the time to search that store is great.
Legendary magic?
What kinds of magic have you found so far?
A spell that erases mold and
a spell that removes stubborn oil stains.
Amazing.
Those were indeed convenient
enough to revolutionize cleaning.
Are these like grandma's household tricks?
Anyway, we're just going to have to wait it out.
To underestimate winter in the Northern Lands
is tantamount to suicide, after all.
Sir Stark did almost die last time.
I'm from the Northern Lands, you know?
I'm well aware.
Looks like we'll be together for a little bit longer.
The cold front should pass soon.
You'll finally be able to set out.
Yeah, finally.
Wait, haven't we spent almost no time together?
Sein.
Do you have a moment?
What's up, Frieren?
It's rare for you to come to the pub.
Stark and Fern are acting weird.
I think they're having a fight. Can you mediate?
I don't mind, but why are you asking me?
Mediation is the priest's job.
It is?
What a scene.
Hey, what happened?
It's Sir Stark's fault.
Yes. It's all my fault.
This is getting us nowhere.
Come to the other room, one at a time.
So, what happened?
You know how when we first got here,
Fern touched my cheek with her cold hand?
Oh yeah, I remember that.
I got back at her today.
And Fern got really pissed.
What are you, twelve?
You know she wouldn't like
having her face touched like that.
Are you fine leaving it like this?
I want to make up with her.
Stark, unlike me, you're a good boy at heart.
Just be honest and say you're sorry.
If you want to make up with her,
you gotta tell her that.
Frieren won't mediate your fights, you know?
Yeah, I know. I'll apologize to her.
Stark feels bad about it.
He's just being childish,
he didn't mean you any harm.
I know.
I was being unreasonable.
I want to apologize.
I'm the one who started this in the first place,
and I'm not bothered by being touched.
It's just that he was holding my shoulder so strongly.
It scared me a little.
Do you hate Stark?
Why would you ask such a thing?
Does it look like I do?
Then go tell him that it
was scary and make up with him.
Be more gentle.
I'm sorry.
Get together already!
I don't really get it, but I can see
you're really trying your best.
Thanks, you've been a great help.
Frieren, you're about the only
person who praises me like a kid.
You are a kid, aren't you?
Well, it doesn't feel bad.
Say, I've been wondering.
What makes you look after me so much?
Even back when you invited me on this journey...
I guess it was self-loathing after all.
The way you were avoiding going on your adventure
reminded me of myself before
I left to defeat the demon king.
It made me really mad.
That doesn't really constitute a reason, though.
I think that's why I wanted
to give you the opportunity to leave.
What do you mean?
I mean, that's what Himmel the Hero would've done.
Take my hand, Frieren.
I'm your chance to embark on a journey.
Himmel and the others gave
me the courage to set out,
and taught me the joy of being with friends.
What do you think, Sein?
It's been fun, hasn't it?
Yeah.
It's been really fun.
I'll become an unforgettable champion,
just like Himmel the Hero.
I'm talking about the present, Sein.
And I believed what she said.
Gorilla talked about you a lot.
He talked about how you two would
leave your mark on history as champions.
I'm going to go after Gorilla.
I'm done regretting my choices.
I understand.
Take care.
See you again.
See you.
We split up pretty unceremoniously, huh?
Well, Sein is an adult, unlike you two.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
It sure is quiet being by myself.
29 years after the death
of Himmel the Hero
Northern Lands,
The Offens
Huh?
That's unusual, they're still asleep.
We've been walking all day recently,
so they must be pretty tired.
I guess that's alright.
Hey, breakfast's ready. It's time to wake up.
Fern?
Hey, Frieren, wake up.
Just another half a day.
Isn't that too much sleep?
More importantly, it looks like Fern is sick.
Hey.
Stop it.
Yeah, she has a fever.
She'll need to keep warm and rest more.
Hmm.
That's strange.
I brought some water.
There it is.
What's that?
A notebook about medicinal herbs that Sein left us.
Oh, that was nice of him.
If I can figure out the illness
with magic, we'll know which herbs to use.
Isn't identifying illnesses the goddess's magic?
Don't you need the holy scriptures to use that?
I do own a copy of the holy scriptures.
Huh?
It's being used as a trivet!
Even if I don't have any talent as a priest,
I can at least identify basic illnesses.
Not complicated ones, though.
Is she going to be okay?
Yeah, it's just a cold.
What herbs can we find in this region...?
That reminds me,
I think I once gathered herbs
with Himmel and the others near here.
For now, let's find a place to get away from the cold.
You're right.
Oh dear.
You're a real lifesaver.
I didn't expect anyone to be
living this deep in the mountains.
There was a village here last time I came by.
It's been decades since this was a village.
It was a storied place that
even the hero once passed through.
Well, take your time and rest up.
Thanks.
By the way, there was an icicle cherry tree nearby, right?
Yes, north of here.
The path there is somewhat tangled, though.
That's fine.
I've been there before.
Alright, I'm going to go back to work.
Wait for a bit, Fern.
We'll go grab ingredients for your medicine.
You've been holding her hand since we got here.
I mean, she looks quite uncomfortable.
Holding her hand will put her more at ease.
She's been like this since she was a kid.
What's wrong?
Lady Frieren, that's embarrassing.
Why?
Don't treat me like a kid.
I see, okay.
I guess she'll be a full-grown
adult in another two years.
She was only this tall not too long ago.
I was taller than her for
most of our time together, too.
She grew up in a flash.
You see, in my mind, Fern is still a child.
That'll probably never change.
Frieren.
We should hurry and get
the ingredients for the medicine.
Yeah.
We're almost at the icicle cherry tree.
So that icicle cherry tree is our last ingredient?
Well, we'll be using
the mushrooms that grow at its roots.
It's pretty, isn't it?
I wish Fern was here to see it, too.
It might be my favorite winter blossom.
The petals are poisonous, so be careful.
Say, why were you holding Fern's hand?
You don't treat her much like a kid normally.
I don't think I was treating her like a kid.
I was just holding her hand
to try and comfort her.
It's the only way I know to soften her pain.
I wonder what I should've done.
I think you just gotta do what you feel like doing.
That's what Master did.
I think we all need some emotional support.
Everyone appreciates getting support like that.
What do you think you're doing?
You were groaning in your sleep.
It's easy to feel lonely when you have a cold, after all.
My mother, who died when I was young,
used to hold my hand like this.
It makes you feel strangely at ease.
That was when you were a child, though, wasn't it?
Children aren't the only ones
who need emotional support.
It doesn't feel bad, right?
I guess not.
I suppose it is nice.
I'm handsome when I'm caring, too, aren't I?
Shut up.
We finished the medicine.
Fern was probably embarrassed because I was there.
You don't want others to see
you getting pampered, you know?
Thanks, Stark.
I'll try doing what I want.
In return, I'll hold your hand if you catch a cold, too.
No thanks, that's embarrassing.
Alright, let's grab these mushrooms.
There we go.
They're bigger than I expected. Scary!
Now we add the other ingredients,
and mix everything very well.
You look like a witch. Incredibly scary!
Open up, Fern.
You're good at this. Thanks for the help.
Am I?
It's okay, you'll get better soon.
Lady Frieren, I'm not a child anymore...
I know.
I'm well aware.
Do take care of yourself!
Thank you for everything!
Feeling better now, huh?
It's thanks to you, Lady Frieren, and Sir Sein's notes.
The woman here took good care of me, as well.
Alright.
Then we're off to Äußerst, the city of magic.
And
I'm
al
right
I'll
be
al
right
Yeah,
I
hear
you
I
care
a
bout
ling
the
wind
u
pon
my
hair
and
loo
king
back
a
gain
have
come
days
that
you
spent
with
Each
mo
ment
had
pur
pose
and
you
knew
it
all
those
years
with
all
the
pain
that
it
might
bring
thank
ful
for
all
I've
been
through
These
fee
lings
are
my
proof
I'm
live
I'll
ne
ver
beg
or
pray
That
gain
nee
kyou
da
ke
wa
So
just
dashi
think
back
on
you,
my
friend
found
you
gain
Some
where
long
the
win
ding
road
woul
dn't
he
si
tate
stay
by
your
side
'til
the
end
A
ny
time,
a
where
place
that
I
go
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'll
al
ways
have
your
smi
le
A
ny
time,
a
where
itsu
mo
When
I
close
my
eyes,
see
you
ze
ttai
nan
te
naku
mo
There's
so
much
we'll
ne
ver
know
A
ny
time,
a
where
when
you're
al
ways
here
wi
thin
my
heart
A
ny
time,
a
where
know
my
tears
are
bound
ning
sky
is
sure
glow
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'm
whis
come
back
home
Could you
show me that?
Try it if you dare.
Time to
take a breather.
We've got
quite the lineup
You wanna put it to the test?
this year.
There's no way I can do it by myself.
You have the eyes of a murderer.
Don't call me an elder.
No clue.
We will commence the First-Rank Mage Selection Exam.
Episode 18
First-Rank Mage Selection Exam