No wonder the Ruined King's Tomb is impenetrable.
I sure wasn't expecting something like this.
Denken, do you have
any countermeasures against that?
Let's just say,
if this wasn't an exam, I would
have long since broken the flask.
You're
breeze
blow
ing
through
When
you
close
your
eyes,
sun
light
starts
fade
tell
what
you
might
be
thin
king
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
Once
your
eyes
once
a
gain
are
o
pen
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
zing
out
head,
clear
as
orbs
of
glass
Some
where
deep
wi
thin,
I
can
sense
the
clouds
clea
ring
blue
reign
and
ba
nish
gray
Buds
are
bloo
ming
storms
will
calm
as
the
fog
rolls
wer's
mist
I'll
take
con
trol
of
this
bea
ting
wi
thin
boku
We'll
be
one
with
the
wind
Let's
reach
the
clouds
yond
ring
end
less
ly
in
the
dawn
Episode 24: Perfect Replica
The lord of that dungeon is the mirror devil, Spiegel.
It's a monster of the age of myth that is
mentioned in the legends of Ewig the Sage.
It is thought that Spiegel reads
the memories of those who enter the dungeon
and uses them to create a replica of the target.
There are monsters with similar powers
in modern times, like the Einsam.
But Spiegel imitates people's
power, mana, and even techniques,
creating flawless physical replicas.
It's why the Ruined King's Tomb is still uncleared.
Why did Sense pick such a venue for the exam?
The replicas are just as strong as the targets.
To defeat them without sacrifices,
one needs teamwork and
an awareness of one's weaknesses.
It's quite a fitting exam for a pacifist like her.
This is bad.
Fall back!
Denken!
Now, what shall we do about this?
A dead end, huh?
We're in quite the pinch, aren't we?
Four-eyes, can you give me
your opinion as an expert on cloning magic?
I told you, my name is Land.
I guess it doesn't matter.
How perfectly do you think
that replica is copying me?
Übel, you're the kind of person
who keeps talking during a fight, aren't you?
Almost like you'd die if you stopped.
How observant of you.
Yeah, I might die.
It's quiet.
Does that mean it's not copying
my memories or personality?
No, it probably just can't talk.
It stole the escape golem
from my pocket during the initial assault.
I see, that is something I'd do.
It also knows about us.
It's not coming after us even though we're cornered
because it's wary of your Solganiel.
Either that, or it's toying with us
for its own enjoyment.
That's disturbing.
You're bleeding a lot.
Four-eyes, you're not gonna last long at this rate.
I suppose not.
Can you tell me one last thing?
Are you the real four-eyes?
Well, who can say?
Use my flask.
That's for your survival.
Huh, is that so?
Alright, four-eyes. Give me a minute.
I'll get back your flask.
Hey, wait—
Yeah, of course it's going to close the distance.
Solganiel requires the target's
entire body to be in view.
Whoever misjudges the distance first is going to lose.
Since we're equal, I'm going to need luck to win.
I've always had the worst luck,
so I hate fights that rely on luck.
That's why I don't want to be fighting against myself.
Man, I just can't help but rush to my death.
Yeah, I've got the worst luck.
That's why I didn't want to do this.
That said,
it looks like your luck was even worse.
Four-eyes, you got here faster than I expected.
So the flask was fake, after all.
Übel... You knew that wasn't the real me, didn't you?
Why rush to your death like that?
Because I was sure you'd come to my rescue, I guess.
Do I look like I'm that nice to you?
Nope, not at all.
Besides, that's irrelevant.
You didn't accept my flask, four-eyes.
You don't want someone else
to die because of you, right?
That's why I designed a situation
where I'd die because of you.
Thanks, four-eyes.
I feel like I understand you a bit better now.
I see, good for you.
So, will you be able to empathize with me?
I think I still need more time.
I think we're pretty close to the core.
Lady Frieren, there's a staircase over there.
Fern, show me the map.
I think we've finished exploring this floor.
There's a hidden room on the other side of this wall.
I'm sure there's treasure.
It feels like... there might be a rare grimoire in there.
There wasn't anything
that looked like an entrance, though.
That's true.
But there's definitely a room here,
considering the layout of the dungeon.
Lady Frieren, this is amazing.
It depicts the triumphs of the buried king.
I've never seen a mural of
the Unified Dynasty in such good condition.
This is a valuable discovery.
It's magnificent, isn't it?
We're making progress almost too smoothly.
Are we just going to easily pass the exam at this rate?
Maybe.
What's up?
Why are you waiting around here?
Considering the layout, the core is beyond this room.
And?
That thing has been standing
guard for half a day already.
This is getting interesting.
This is how conquering a dungeon should be.
A perfect replica, huh?
It does indeed look like it's as powerful as me.
We can't reach the core without
doing something about that replica.
Do you have any ideas?
Let's see... If it really is a complete recreation of me,
I guess it would have the same
weaknesses as a live mage.
To defeat a superior mage, you can use
either restraining magic or mind control magic.
I'm resistant to both, though.
They could create a slight opening, though.
That should be all you need to defeat it.
Methode.
You're good at these kinds of tricks, aren't you?
I wouldn't say I'm particularly good at them.
Well then, excuse me.
This is curious.
My restraining spell isn't working.
You smell nice.
It normally works, unless there's a large gap in mana.
Lady Frieren, please look me in the eyes next.
Mind control isn't working, either.
I'm not capable of breaking
Lady Frieren's mental defenses.
Oh, dear.
Looks like you really are resistant to both.
While her mental defenses are complex and sturdy,
they seem to use quite an old structure.
An expert in mind magic
might be able to exploit a weak point.
Are you aware of any among the examinees?
Edel, the second-rank mage, should be able to.
However, unlike me,
she has absolutely no fighting ability.
I'm honestly not sure whether
she'll be able to make it here...
The use of mind control also relies
on the assumption that the target has free will.
Are the replicas really detailed enough for that?
We're still lacking a lot of information.
Edel, what do you think that is?
Who knows.
However, it seems safe to assume
it's just as strong as the first-rank mage, Sense.
There's only so long we can hide
while concealing our mana.
We've got to defeat it.
You think we can defeat it, Blei?
It's one thing for me, but neither
of you can properly fight in this dungeon.
Modern magic isn't suited
for dungeon combat in the first place.
That's a result of most dungeons having been cleared
around the time the demon king was defeated.
With powerful defensive spells
taking so much of our mana,
offensive spells utilizing the environment
have become more common.
Manipulating existing matter takes far less mana
than creating new matter does, after all.
That thing has a powerful advantage in that regard.
Countless spells are cast on its hair.
I think we can assume it has plenty
of options for fighting in a dungeon.
By my reckoning, we can't win against it.
Magic is all about imagination.
That replica freely manipulates the nigh-
uncountable number of threads that make up hair.
Its ability to visualize
is far beyond that of any normal human,
so there's no doubt it's
a vastly more powerful mage than us.
I honestly think it's a miracle we've
been able to avoid it for this long.
We did our best.
Combat wasn't our forte anyway,
so it's about time we give up.
Honestly, I'm scared and want to go home.
Edel, would your voice not work?
Mind control magic is my clan's specialty,
but don't think I'll be able to fulfill
the conditions for advanced commands against that.
At most, I might be able to
make it kneel to create an opening.
Even then, I'd need to speak
the command while looking it in the eyes.
So it's not impossible.
Assuming it has free will.
How long do we need to stall it?
Fifteen seconds.
Not like any more than that is feasible, anyway.
What do you mean?
You're about to see.
Defend us from all directions!
Huh?
In modern magic combat, there are
two ways of overcoming defensive magic.
Either you break it down with sheer mass,
or you bypass it with technique.
A large quantity of attacks usually implies the latter.
I'm surprised.
I didn't think someone would use both.
The attacks have the weight of boulders.
I'd thought we would last fifteen seconds
with a complete defensive barrier,
but it broke through so fast.
But our eyes have met.
The best mages carefully observe their opponents.
Kneel!
I see how it is.
It doesn't have free will.
It's but a thorough imitation of a person's free will.
We have no chance of winning.
I guess we had no choice
but to ride the coattails of others.
Run, and try to join up with the combatants.
As I said, I'm giving up.
I'm sick of this pain.
It even protects you, now that's convenient.
We should run, too.
Is anyone going to reach
the core of the dungeon like this?
I told you.
She never intended to pass anyone.
We're still lacking quite a lot of information.
We should consider what to do
if the replica doesn't have free will.
Though I guess it'll turn into
a pure contest of power, then.
Could you beat it?
Dunno, not sure.
Damn it, I have no idea what they're thinking.
Though, as expected, our matchups are looking good.
Ehre would completely overwhelm
the two of us in a pure contest of mana.
But I know how to strategize to win.
No matter the opponent, no matter the situation.
A contest of power, huh?
Um, in that case,
I might be able to kill Lady Frieren.
Is that so?
Yes.
Alright,
let's make a plan.
And
I'm
al
right
I'll
be
al
right
Yeah,
I
hear
you
I
care
a
bout
ling
the
wind
u
pon
my
hair
and
loo
king
back
a
gain
have
come
days
that
you
spent
with
Each
mo
ment
had
pur
pose
and
you
knew
it
all
those
years
with
all
the
pain
that
it
might
bring
thank
ful
for
all
I've
been
through
These
fee
lings
are
my
proof
I'm
live
I'll
ne
ver
beg
or
pray
That
gain
nee
kyou
da
ke
wa
So
just
dashi
think
back
on
you,
my
friend
found
you
gain
Some
where
long
the
win
ding
road
woul
dn't
he
si
tate
stay
by
your
side
'til
the
end
A
ny
time,
a
where
place
that
I
go
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'll
al
ways
have
your
smi
le
A
ny
time,
a
where
itsu
mo
When
I
close
my
eyes,
see
you
ze
ttai
nan
te
naku
mo
There's
so
much
we'll
ne
ver
know
A
ny
time,
a
where
when
you're
al
ways
here
wi
thin
my
heart
A
ny
time,
a
where
know
my
tears
are
bound
ning
sky
is
sure
glow
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'm
whis
come
back
home
Alright, here's the plan.
Let's make a plan.
So, we had information.
Could we cooperate?
Maybe you should
It's truly
just apologize?
They don't have
unpleasant.
any weaknesses.
You look like
you're having fun.
Episode 25
Fatal Gap
It's a fatal gap in Frieren's defenses.