Northern Lands,
The Ruined King's Tomb
First off, let me congratulate the eighteen of you
Second Exam — Examiner
Sense — First-Rank Mage
on passing the first-stage exam.
I've been hearing quite a lot of speculation
regarding the exams I've headed.
I'm sure some of you
have heard these rumors as well.
But there's no need to be nervous.
The exam is very straightforward.
Anyone aiming to be a first-class mage
should be able to get through it without issue.
I will now explain the specifics
of the second-stage exam.
You're
breeze
blow
ing
through
When
you
close
your
eyes,
sun
light
starts
fade
tell
what
you
might
be
thin
king
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
Once
your
eyes
once
a
gain
are
o
pen
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
zing
out
head,
clear
as
orbs
of
glass
Some
where
deep
wi
thin,
I
can
sense
the
clouds
clea
ring
blue
reign
and
ba
nish
gray
Buds
are
bloo
ming
storms
will
calm
as
the
fog
rolls
wer's
mist
I'll
take
con
trol
of
this
bea
ting
wi
thin
boku
We'll
be
one
with
the
wind
Let's
reach
the
clouds
yond
ring
end
less
ly
in
the
dawn
Episode 23: Conquering a Dungeon
For the second-stage exam,
you will conquer a dungeon.
You will be conquering the Ruined King's Tomb.
There is just one requirement to pass.
You must reach the core of the Ruined King's Tomb.
I'm a pacifist; I don't like conflict.
Thus, all who reach the core will pass.
Wait.
This is an uncleared dungeon,
from which many adventurers have not returned.
Do you intend to fail everyone again?
What do you mean?
We're looking for the pinnacle of mages.
Achieving the impossible
is what makes a first-rank mage.
The uncleared and uncharted
are no issue to the first-rank mage.
How should we prove that we reached the core?
Should we bring back coin or treasures?
There is no need for you to prove it.
I will accompany you to the core.
Though, naturally, I won't be helping you examinees.
I will also give each of you one of these flasks.
They're escape golems, developed
by the first-rank mage Lernen.
If you break the flask, a golem
will appear and carry you out of the dungeon.
They're prototypes, but should be sufficiently safe.
You will fail the exam if you use it,
but if you feel you can't continue
due to injuries or the like, don't hesitate to use it.
I don't condone the deaths of promising talent.
The flasks will also break
automatically at dawn tomorrow.
That is the time limit for the second exam.
The exam starts now.
There are multiple entrances.
Looks like the dungeon dates to the Unified Dynasty.
Dungeons of that age
always have multiple entrances,
which are all connected to the core.
If we investigate each of them,
we should be able to get a rough idea of the dungeon's layout.
We should all split up and—
Why are you assuming we'll work together?
There is no need for conflict in this exam.
We will fare better if we all cooperate.
That's out of the question.
Unlike the first exam, the survival
of allies isn't a requirement to pass.
Grouping up doesn't mean
you're obligated to save anyone,
and you even risk being sacrificed
when push comes to shove.
You especially seem pretty
knowledgeable about dungeons.
I'll go by myself.
Well, considering what happened in the first exam,
it'll be hard to team up
with people we don't really know.
Let's go.
Wait a moment.
Fools.
To think they don't understand
how advantageous teaming up is.
Let's go, Fern.
Are you sure, Lady Frieren?
There's no cooperation to be had here.
Not after that display.
Hm.
Well then, I will follow you two.
I feel like you'll reach the core with the least trouble.
Don't get in the way.
I won't.
I will neither hinder nor help.
This is the safest path.
Let's proceed carefully while we map out the place.
That stone there...
It's a trap, so be careful.
You really are knowledgeable about dungeons.
That wasn't always the case,
but Himmel liked dungeons.
We explored a lot of them
on monster extermination requests.
What do you mean, he liked dungeons?
Just what I said.
He said they excited him.
Doesn't make sense, does it?
It's the staircase to the next floor.
I see, so this path's a dud.
Let's go back to that last fork.
Indeed.
Why? Our target is the monster
at the core of the dungeon.
When will you learn, Eisen?
You're meant to fully clear each
floor of the dungeon before proceeding.
That's common sense for adventurers.
Think you mean "uncommon nonsense."
You think I'm a clown, don't you?
Isn't it best if we can
have fun while helping people?
It's not always going to be this easy.
Dungeons are going to become more dangerous as we go on.
Yeah, what she said.
I'm going to enjoy this until the end.
We'll have fun adventuring, exploring dungeons,
defeating monsters, searching for treasures...
And before we know it, we'll have saved the world.
That's the kind of journey I want.
Besides,
there might be a rare
grimoire at the other side of the fork.
What are you waiting for? Let's hurry.
It really doesn't make sense, does it?
Let's go, Kanne.
It's only the five of us left, huh?
If we had all cooperated and divided roles,
we would have had a good chance
of conquering this place.
We had enough skilled mages here to do it.
Denken, not everyone can be that rational about it.
You said it yourself at the end of the first exam.
It must've rubbed them the wrong way.
Just think of it as only
the smartest of us remaining.
At the very least,
there's no one here who would drag us down
by falling for a simple trap like a mimic.
Isn't that good enough?
As if anyone in this exam would be that foolish.
Let's go.
This mana...
It might be a grimoire.
Lady Frieren, you saw me check
this chest with Miekheit, right?
It's a mimic.
Fern, that spell is accurate 99% of the time.
What about it?
There are historical discoveries that were only
made because great mages caught on to that last 1%.
I'm sure of it.
There's a precious grimoire in here.
My experience as a mage is telling me so.
It's dark! It's scary!
So scary!
So dark and scary!
I may have picked the wrong people to follow.
Don't step on the center of the floor.
The ceiling will come falling down.
Is that human-shaped stain there...
That's brutal. Even the bones are gone.
Gargoyles!
Denken, someone was trapped.
I know.
She's on the other side of that wall.
Stand back.
It's no use, after all.
Nothing we can do.
Break the flask!
Wow.
We've lost one already, huh?
The slightest misstep can be fatal.
This is the Ruined King's Tomb, huh?
Hey, Fern, listen.
Stop pulling for a minute before I split in half.
Alright.
At times like this,
you have to push instead of pull.
The mimic will go bleh and stop biting down.
What are they, dogs?
I'm saved.
Geez.
What did you do when you were by yourself?
I'd blow them up
with offensive magic from the inside.
But it makes my hair all frizzy, so I don't like doing it.
I'm home.
My hair turned into drills.
So that's why your hairstyle
changes every now and then.
Why?
Well, let's put that behind us,
and continue exploring.
Those are Gargoyles.
Let's defeat them before they move.
These medals are all over the place, aren't they?
I think there's an eccentric who collects these.
This seems like the right path, so let's turn back.
Why?
This is going surprisingly smoothly.
It does seem strange for an uncleared dungeon.
The core should be close, too, considering the layout.
Either way, we can't let our guard down.
Let's take a break once we find
the next burial chamber.
We found some pretty good stuff.
It just looks like junk to me.
Hm.
I don't understand.
Truly.
How does stuff like that make her happy?
She's rubbing her face on it...
You're the one I don't understand, Fern.
I've never seen a mage
as young as you with such skill.
You must have trained quite a lot.
Yet I don't sense any passion
or determination in you.
You're a strange girl.
I became a full-fledged mage
to repay my debt to someone.
That was my life's goal at the time,
so I gave it my all,
never once thinking about what would come after.
I must've used up all my
passion and determination back then.
Then why do you continue to pursue magic?
Lady Frieren looks like she's having fun, doesn't she?
That she does.
The first time I entered a dungeon,
Lady Frieren was smiling about
the junk artifacts she was collecting.
I couldn't help but smile with her.
I think the reason I pursue magic is because
I enjoy seeing her be so passionate about it.
Let's move on.
Following you two was the right choice, after all.
I'm sure you'll be able to enjoy
even this grueling dungeon.
The ambience has changed.
The core might be close.
Wirbel.
What, can't walk anymore?
I've been restrained.
There are three mages with hidden mana.
It's an ambush.
Scharf, block their line of sight.
The spell cast on Ehre is Solganiel.
I'm aware.
No wonder the Ruined King's Tomb is impenetrable.
I sure wasn't expecting something like this.
Scharf, you take me.
Ehre, go for Scharf.
I'll crush Ehre.
Let's do this shit.
Replicas made with magic.
The work of a monster or demon, I imagine.
I've never seen such a perfect non-personal replica.
It was equal to Laufen in both mana and skill.
It even carried itself the same.
It might be exploiting your memories.
Not a great feeling.
Being able to tell they're fake
at a glance is the only saving grace.
At least we don't have to worry about friendly fire.
If the caster of this spell
can manipulate multiple replicas at once,
they'll make a terrifying threat.
Either way, we were right to group up.
It gives us more countermeasures against them.
Denken, do you have
any countermeasures against that?
Let's just say,
if this wasn't an exam, I would
have long since broken the flask.
And
I'm
al
right
I'll
be
al
right
Yeah,
I
hear
you
I
care
a
bout
ling
the
wind
u
pon
my
hair
and
loo
king
back
a
gain
have
come
days
that
you
spent
with
Each
mo
ment
had
pur
pose
and
you
knew
it
all
those
years
with
all
the
pain
that
it
might
bring
thank
ful
for
all
I've
been
through
These
fee
lings
are
my
proof
I'm
live
I'll
ne
ver
beg
or
pray
That
gain
nee
kyou
da
ke
wa
So
just
dashi
think
back
on
you,
my
friend
found
you
gain
Some
where
long
the
win
ding
road
woul
dn't
he
si
tate
stay
by
your
side
'til
the
end
A
ny
time,
a
where
place
that
I
go
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'll
al
ways
have
your
smi
le
A
ny
time,
a
where
itsu
mo
When
I
close
my
eyes,
see
you
ze
ttai
nan
te
naku
mo
There's
so
much
we'll
ne
ver
know
A
ny
time,
a
where
when
you're
al
ways
here
wi
thin
my
heart
A
ny
time,
a
where
know
my
tears
are
bound
ning
sky
is
sure
glow
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'm
whis
come
back
home
Now,
Smells good.
It's about time
we give up.
what shall we do about this.
Since we're equal,
That's disturbing.
I'm going to need
Please
luck to win.
look me
in the eyes.
So, it's not impossible.
How long do we need to stall her?
Episode 24
Perfect Replica