If something is to kill you,
it'll either be the demon king...
or a human mage.
You're
breeze
blow
ing
through
When
you
close
your
eyes,
sun
light
starts
fade
tell
what
you
might
be
thin
king
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
Once
your
eyes
once
a
gain
are
o
pen
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
zing
out
head,
clear
as
orbs
of
glass
Some
where
deep
wi
thin,
I
can
sense
the
clouds
clea
ring
blue
reign
and
ba
nish
gray
Buds
are
bloo
ming
storms
will
calm
as
the
fog
rolls
wer's
mist
I'll
take
con
trol
of
this
bea
ting
wi
thin
boku
We'll
be
one
with
the
wind
Let's
reach
the
clouds
yond
ring
end
less
ly
in
the
dawn
Episode 26: Pinnacle of Magic
It blocked our attack.
Within expectations.
From here on out, it'll be a battle of attrition.
They really are here.
Methode's observations were right.
Don't drag me down.
That's my line.
Methode has determined
the precise locations of the replicas.
If they swarm us, we won't have a chance.
We should split up and fend
them off before they gather here.
We've shared our worst matchups.
A bad matchup for you is also
a bad matchup for your replica.
Our advantage is being able
to strategize and cooperate.
If we correctly choose our opponents,
we should have the edge in battle.
If you cannot beat your opponent
by yourself, outnumber them.
It's almost funny how easily I can fight.
We should be able to keep
the replicas at bay this way.
Okay. As planned, then.
Yes, I wish you luck.
I have one concern.
I'm not detecting a replica for every examinee here.
In particular, I can't find
our greatest threat, Lady Sense's replica.
Yeah, I can't detect it, either.
We definitely can't overlook Sense's replica.
If we're attacked from behind,
I won't be able to protect Fern.
If worst comes to worst, we both might die.
I haven't been able to locate
Lady Fern's or Sir Denken's replicas, either.
I'll have to search with
more accurate short-range detection.
If you weren't here,
this wouldn't be a concern, though.
First-rank mages must be able
to weather unreasonable adversity.
This isn't even unreasonable.
Besides, you can pass the exam
just by protecting your allies.
Truly a kind, peaceful exam, don't you think?
We beat them.
Doesn't feel good, though.
An ambush.
Absurd.
I don't believe I ever neglected my mana detection.
Lawine, break your flask, too.
You're mature enough
to know when to give up, right?
There's another exam in three years.
Damn it.
I didn't make it.
Though I imagine my aid
wouldn't have changed the outcome.
Even though it has its back turned,
there's no hint of an opening.
Regardless, I'm going to have to buy some time.
You're the Imperial Mage, Denken, right?
What's the situation?
Are you planning to fight that thing?
I don't think you can win, though?
I'm well aware.
Hey, Denken, do we really need
to fight this to conquer the dungeon?
Frieren is—
I don't need an explanation.
Is it necessary?
It is.
Let me handle it, then.
What are you talking about?
Denken is the strongest of us.
And besides, you couldn't even win against Wirbel.
That's not really the point, though.
It's true, I'm an inexperienced third-rank mage.
I'm much weaker than Wirbel or Denken.
But I think I can win against Sense.
This is the spell I'm best at.
The Spell That Can Cut Just About Anything: Relseiden.
Anything I believe it can cut, it cuts,
and anything I don't believe it can cut, it doesn't.
What about it?
It's easily blocked by defensive magic.
Oh yeah, you were watching
my fight with Wirbel, weren't you?
Yeah, defensive magic
is designed to block magic, after all.
I can't really visualize it being cut.
Is that so?
Then it won't work on Sense anyway.
Even just counting what I can detect,
several layers of spells equal to defensive
magic have been cast on its hair.
Like I said, I don't care about any of that logic.
I'm talking about visualization.
Hey, wait.
Hm.
As expected, Solganiel doesn't work.
Hair is part of one's body, after all.
I can't get its whole body in my field of vision.
Relseiden.
As expected, my replica's opponent is Übel.
The outcome of that fight is clear.
It probably won't even be a real fight.
It was during the Second-Rank
Mage Selection Exam two years ago.
The first-rank mage, Burg,
was in charge of the exam.
He'd never been wounded
since becoming a first-rank mage.
That's how specialized in defense his magic was.
The Indomitable Cloak,
a cloak he created with his magic,
was woven with enough defensive enchantments
to repel all manner of attacks.
The rules for passing
the second-stage exam were very simple.
The examinees were to attack Burg's cloak,
and make him take even a single step back.
The reason murder would disqualify examinees,
was to make people have a modicum
of restraint, and to protect the other examinees.
Next.
No one was worried about Burg in the least.
Oops, I cut too much.
But he was easily killed by a nameless girl,
who had only just become a third-rank mage.
I'm disqualified, right?
I know.
Can I go?
I have one question for you.
Go ahead.
How did you get through the Indomitable Cloak?
Um, Lady Sense, have you ever done any sewing?
No. What about it?
You do seem like you come from a good family.
Or do you just do that kind of stuff with magic?
Well, you know, I'm kinda clumsy,
so I've never done anything like that either.
I used to watch my sister sew a lot.
You see, when cutting cloth,
you start with the scissors like this,
and cut it by sliding them along like this.
It makes a really nice sound.
I loved that sound.
What's your point?
I'm talking about visualization.
Cloth is something you can cut.
Everyone knows that.
She's insane.
It's true, anyone can visualize cutting cloth.
Even an idiot could.
But the world of magic isn't that simple.
You cannot use magic to realize
what you cannot perfectly visualize.
Much like an ant can't visualize
crushing a giant dragon beneath its feet,
there exist almost no mages who can visualize
cutting that cloak with all its enchantments.
Because any mage can tell at a glance
that his cloak will repel all manner of attacks.
Even an idiot could tell.
Intelligent creatures like humans
cannot escape those limitations.
And yet, she acted in accordance with her intuition.
Even though she intellectually
knew the cloak was uncuttable,
she followed her intuition, and constructed
an image of herself cutting up the cloak.
I cannot imagine her having a human mental state.
She's a savant.
Can I go now?
Yes.
By the way, Lady Sense, your hair is very beautiful.
Taking care of it must be a lot of work.
It's possible I had already lost at that point.
I can't visualize myself winning against Übel.
She's too bad of a match for me.
Everyone uses their head too much.
Hair is something you cut.
Taking care of my hair?
It's hell.
I don't even want to think about it.
She should just cut it, then.
I get the gist of the situation.
So you're buying time
for Frieren to take down Spiegel.
That's correct.
We also took care of three replicas.
That makes things simpler.
Well, then—
Oh.
It seems Lady Sense's replica was just defeated.
This mana...
it was Übel, the third-rank mage, who did it.
That's surprising.
You think so?
I think it was a pretty bad matchup.
Fights between mages are a bit
like rock-paper-scissors, after all.
Though an incredibly complicated
and difficult version, with countless different hands.
So you want to increase the number
of hands available as much as you can.
We're in.
We'll help stall the replicas.
I'm not one to trust strangers,
but I'm not stupid enough
to not join the winning team.
There are still two replicas we definitely
need to stall at the moment.
I've located one of them, Sir Denken's replica.
I'll ask you to take care of that one.
Please leave the other one,
Lady Fern's replica, to me.
It seems she is especially good at hiding her mana,
so if we don't find her, there very well
may be fatalities from an ambush.
Will you really be fine by yourself?
I can focus on mana detection better by myself.
She's quite strong, you know.
I'm rather versatile,
so stalling is one thing I'm good at.
Moreover, I've confirmed that restraining magic works on her in person.
There.
I can't move.
Alright, let's give them what we've got.
Übel, this...
isn't my imagination, is it?
Yeah, I don't think it is.
I mean, you can't move, can you?
My replica has regenerated.
You think this is going to continue
until that Spiegel thing is defeated?
It's a battle of attrition, this is getting fun.
You can say that again.
Isn't it time to give up?
That gap isn't good enough, either.
Fern doesn't have the experience to notice it.
That leaves me no choice.
The gap in mana detection
isn't going to be enough to get the kill.
You're right.
If only the gap was bigger, I could win.
But you would win, right?
Then let's make an opening.
Can you do that?
If I show an opening,
it will show an even bigger opening.
But then you will...
If I concentrate on defense, it won't be lethal.
Then, what's the strategy in that case?
I'll leave it to you.
Whatever you think works, will work.
How can you be so sure about that?
Because I underestimate you.
That's a relief.
We have good odds of winning this fight, then.
It's still standing,
but it's fatally wounded.
I need to finish it.
What happened?
Was I attacked?
I can't sense any mana.
I can't perceive this attack as magic.
Incredible...
Lady Frieren...
So this is the pinnacle of magic...
But... it's unlike you...
to be so wide open.
You did well, Fern.
I think it's been eighty years
since I was cornered enough to use that.
Alright, let's end this.
It's finally over.
I can't move anymore.
Wirbel, give me a piggyback ride.
You guys always collapse, don't you?
So this is the core of the Ruined King's Tomb.
You have conquered the Ruined King's Tomb.
This is a historical achievement,
worthy of a first-rank mage.
As promised, everyone who has reached
the core passes the second-stage exam.
So, where have our foremost contributors gone?
It's dark! It's scary!
It's dark and scary...
Well, I kinda get how she feels.
Dark and scary...
Well then, the second stage has concluded.
And they can even use healing magic!
What do you think, amazing, isn't it?
Who are you?
And
I'm
al
right
I'll
be
al
right
Yeah,
I
hear
you
I
care
a
bout
ling
the
wind
u
pon
my
hair
and
loo
king
back
a
gain
have
come
days
that
you
spent
with
Each
mo
ment
had
pur
pose
and
you
knew
it
all
those
years
with
all
the
pain
that
it
might
bring
thank
ful
for
all
I've
been
through
These
fee
lings
are
my
proof
I'm
live
I'll
ne
ver
beg
or
pray
That
gain
nee
kyou
da
ke
wa
So
just
dashi
think
back
on
you,
my
friend
found
you
gain
Some
where
long
the
win
ding
road
woul
dn't
he
si
tate
stay
by
your
side
'til
the
end
A
ny
time,
a
where
place
that
I
go
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'll
al
ways
have
your
smi
le
A
ny
time,
a
where
itsu
mo
When
I
close
my
eyes,
see
you
ze
ttai
nan
te
naku
mo
There's
so
much
we'll
ne
ver
know
A
ny
time,
a
where
when
you're
al
ways
here
wi
thin
my
heart
A
ny
time,
a
where
know
my
tears
are
bound
ning
sky
is
sure
glow
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'm
whis
come
back
home
It's been with me
You were
unlucky
since I was little.
this time.
A spell you learned from Flamme.
I may not look it,
It's serious,
huh?
but I feel awful right now.
We will now begin the third-stage exam.
Fern,
Go on,
make fun of me like always.
let's go home.
Episode 27
Age of Humans
The age of humans has arrived.