The first-stage exam is hereby concluded.
Team 1
Methode
Ton
Länge
A total of eighteen examinees,
comprising six teams, have passed.
Team 2
Frieren
Lawine
Kanne
Team 4
Fern
Land
Übel
The second-stage exam is in three days.
Team 8
Wirbel
Scharf
Ehre
Team 13
Denken
Richter
Laufen
We will notify you of the details in the coming days.
Team 17
Edel
Blei
Dunst
That is all.
You are dismissed.
You're
breeze
blow
ing
through
When
you
close
your
eyes,
sun
light
starts
fade
tell
what
you
might
be
thin
king
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
Once
your
eyes
once
a
gain
are
o
pen
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
zing
out
head,
clear
as
orbs
of
glass
Some
where
deep
wi
thin,
I
can
sense
the
clouds
clea
ring
blue
reign
and
ba
nish
gray
Buds
are
bloo
ming
storms
will
calm
as
the
fog
rolls
wer's
mist
I'll
take
con
trol
of
this
bea
ting
wi
thin
boku
We'll
be
one
with
the
wind
Let's
reach
the
clouds
yond
ring
end
less
ly
in
the
dawn
Episode 22: We'll Be Enemies Next Time
It's evening, huh?
Lazing around is pretty nice.
Who's that?
Coming!
Fern?
Weren't you out taking the exam?
We got back last night after the exam ended.
Sir Stark, it's evening right now, isn't it?
You were sleeping, weren't you?
You stayed up late, didn't you?
Yes.
What else?
I had some juice in the middle of the night.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry, alright?
You made her angry.
You just woke up, too, didn't you, Lady Frieren?
I got caught in the crossfire.
Looks like we're gonna need
to spend today pacifying Fern.
What are we going to do?
Let's go eat some tasty food.
Tasty food?
It's a little expensive,
but we found a nice place here
when we came through with Himmel's party.
That was eighty years ago, right?
You think it's still around?
Oh, my.
It turned on.
I told you I'd fix it, didn't I?
Thanks, you're always a great help, Richter.
You're welcome.
Ah, yes, take these as well.
Alright, see you later.
Hey, Grandma, I'm not a kid anymore.
I'm a grown man already.
You're still basically a child to someone my age.
You like those, don't you?
Sorry, I'm closing shop.
You see, an insane old man forced me into a fistfight.
I've got to rest up.
That sounds like quite the ordeal, Richter.
Why don't you come grab some food with us?
There's a restaurant I'm looking for,
but Laufen and I don't know our way around here.
Why are you with Denken in the first place, Laufen?
And what's that you're eating?
Gramps bought them for me.
I'm not sharing.
Wow, you've totally become his granddaughter.
Leave.
We're not a team anymore.
You lack political acumen.
If you're going to live as a mage,
it would pay to stay in my good graces.
There are plenty of restaurants around.
Just choose a random one.
My wife...
There's a place I once visited with my late wife.
I can't forget the taste of the food there.
You'll be treating me, yes?
Of course.
I told you it would pay.
Four-eyes.
Übel.
Nice to meet you, I suppose.
I guess you don't need clones
just to wander the streets.
I don't mind small talk,
but we're going to have to keep walking.
Sure, but if you try to run, I might end up killing you.
Can I ask you something?
Übel...
You have no qualms about killing people, do you?
Why didn't you kill Wirbel?
You had a chance, didn't you?
Oh, so you were watching.
Nothing gets by you, huh?
It's kinda hard to put into words.
I'm surprised.
You still want to be human, even though
your hands are already stained with blood.
That's right. I need the time
to gather the resolve to kill.
Because I could empathize with him, I guess.
I found myself wanting some time before the kill, too.
I can't move.
This is...
Solganiel.
The Spell That Binds Anyone in Sight.
The spells people are proficient in
reflect their life and character.
It's always been like that for me.
If I can empathize with a spell, I'll be able to use it.
If I can't empathize with it, I won't.
Four-eyes, your clones are such perfect copies,
they retain the same capabilities as the original.
What were you thinking?
What kind of life have you lived?
Tell me.
I see.
You're the type that uses magic by feel.
You just use spells, without even
understanding the underlying principles.
I hate brainless people like that.
That's not an answer.
I'm saying that I won't tell you,
because I don't like you.
You can kill me if you want.
However, you'll never have another chance
to empathize with me again.
Nah, I'm good.
I feel like I've gotten a glimpse of you.
I see.
I wanna know more.
Where were you trying to go?
Who knows.
Don't follow me.
This is it.
You made a good choice, Denken.
This is the best restaurant in town.
I come here often.
It's been fifty years since I came here with my wife,
but it hasn't changed at all.
How curious.
Are you sure?
Can I really order as many desserts as I want?
Yeah.
Denken, it's Frieren.
What should I get?
My recommendation is...
This is such a luxury, and it's not even my birthday...
Leave them, they look like they're having fun.
Meals are meant to be enjoyed.
That's why we're here.
Alright, it's time to stock up.
That sure is a lot of food.
Yeah, Lady Frieren does this occasionally.
Thank you for recovering this knife,
a family heirloom, from the demons.
I, Lecker, prodigy chef of the century,
will serve and reward you to the best of my abilities.
That's quite the heaping of food.
The food here is really good, after all.
I ought to thoroughly enjoy it.
Instead of eating that much at once,
you could just come here again.
I thought so too, but there are many
flavors I ended up never experiencing again.
Rest assured, Lady Frieren.
I intend to pass these
flavors on to future generations.
You will still find them
in one hundred, even two hundred years.
Is that so?
It's funny, all chefs say that.
They say that, and then their successors change it,
trying to leave their marks on history.
When that happens, you can go
and find even tastier food.
With all due respect, Sir Himmel,
no food in the world will surpass mine.
Then make sure you pass it down to the future.
That's the reward I ask for.
If it is the hero's request, I will make sure to achieve
this feat that no chef has ever achieved before.
Frieren, this is crazy good.
Am I allowed to be this happy?
Really? All that enthusiasm,
and the flavors still changed.
I won't have to search for tastier food, though.
It's even better than last time.
It really is good.
You've got some on your face, Sir Stark.
You need to eat your vegetables.
You've totally become her grandpa.
Huh, you're a surprisingly light eater.
What's it to you?
That was delicious, Lady Frieren.
I'm so glad we were able to cheer her up.
By the way, are we okay money-wise?
That wiped out my secret stash.
This is the spiritual state of nothingness.
You have done well to achieve
the essence of a true warrior.
There is nothing more for me to teach you.
Who's that old man?
I don't know.
He just randomly starts
talking to me while I'm training.
You sure are liked by strange people.
Anyways, you have a moment?
I need your help.
What happened?
She's totally pissed.
This is even worse than yesterday.
Yeah.
What did you do?
It was my turn to go shopping, but I overslept...
That's nothing out of the usual, though.
Why's it a problem now?
Fern's the type to let it build up, then explode.
What happens when she explodes?
She stops talking to me.
What are you guys, twelve?
Please, Stark!
Talk to her for me!
She won't listen to me!
What?
I don't wanna!
I'm scared!
That makes sense. Sorry for asking that of you.
Uhm, Miss Fern?
It looks like she's reflecting on her behavior...
I want some.
Huh?
I want some sweets.
What a pain...
Alright, let's go buy some together!
Is there anything left of my secret stash?
Oh, that guy...
I think he was Wirbel, of the Northern Mage Corps.
You're a warrior, aren't you?
Uh, what do you want from me?
What do you think?
What?!
This one's a miss.
What are they doing?
Sorry, I'm late, Kanne.
Lawine, that outfit is even cuter than usual.
My brothers are back from the imperial capital.
They buy all this unnecessary
stuff for me every single time.
I'm not a dress-up doll!
Mom gets all excited, too.
There's no stopping them.
You're even more spoiled than I am.
If that's what you think, switch with me.
It's hell being compared
to my overachieving brothers.
Come on, let's go. I feel like I'm gonna suffocate.
I'll be escorting you today then, Lawine.
Ow! Ow! They're gonna come off!
Um, Miss Fern, what shall we get?
Anything is fine, you can choose.
Anything is definitely not fine.
What should we do?
I'm the wrong person to ask.
Oh, it's Frieren.
Yeah.
This is perfect.
We were just about to go visit you.
Who are they?
They were on my team for the exam.
Yeah, Frieren helped us out a bunch.
She was like a teacher.
Because they kept quarreling.
That's on Lawine.
Ow!
I feel out of place among all these girls.
There, there.
Hey!
Huh?
You're a warrior, aren't you?
Uh?
Uh, wait.
Stop, what are you doing?
You're great.
What's going on?!
Crops are being thrashed by some Fressers,
and we accepted a request from
the Continental Magic Association to eliminate them.
We're looking for a vanguard.
We met during the exam.
Is this guy in your party?
Can we borrow him?
Go ahead.
So mean!
This is so mean...
They're taking him away, is that okay?
I'm sure it's fine.
He didn't seem to mean any harm.
It's almost like he's a different person.
He's probably the type to act
like a whole different person at work.
My brothers are like that, too.
Here, Frieren.
This is a thank-you gift.
I haven't done anything to be thanked for.
That's not true.
Without you, we couldn't
have passed the first-stage exam.
Thanks!
Thanks,
Sir Himmel!
Everything's okay now.
Yeah!
Alright, your mom and dad are waiting.
Why do you help people, Himmel?
Because I'm a hero.
That's not what I meant.
I guess...
It might be for my own sake.
I want people to remember me,
even just a little bit.
To live is to have others
know you and remember you.
What do you need to do for people to remember you?
Just a little bit is fine.
You just need to change someone's life a little.
I'm sure that's all you need.
And then Lawine...
No, that was you...
Huh, was it...
That other time too...
Lady Frieren, the sweets
they gave us are incredibly good.
She finally cheered up.
Oh yeah, you wouldn't wake up
for quite a while on the second day.
Don't talk about that.
She's going to start sulking again.
Frieren.
If the first-rank exam has
three stages, like in previous years...
We'll be enemies next time, won't we?
I guess so.
What is it?
It's a notice regarding the next exam.
The date, time, and location of the second stage,
as well as the name of the examiner.
The examiner is Sense, huh?
How unlucky.
Even though we passed the first stage.
What do you mean?
Sense has been the examiner of four exams.
No one has passed any of them.
This meat is so good.
Dude, you're amazing.
So this is the essence of a true warrior!
What a cruel task for an exam.
You think?
I'm a pacifist.
Unlike you, Genau.
And
I'm
al
right
I'll
be
al
right
Yeah,
I
hear
you
I
care
a
bout
ling
the
wind
u
pon
my
hair
and
loo
king
back
a
gain
have
come
days
that
you
spent
with
Each
mo
ment
had
pur
pose
and
you
knew
it
all
those
years
with
all
the
pain
that
it
might
bring
thank
ful
for
all
I've
been
through
These
fee
lings
are
my
proof
I'm
live
I'll
ne
ver
beg
or
pray
That
gain
nee
kyou
da
ke
wa
So
just
dashi
think
back
on
you,
my
friend
found
you
gain
Some
where
long
the
win
ding
road
woul
dn't
he
si
tate
stay
by
your
side
'til
the
end
A
ny
time,
a
where
place
that
I
go
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'll
al
ways
have
your
smi
le
A
ny
time,
a
where
itsu
mo
When
I
close
my
eyes,
see
you
ze
ttai
nan
te
naku
mo
There's
so
much
we'll
ne
ver
know
A
ny
time,
a
where
when
you're
al
ways
here
wi
thin
my
heart
A
ny
time,
a
where
know
my
tears
are
bound
ning
sky
is
sure
glow
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'm
whis
come
back
home
This sure is a surprise.
Gargoyles!
It's a Mimic.
That's brutal.
That's out of
the question.
The work of a
Even the bones are gone.
monster or demon,
I imagine.
Let's proceed carefully
while we map out the place.
It would be
a terrifying threat.
Episode 23
Conquering a Dungeon
For the second-stage exam,
you will be conquering a dungeon.