It's been a while, Flamme.
You're
breeze
blow
ing
through
When
you
close
your
eyes,
sun
light
starts
fade
tell
what
you
might
be
thin
king
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
Once
your
eyes
once
a
gain
are
o
pen
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
zing
out
head,
clear
as
orbs
of
glass
Some
where
deep
wi
thin,
I
can
sense
the
clouds
clea
ring
blue
reign
and
ba
nish
gray
Buds
are
bloo
ming
storms
will
calm
as
the
fog
rolls
wer's
mist
I'll
take
con
trol
of
this
bea
ting
wi
thin
boku
We'll
be
one
with
the
wind
Let's
reach
the
clouds
yond
ring
end
less
ly
in
the
dawn
Episode 21: The World of Magic
Balgland.
The young ones are too hot-blooded, aren't they?
This "special privilege" is nonsense.
Say, why do you think that?
Do you even need to ask?
Magic is most enjoyable when you're pursuing it.
It's that simple.
I see.
Time sure flows quickly.
The apprentice I took on a whim
has already brought along her own apprentice.
This is Frieren.
An elf, huh?
You're strong.
I like you.
Tell me what magic you desire most.
I will grant you a single spell.
What magic I desire?
I know almost all grimoires
written throughout history.
Mages spend their whole lives pursuing the magic they desire.
Tell me yours.
I will grant it to you.
I don't need it.
Magic is most enjoyable when you're pursuing it.
Flamme. This girl is no good after all.
She lacks ambition. Burning ambition.
Master.
This girl will defeat the demon king one day.
I believe she's the kind of mage
who will lead us to an age of peace.
You mean to say I cannot?
You long for combat.
You will not be able to defeat the demon king.
It's not possible for you or me.
Think about it, master.
You can't imagine yourself
living in an age of peace, can you?
Frieren is a mage fit for an era of peace.
I like it.
That's how a mage should be.
Damn it.
I can't freeze him at all.
He has too much of a mana advantage.
Nephtia.
Too weak.
Kanne, defend!
I know!
So, you ended up making quite the scene.
I do believe I know most of your tricks.
Ice magic lacking in force,
and a mage that can't fight without water.
What am I even doing here?
At this rate, I really am just babysitting kids.
You sure like laying it on.
With all this flashy magic, is your mana going to last?
You're graduates from a magic school, aren't you?
Are the elders there still teaching
attrition tactics focused on defensive magic?
What do you mean?
Let me give you a lecture on magic history.
Modern defensive magic was developed
as a countermeasure to Solltrag.
As such, it's very resistant to magic itself,
but doesn't help in defending
against physical threats.
There is, of course, a clear reason for this.
It's because it was enough to defend against
the physical attacks of monsters and warriors.
Defensive magic mustn't be over-engineered.
If you seek perfection, the structure will be too complex,
and have critical repercussions on casting time.
The history of magic is one of offense and defense.
That's why modern offensive magic
has come to favor physical attacks.
Do you understand what I'm trying to say?
Kanne, no! Dodge!
My magic uses an overwhelming
amount of physical matter to attack.
Take a nap or something.
Give me a break.
I don't enjoy hurting people.
Or what? Do you want me to kill you, after all?
You sure you wanna be getting this close?
People are 60% water, you know?
What about it?
Magic is all about imagination.
Can you imagine how water
is distributed through a person's body?
Can you imagine isolating and manipulating it?
How are you going to do that against
a mage protected by large amounts of mana?
If you can't imagine it, you can't realize it with magic.
Besides, even if there was water here,
a little girl like you wouldn't be a threat.
Bluffs don't work either, huh?
What an obnoxious adult.
I did notice one thing, though.
You're telling a lie, aren't you, bastard?
If you really liked fighting enough to lecture us about it,
you would have crushed us down by the water.
What are you so afraid of?
Settle down.
My job is to put you to bed.
As long as Denken doesn't lose, that is.
At this rate, I'll run out of mana,
and that'll be the end of it.
This is a little much for my age.
Sorry, but I'm going to end this early, Frieren.
Waldgose.
Daosdolg.
That geezer... What a way to fight.
That old man sure is flashy.
Is the barrier going to be okay?
Stupid question.
The barrier was put here by the Great Mage Serie.
It won't be destroyed by any amount of brute force.
I see. If you say so.
By the way, since sometime last night,
someone has been analyzing the barrier.
To what end?
No idea.
It's a futile effort anyway.
Do you think there's a mage
who can surpass Serie in this world?
Katastravia.
You're kidding me, a counterattack?
Those were ceaseless arrows of light!
There was no opening for—
I'm out of mana.
This is it, huh?
I can't believe it.
She never used anything but basic combat magic.
It’s like this was just practical training for a pupil.
I'm surprised.
After how far I've come,
I didn't think I still had this far to go.
Tell me where Laufen is.
You must know.
You will be returning the Stille.
If you were in my position, would you give it away?
I suppose not.
Laufen, you're hiding nearby, aren't you?
Bring the Stille here.
If you don't, I'll kill Denken.
Don't do it, Laufen. She won't kill me.
You get that, right?
Gramps got beaten.
I can't—
No, not even Richter could win against her.
But she's let her guard down.
She's not touching Gramps's body.
Don't use Silwehr. Keep hiding.
She'll detect you from the slightest amount of mana.
At this distance, I can grab Gramps and get away.
Stop, it's a trap.
No getting around it.
I didn't really want to do this...
Found you.
Fool.
Damn greenhorn.
It was clear she wasn't going to kill me.
But she would've beaten you
within an inch of your life.
Even so, we would've won.
Gramps, why would you
go so far to become a first-rank mage?
Don't you already have wealth,
authority, and anything else you might want?
I'm from deep in the Northern Plateau.
Only first-rank mages can go there now
due to the rampaging of the demons.
It's been a while, and I wanted to visit a grave there.
That's it.
Shouldn't you go check on those kids?
Though it may already be too late.
Richter will kill them before facing you.
He's the kind of person who can
make a pragmatic decision like that.
They'll be fine. Kanne and Lawine will win.
I just finished analyzing the barrier.
I didn't think Denken would lose.
Well then,
I'm done babysitting you.
Looks like he's seriously trying to kill us now.
We really won't last a minute at this rate.
Barrier? Analyzing?
What do you mean?
Frieren, you can't mean...
Genau.
Don't worry, it's impossible.
Hell would sooner freeze over.
It's going to break.
Sense, who is that elven mage?
The examinee list says her name is Frieren.
The same name as the mage of the heroes' party.
She apparently also has the mark of the holy staff.
The last Great Mage...
You've done it now, Frieren.
Quite the greeting after
a thousand years, don't you think?
This is why I can't give up magic.
In the world of magic,
hell does sometimes freeze over.
To think you'd actually destroy the barrier.
Why break it?
I felt bad for Kanne.
Magic should be free.
The mage who manipulates water?
Magic is all about imagination.
Can you imagine winning against
a mage who manipulates water in the rain?
I can't, at least.
That Richter guy probably can't, either.
The barrier...
What happened?
It's raining.
Never mind, I can check that later.
I need to hurry and finish—
You finally showed an opening.
Your mana control slipped in your rush.
You think that'll buy you enough time to—
I get it now.
I get why you're afraid of
the Spell That Manipulates Water.
This is exactly the kind of overwhelming amount
of physical matter you were talking about.
Lawine, don't let him get away.
Riemstrohr.
It's not like I even have anywhere to run.
This is why I hate water.
Looks like you won.
Let's get out of here.
There's still two hours until sunset.
You can hide your mana that long, right?
There's nothing to hide, I'm out of mana.
I see. You did well.
Don't pat me.
Sorry.
You can't win every time.
Denken and I are both out of mana.
There's two hours left.
It's over.
Laufen, can you break these restraints?
You've got to be kidding. These restraints
have an incredible amount of mana in them.
Then the tree. Knock it over.
Denken, we're done for.
I don't have enough mana left to use Silwehr either.
Richter, Laufen, what do you think
an Imperial Mage would do in this situation?
Struggle until the last moment, no matter what.
We're going to search for other
traces of battle and follow them.
You know, Fern,
you're really boring.
You're really only using basic magic.
Tell that to Lady Frieren.
Oh yeah, that elf is your master, isn't she?
We got drenched because of her.
Make sure to tell her off for that.
I fully intend to.
Oh, I'm not restricted
regarding non-combat magic, though.
Oh yeah, you did use the Spell That Catches Birds.
What other spells can you use?
Let's see.
The Spell That Lets You See Through Clothes.
I'm not going to use it.
Hey, sorry to intrude on this fun chat,
but shouldn't you avoid
giving away your hand like this?
We'll be enemies in the second-stage exam.
I guess.
Sorry about that.
I feel like you could've opened up
a bit more though, four-eyes.
Found them.
Their team already lost.
The corpse of their teammate is nearby.
They have no way to pass anymore,
but they're still cradling the Stille.
Are we going to negotiate with them, Denken?
I doubt they're willing.
If I was in their shoes,
I would accept no amount of money.
Why not?
Because it would rub me the wrong way.
It's not a matter of logic.
Laufen, you wait here.
Grab the Stille if you get a chance.
Richter, come with me.
What's your plan?
We're approaching them head-on?
I don't have any mana left, you know?
You should understand.
The same goes for them.
Prepare yourself.
You're a man, aren't you?
Hey, you're kidding, right?
It's time to throw down!
It's time.
The first-stage exam is hereby concluded.
A total of six teams,
or eighteen examinees, have passed.
The second-stage exam is in three days.
We will notify you of the details in the coming days.
That is all.
You're dismissed.
It's already been two days
since they started the exam.
Fern can't scold me for staying up late.
It's almost scary how great this is.
You must have it rough, kid.
And
I'm
al
right
I'll
be
al
right
Yeah,
I
hear
you
I
care
a
bout
ling
the
wind
u
pon
my
hair
and
loo
king
back
a
gain
have
come
days
that
you
spent
with
Each
mo
ment
had
pur
pose
and
you
knew
it
all
those
years
with
all
the
pain
that
it
might
bring
thank
ful
for
all
I've
been
through
These
fee
lings
are
my
proof
I'm
live
I'll
ne
ver
beg
or
pray
That
gain
nee
kyou
da
ke
wa
So
just
dashi
think
back
on
you,
my
friend
found
you
gain
Some
where
long
the
win
ding
road
woul
dn't
he
si
tate
stay
by
your
side
'til
the
end
A
ny
time,
a
where
place
that
I
go
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'll
al
ways
have
your
smi
le
A
ny
time,
a
where
itsu
mo
When
I
close
my
eyes,
see
you
ze
ttai
nan
te
naku
mo
There's
so
much
we'll
ne
ver
know
A
ny
time,
a
where
when
you're
al
ways
here
wi
thin
my
heart
A
ny
time,
a
where
know
my
tears
are
bound
ning
sky
is
sure
glow
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'm
whis
come
back
home
I'm not sharing.
Rest assured,
Don't talk about that.
Lady Frieren.
You're even more spoiled than me.
What a luxury,
You gotta eat
your vegetables.
and it's not even my birthday...
What a pain...
We're not a team anymore.
Episode 22
We'll Be Enemies Next Time