We're still lacking quite a lot of information.
We should consider what to do
if the replica doesn't have free will.
Though I guess it'll turn into
a pure contest of power, then.
Could you beat it?
Dunno, not sure.
Um, in that case,
I might be able to kill Lady Frieren.
Is that so?
Yes.
Alright,
let's make a plan.
You're
breeze
blow
ing
through
When
you
close
your
eyes,
sun
light
starts
fade
tell
what
you
might
be
thin
king
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
Once
your
eyes
once
a
gain
are
o
pen
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
zing
out
head,
clear
as
orbs
of
glass
Some
where
deep
wi
thin,
I
can
sense
the
clouds
clea
ring
blue
reign
and
ba
nish
gray
Buds
are
bloo
ming
storms
will
calm
as
the
fog
rolls
wer's
mist
I'll
take
con
trol
of
this
bea
ting
wi
thin
boku
We'll
be
one
with
the
wind
Let's
reach
the
clouds
yond
ring
end
less
ly
in
the
dawn
Episode 25: Fatal Gap
So, to confirm,
if the replica does have free will,
we'll use Edel's mind control magic
to break my mental defenses,
and Fern will make the kill, yeah?
Yes.
That's it?
Sir Dunst.
What about Lady Edel?
She was pierced by Lady Sense's
replica and dropped out.
I see.
Sir Blei, as well?
I managed to get away because he bought me time.
I only hope he managed to escape safely.
Leave me! Go!
But...
It's better than none of us making it.
I have information.
Could we cooperate?
That was my intention from the beginning.
Is there anyone who can treat him?
I have a copy of the holy scriptures.
I can cast a simple healing spell.
Please do.
I see.
So the replicas have no free will?
Yes. According to Lady Edel's investigation,
they are thoroughly imitating a person's free will,
but do not actually possess it themselves.
Well, there goes the last
easy way of defeating them.
We'll need to make a plan on that basis.
That said, Frieren, there are still
too many uncertainties.
The biggest problem is that we don't know
how those replicas work, or what's creating them.
We can't act without knowing their nature.
Especially since we don't know if they have
the same weaknesses replicas usually do.
If that replica really is just as strong
as Frieren, there may very well be casualties.
I'm not telling you.
Didn't think so.
They don't have any weaknesses.
A monster from the age of myth called
the Spiegel is controlling the replicas.
Lawine.
How do you know that?
My oldest brother was part of
the Continental Magic Association's advance team
for their attempt at conquering
the Ruined King's Tomb.
So you had information.
No wonder you made it this far.
Not very rational if you ask me, though.
You should have shared that information
and cooperated with us from the start.
We couldn't really cooperate in that atmosphere.
And before we knew it,
Frieren had already gone ahead.
Besides, you're the kind to ruthlessly abandon
others if there aren't any rules, aren't you, old man?
There was no way we could just cooperate.
She really hates you, doesn't she?
I am indeed an old man,
but it's not easy having it said to your face, eh?
Maybe you should apologize?
My bad, pops.
According to the advance team's observations,
Spiegel is behind that door, inside the treasure room.
Apparently its real body is
a weak monster with no offensive capabilities.
If you defeat it, the replicas will disappear.
That matches what we've
figured out with mana detection.
The monster is behind the door.
But a powerful seal has been cast on it.
I've confirmed that as well.
It's the work of my replica.
It's the Spell That Guards
a Treasure Room Door With One's Life.
It's a top-grade folk sealing spell.
That door won't open unless the caster dies.
There's also the option of bypassing
the door and breaking through the wall,
but I bet that's been accounted for already.
Regardless, that means we need to beat
that replica in order to defeat Spiegel.
We'd better hurry if we want to defeat it.
What do you mean?
Spiegel creates replicas
of everyone inside the dungeon.
Those replicas have a habit
of gravitating toward the core.
Besides my brother's unit, the previous
advance team was almost entirely wiped out.
Right here, just before the dungeon's core.
I see.
Excuse me...
The replicas are thoroughly
imitating people's free will, right?
So weaknesses based on behavioral patterns
should be the same as the original, right?
In all likelihood.
In that case, we might still have a chance.
What would that weakness be?
Lady Frieren, could you stand by the wall over there?
Sure.
This is...
Unbelievable...
Of all the things...
You've noticed.
Did you get anything?
Nope.
This is indeed a fatal gap in Frieren's defenses.
How did I miss this while fighting her?
No, knowing that she's a master
is precisely what prevented me from noticing.
The moment she uses a spell,
her mana detection cuts out for just an instant.
Isn't that a mistake apprentice mages often make?
Yeah, I've always had trouble with that.
If you were aware of it, why didn't you tell us?
I mean, it's embarrassing.
Is now the time to be saying that?
That said, she's superior in all other aspects.
There are not going to be many
mages who can make use of that gap.
Regardless, let's discuss our strategy.
Assuming we manage to deal with Frieren's replica...
Lady Frieren, you look like you're having fun.
Yeah.
Alright, here's the plan.
So, Eisen, you'll lure it in and attack it from the side.
Frieren will provide covering fire.
What about Heiter?
He's got a hangover, so he's out for today.
He's stone dead.
I was just thinking how we'd often have discussions
like this when trying to beat a dungeon boss.
Alright.
Let's conquer this dungeon.
Can you win?
Don't worry, no dungeon is unconquerable.
I'm the mage of the party that conquered
more dungeons than any other.
Are you sure you'll be fine with just
the two of you fighting against Frieren's replica?
It'll be easier to predict its actions with fewer people.
We'd almost certainly win if everyone fought,
but I think the majority of us would die.
There probably wouldn't be a chance
to use the escape golems, either.
So, holding back the replicas heading
towards the core is more important?
If we're attacked from behind, it'll be the end of us.
Okay. As planned, then.
Yes, I wish you luck.
Alright, open the door.
Now, then.
Everyone state their worst matchup among us.
Zudrazirm.
It's exactly the behavior Lady Frieren predicted.
Vulsanbel.
My mana detection cut out.
I'm going to be wary of Fern,
who used that chance to hide.
But since I'm fighting
an opponent just as strong as I,
I don't have the luxury of searching for her.
I mean,
I know best just how scary I can be.
It'll be fine.
When you've completely hidden yourself,
even I can't find you that easily.
Is Solltrag really the right spell
to use for the attack, though?
It has the shortest casting time.
What's more, since Solltrag
is a relatively new spell for elves,
it hasn't been long enough for us to be
able to defend against it with pure instinct.
Processing it will take just a moment,
an almost insignificant amount of time,
but it'll delay my defense.
But you're different.
For you, Solltrag is a normal spell
that's been around since before you were born,
and it's been carved into you
as a fundamental of being a mage.
Your Solltrag can kill me.
Put as much mana into it as you can.
Frieren, you hate me, don't you?
Why did you come here?
To be honest, I thought I'd never meet you again.
I came to deliver Master's will.
It's been fifty years.
I see.
So, Flamme has died.
Aren't you sad?
I raised her on a whim.
It's like a report.
What did she write?
The emperor has permitted
the research of magic throughout the country.
In human culture, magic was
treated as a demonic art until now,
and open research was a taboo.
Flamme is the one who advocated for the change,
and she was involved in the education
of these so-called imperial mages.
It says she wants me to continue her work.
What an extravagant will.
Legalizing magic is already
a remarkable feat on its own,
yet she asks for even more?
Is it that impressive?
It means the Unified Empire,
the largest on the continent,
will begin researching magic
and exploring its military applications.
The surrounding countries won't stay quiet, either.
In mere decades, magic will
have spread across the continent.
It's the arrival of an age
where anyone can use magic.
This means, in the near future,
humanity will gain the power
to resist the demon king's army.
I see, that's amazing.
Very much so.
It really is.
However, it's not what I want.
Leave, Frieren.
I will not follow such a will.
It's truly unpleasant.
An age where anyone can use magic?
Magic should be special.
I intend to only teach those with talent.
To think she would leave me a will like this...
I guess Flamme and I
never came to an understanding.
In the end, she was just
an apprentice I took on a whim.
Master said you would probably
get angry and rip up her will.
She said she wanted to tell you anyway.
She said her dream came true.
Doesn't make sense, does it?
Well, I'm gonna go.
I don't think we'll meet again.
Frieren.
You want to take a walk with me first?
We have all the time in the world.
An age where anyone could
use magic was Flamme's dream.
I'm sure she didn't care
about all this in the beginning.
It wasn't for humanity's sake,
or because she wanted power
to resist the demon king's army.
Do you know what her favorite spell was?
The Spell That Creates a Field of Flowers.
A stupid spell that's entirely useless.
She really loved magic.
She seriously wished
that anyone could use such a spell.
It made my skin crawl.
It's like the childish dream of an innocent girl.
But that's what she was.
It's a fantasy she told me when
she was a little girl, much smaller than me.
I honestly thought such an age was a long time away,
and not something she herself could make a reality.
In what to me was a short, ephemeral life,
she climbed her way to becoming
the founder of human magic.
Master always made decisions very quickly,
like she was being hurried on by something.
Humans have limited time.
The steady march of death is never too far behind.
There are many times in life
when one must make an important decision,
but they can't put those decisions off.
We can drag our feet
for a hundred, two hundred years.
Even if we procrastinate for
a thousand years, it's no problem at all.
Our time is nigh eternal, after all.
Frieren, humans have been slowly progressing
ever since they first established a civilization.
But from here on out,
their progress will only accelerate.
A thousand years.
In a mere thousand years,
the age of humans will come.
Humans will surpass us.
Don't neglect your training, Frieren.
If something is to kill you,
it'll either be the demon king...
or a human mage.
Exciting, isn't it, Serie?
A new age, full of mages and countless
spells, is just around the corner.
And
I'm
al
right
I'll
be
al
right
Yeah,
I
hear
you
I
care
a
bout
ling
the
wind
u
pon
my
hair
and
loo
king
back
a
gain
have
come
days
that
you
spent
with
Each
mo
ment
had
pur
pose
and
you
knew
it
all
those
years
with
all
the
pain
that
it
might
bring
thank
ful
for
all
I've
been
through
These
fee
lings
are
my
proof
I'm
live
I'll
ne
ver
beg
or
pray
That
gain
nee
kyou
da
ke
wa
So
just
dashi
think
back
on
you,
my
friend
found
you
gain
Some
where
long
the
win
ding
road
woul
dn't
he
si
tate
stay
by
your
side
'til
the
end
A
ny
time,
a
where
place
that
I
go
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'll
al
ways
have
your
smi
le
A
ny
time,
a
where
itsu
mo
When
I
close
my
eyes,
see
you
ze
ttai
nan
te
naku
mo
There's
so
much
we'll
ne
ver
know
A
ny
time,
a
where
when
you're
al
ways
here
wi
thin
my
heart
A
ny
time,
a
where
know
my
tears
are
bound
ning
sky
is
sure
glow
A
ny
time,
a
where
I'm
whis
come
back
home
Alright,
If worst
let's end this.
comes to worst,
we might both die.
Incredible...
I'll leave it to you.
That gap wasn't
good enough, either.
Lady Frieren...
Within expectations.
That leaves me
no choice.
Episode 26
Pinnacle of Magic
So this is the pinnacle of magic.