It's
a
sto
ry
that's
like
fai
tale
jour
ney
vast
in
scale
tion
of
a
lon
ger
path
part
most
e
ver
know
Long
a
go
lived
an
e
vil
fear
some
king
Sprea
ding
ter
ror
and
dark
ness
far
wide
struck
him
down
flee
ting
chap
ter
I
can
still
re
call
AN AGELESS ELEGY
P3cmCn8aUpUoDQ
!wkQ'e9nQu64r
AN AGELESS ELEGY
tain
falls
u
pon
this
play
found
e
ter
nal
peace
ches
far
and
wide
cross
a
land
march
of
time
goes
on
a
heart
less
beat
There
will
come
a
day
when
all's
life
you
lived
Will
crum
ble,
fade,
there
are
things
that
can
live
Like
your
words
and
dreams
'til
I'll
car
ry
them
a
long
in
side
were
just
velers
who
met
on
the
road
side
still
to
this
day,
I
find
strug
gle
un
der
stand
grief
I
feel
wi
thin
per
sists
and
grows
e
ver
stron
late
to
ask
you
the
ques
tions
trace
the
steps
we
wal
ked
all
those
years
find
there
is
n't
you
I'm
sure
at
least
I'll
find
a
clue
Right
at
the
end
em
barks
a
new
sto
ry
Lear
ning
of
peo
ple
on
this
jour
days
will
go
on
for
e
ver,
ver
as
we
march
Episode 15: The Smell of Trouble
29 years after the death
of Himmel the Hero
Northern Lands,
Laub Hills
How long have you guys been traveling?
Uh...
It's been around four years since
I started traveling with Lady Frieren.
About a year for me.
I see.
You know, this party is missing something.
What do you think it is?
We have a vanguard, some mages, and a priest.
Perhaps a thief?
Since Lady Frieren always falls for mimics.
Geez.
Treasure chests hold limitless potential.
No.
We're missing something more important.
We're missing a milf!
Normally there's at least one in a party!
A sexy and mature older woman!
Is there, now?
We have Frieren, don't we?
She's not a milf, though...
He looks incredibly pained.
Well, sorry about that.
L-Look, we're almost at the next village!
They're still breathing.
Yeah, same here.
What happened?
They're all asleep.
This smells of trouble.
We should move on to the next village.
Don't make me angry, Lady Frieren.
Just kidding.
It's a curse.
I knew it. What a pain.
Hey, Frieren, what's a curse?
Among the spells used by monsters and demons,
some do things like putting
people to sleep, or turning them to stone.
Of those, ones that humanity
doesn't yet understand are called curses.
Humanity's mastery of magic is
insufficient to comprehend or dispel them.
So, it's already over for this village?
That only applies to humanity's magic.
It's another story for the goddess's magic wielded by priests.
Dealing with curses has
long been the domain of priests.
How's it look, Sein?
Think you can fix 'em up?
Don't rush me.
I'm trying to figure out
the type and source of the curse.
How is the goddess's magic
different from other magic?
Her magic is written in the holy scriptures,
and can only be used by those who possess them.
Much like with demons' magic,
we don't understand most of it.
That's why the scriptures aren't very interesting.
Besides, it's hard to use if you
don't have the innate capacity for it.
That capacity also makes curses less effective.
I think it's called the goddess's blessing?
It's why priests are generally resistant to curses.
So even you can't defend against curses very well?
Mages can't really detect curses, no.
It does vaguely feel like I'm being attacked,
so this village is probably
still under the effect of the curse.
It feels prickly.
You mean we're actively being cursed?!
That's terrifying!
It looks to be a pretty unusual curse.
You can't dispel it?
I'd need to perform a ritual,
and I'd need tools to do it.
It'll be faster to stop this curse at the source.
It's being cast by a monster.
I've determined where it's located, too.
Let's go.
Nice and straightforward.
Lady Frieren.
Sir Stark, he...
He's asleep.
Could you wake him temporarily?
With my current abilities,
not for more than five seconds.
That's practically nothing.
Looks like we should really hurry.
Fern won't wake up.
I told her we'd only be taking a short break.
The sleep got to Fern too, huh?
This is starting to get quite dangerous.
I put up a barrier.
Let's stash these two here.
We're almost there. It's close by.
Okay.
Alright, Sein, wake me up when you find it.
Don't fight it by yourself.
I'll defeat it, no matter what.
You know, I told you five seconds is the—
Frieren?
What good is five seconds gonna do?
Oh well.
I do know some combat-oriented magic as well.
It's a subspecies of chaos bloom.
The sleeping villagers are fertilizer for it, huh?
They'll steadily have their
mana drained until they die.
Chaos blooms mix with local
vegetation and develop into subspecies.
It's like a mirror.
But no matter how its form changes,
its core is always its weak point.
Three Lances of the Goddess!
What happened?
Did it deflect my magic?
If I don't precisely hit the core,
its leaves could deflect my magic in any direction.
In the worst case, it could hit Frieren...
Shit. This isn't going anywhere.
Should I wake Frieren?
She's the mage of the heroes' party, though.
If her magic gets deflected...
Never mind the forest,
the whole village could be leveled.
We've only got five seconds.
That's not enough time to explain.
We haven't had enough time to build
the trust needed to convey the issue fast enough.
I don't even understand what she's thinking.
That's right.
You don't know what other people are thinking.
I believe that adventurers don't need
to understand or trust each other.
My old companion, Frieren,
was especially clumsy in that regard.
That's why I decided to trust her words.
She said she would defeat
the demon king, no matter what.
And I believed what she said.
Believe what she said, huh?
Don't fight it by yourself.
I'll defeat it, no matter what.
What a sloppy face that was.
Don't blame me for whatever happens!
Ward of Awakening!
Frieren, only the core—
Okay, got it.
What the hell happened?
Thank you very much.
We won't forget this.
No, we didn't do that much.
No, you've awoken us for
a morning we'll never forget.
It just hit me when I woke up.
"Oh, this is one of those magic-reflecting ones."
You really are an incredible mage, huh?
We only made it out of this alive
because of you, though.
Thanks.
I'm proud of you.
The woman in that village sure was pretty.
He's still on about this.
So that's Vorig.
29 years after the death
of Himmel the Hero
Northern Lands,
The Fortress City of Vorig
29 years after the death
of Himmel the Hero
Northern Lands,
The Fortress City of Vorig
It's the halfway point on our way
to the city of magic, Äußerst.
We've only just reached halfway.
It really is a long journey, isn't it?
Anyway, let's go resupply in Vorig, and...
Um, Lady Frieren. This is awkward, but our funds...
Hey, you over there.
What?
That's a noble's carriage.
Huh?
What? What's going on?
Good body. Acceptable looks.
Come to my mansion.
What is going on?!
What is your name?
Stark.
Lord Orden, this is quite troubling.
You know me?
This is the mansion of the Ordens, one of
the Three Great Knights of the Northern Lands, right?
Your grandfather was a pushy person as well.
What nonsense are you speaking?
Regardless, I'm currently talking with Stark.
He's my party's vanguard.
Stark, do I need your mommy's
permission to talk with you?
Please don't fight.
I have a request. I'll pay well.
This is absurd. Let's go, Stark.
Lady Frieren.
What about those copper coins?
They're all the funds we have, apparently.
We may as well hear you out.
Frieren...
Stark, where are you from?
A village of warriors in Klee, in the Central Lands.
I see. My family is originally from that village, too.
This is my eldest son, Wirt.
My heir, and the champion of this city.
He resembles Sir Stark quite a bit, doesn't he?
He’s his spitting image.
If we dressed him up,
no one from outside our house would notice.
Does that have something to do with your request?
There was a major battle
with the demons last month.
Wirt died in that battle.
He died killing the enemy's general.
That it was a chaotic melee was a small mercy.
The only ones who know of his death
are Gabel here and my closest aides.
What do you plan to make Stark do?
The fortress city of Vorig is
the cornerstone of defense for this region.
I can't allow morale to drop
until our army has recovered.
So you want to cover up your son's death until then.
The most influential people in the region
will gather at a ball in three months.
We'll show them there that Wirt is alive and well.
What's the reward?
Ten gold Strahl coins.
That's three meals and a snack every day for a year.
Throw in a grimoire.
You may take one of your choosing from the library.
Wait, this is never going to work.
First of all, what about this scar?
I've already told the people that Wirt is recovering.
It's a battle scar.
Sir Stark, we need the money.
Sadness.
Gabel. Drill proper etiquette into this boy.
Sir Stark, how are your lessons going?
They're hell.
What do you think?
It doesn't suit you.
So mean.
I'm gonna go get some fresh air.
Lord Orden.
I keep telling you, call me Father.
You never know where people may be listening.
Aren't you being too cold?
It's been less than two months
since your son died, right?
I'm only fulfilling his last request.
We had a different double prepared.
Though he didn't resemble Wirt as much as you.
Though indeed, it brings me no joy to do this.
But this is my son's will.
You'll have to bear with it.
You're really bad with words, dude.
Mut, straighten up.
Yes, Father.
That's my second son, Mut.
Even though he's to become my heir,
he's having trouble improving.
In contrast, Stark is a failure.
Your skill with the sword shows in your posture.
I will teach you the Orden sword style.
What's wrong?
It's okay. Take a deep breath.
This is not your hometown.
What do you think of Mut, Lord Orden?
He's not as talented as his brother.
But he's a hard worker.
His training will not betray him.
He will become a stronger knight than me.
I see.
You should tell Mut that.
I always do.
That's why he's struggling
to improve—it goes to his head.
Well, that's a problem.
What?
I'm also taking lessons?
It's a ball, you know.
Did you think it would be acceptable
for a boy of age to go by himself?
Or is Mommy here going to take him?
Good luck.
This past month was hell.
We need the money, right?
I'm sorry.
We put all that work into practicing. Let's dance.
This really doesn't suit you.
Shall we dance, too?
I'm going to eat cake.
I see.
I would have been the one on
the front lines if not for this injury.
Maybe Wirt wouldn't've died.
Sir.
I take it the ball has ended.
This marks the end of my request.
Gabel, give Frieren the payment.
Stark, your ability as a warrior is incredible.
If you'd like to—
I'm not a replacement for your son.
That's true.
I, too, am not a replacement for your father.
But you don't have a place to call home, do you?
The village of warriors in Klee
was wiped out by demons.
I know that much.
I had a fight with my son the last time I saw him.
It was about some trivial thing.
I told him I never wanted to see his face again.
Even though I didn't truly think that.
I thought it was a miracle when I found you.
All the more reason I can't stay here.
I also said some things I didn't truly mean
to my adoptive father.
That's why I gotta bring back
plenty of stories from my journey.
I see.
Which grimoire should I choose?
Lady Frieren, it's already been half a day.
Sir Gabel is quite troubled.
Please hurry up.
Look, he looks like he's dying.
It seems it's going to take quite a while
for their army to recover.
What's up?
Nothing.
At the very least, he'll have a good heir.
Forgotten heroes, huh?
I don't even know their names,
He's senile...
they're forgotten heroes.
He's been alone for a long time,
hasn't he?
Humans
sure grow
fast.
Episode 16
Long-Lived Friend