Chicken Race.
It is a game of speed whereby they
charge at an obstacle at full speed...
and pull back at the last second...
to prove their bravery.
And now, she is chosen as the obstacle
in this extremely dangerous game.
They are coming!
Kazuma,
it's really too late this time.
They are going to knock me down!
Kazuma, is this some
kind of teasing play?
The sensation of almost
being hit is quite addictive!
What is this? Male ostriches in heat
are continuously leaping over me.
Enough, we have audiences!
Shut up!
(KONOSUBA:
God's Blessing on This Wonderful World! 2)
Blessing.
(Episode 8:
Sightseeing in This Pitiful City!)
No need to trouble yourself.
Looks like Darkness will be fine.
It's all because of my Blessing.
Yes. After we are done with this,
I'll exchange the seat with you.
Great.
Lightning.
Blade of wind.
Fireball.
Are they coming again?
That's great!
Mister, are there any cliffs around here?
No, we only have caves for
shelter when it's raining.
Cave? That will do. Bring me there.
Megumin and Aqua,
let's hop into the carriage.
Let's go, Darkness.
You are too heavy to be carried around.
Don't say that I'm too heavy.
Correct yourself. It should be
my Armour that is too heavy.
Just tie me at the back of the
carriage and drag me along.
This is an emergency.
We don't have any other ways.
No need to be modest with me.
We had run out of options.
Please be faster, Mister.
They are closing in!
Darkness, tell me if you
can't take it anymore.
I'll untie you immediately.
Being bound and dragged
behind a carriage...
and all the while chased
by male ostriches.
-Kazuma, this feels good!
-Don't call out my name!
This is a new discovery,
being treated inhumanely like this!
Although I knew that Kazuma was evil,
even this is too much.
No, it's not like that. It's not me.
Darkness is the one who suggested it.
Mister.
At this rate, they are going
to catch up with us.
This is bad. Mister, where is that cave?
-There's still some distance.
-We can't make it!
Bottomless swamp.
Thank you, Wiz.
For an aristocrat to be
in such a sorry state.
No, this can't do.
Don't look at me, Kazuma.
-Don't look at my disheveled state.
-I told you not to call out my name!
Heal...
Hang in there, Darkness.
Kazuma, I can see the cave already.
I am ready to release my magic.
Alright, Mister, stop the carriage
beside the opening of the cave.
-Roger that.
-Aqua.
Back me up with magic
to increase my power.
Roger that.
Powered.
Snipe...
I see it now.
I was just wondering,
where is the natural instinct of
the Charging Ostriches?
Now I can see it clearly.
Mister, hang in there!
Alright.
This play is not bad at all.
This is expected from Kazuma!
-He drags me on for so long...
-Don't call me.
and tosses me towards the
monsters to be fed on.
-Megumin.
-Explosion!
Please enjoy the food.
This is nicely roasted.
Please have a taste.
It was so beautiful.
I've never thought I could meet...
a powerful magician who could
wield Explosion Magic.
And an archpriest that can
easily heal so many injuries.
A courageous crusader who
stood firm and willing...
to sacrifice herself as a decoy to
bait a herd of charging ostriches
You who wielded a high-class
Swamp Magic to buy some time.
And, of course, you, who lured the
enemies into the caves using your wit.
And you rounded them up
with your resourcefulness.
It was too impressive.
It's enough.
It's not like that at all.
It's our fault.
This is just a small token of our
appreciation. Please accept it.
No, really, there's no need for it.
What are you talking about?
You are the ones who defeated
the Charging Ostriches.
It's our duty as adventurers
to contribute to the battle.
You are a great man.
I've never thought that
true adventurers...
like you still exist
in this selfish world.
I couldn't possibly accept this
reward that I didn't deserve.
Konosuba.
Thank you for your support.
It's not easy to repair this.
But from the looks of it,
you are fixing it with ease.
I'm thrilled to be able to see
my amour being repaired...
right in front of my eyes.
I'm glad that the smithing skills
that I've learned for...
product development can be put to use.
Again, encore!
We will pay for it. Please.
She can probably make
a better living through this.
Wake up, Megumin.
Something is wrong.
Megumin, Wiz, wake up!
If you don't, I'll do something
shameful to you.
Can I? I can, right?
You can't, of course.
What are you trying to do?
Don't scare me like that.
I almost did something bad to you.
Seriously, what are you trying to do?
Let's not talk about this first.
Somebody is coming. Everybody, wake up.
Farsight.
There are a lot of them.
But they are moving very slowly.
Handle the things over here.
I'll get Aqua.
It's our chance to make it up to them.
We had brought them ostrich trouble
during the day because of Darkness.
What is happening? Why am I surrounded
by the undead when I wake up?
Sir Kazuma!
Don't tell me that...
You dare to creep up on us
in the middle of the night, undead?
To the lost souls, rest in peace.
Turn undead.
Hang on, Wiz. Somebody, please help...
Amazing. She took care of
the zombies in a split second.
I'm sorry.
It's their bad luck for running into me.
Look, I am going to purify
each and every one of you.
I'm sorry.
Such a beautiful archpriest.
She looks like a Goddess.
She is the companion of that crusader.
I'm terribly sorry.
I'm sorry for the continuous troubles
caused by my companions.
Although a zombie attack is rare,
I'm glad the archpriest is with us.
I'm sorry.
If it wasn't for our Goddess,
those zombies wouldn't even
come here in the first place.
How was it, Kazuma? My Goddess grandeur?
I've proven myself
quite a bit on this trip.
It's high time for you to
offer me some tributes.
You wouldn't be punished for it.
You have saved us again.
This time, you must accept the reward.
I'm sorry, but I won't
accept it no matter what.
Please wrap this up for me.
Alright.
Open the door.
I'm going to settle our
score today, Megumin.
This is just a little gift from me.
Let's enjoy it together.
Anybody home?
Quick, look at that.
We have reached the city
of water and hot springs,
Arcanretia.
Awesome! Elves and dwarfs.
This is like a fantasy.
The scenery is totally
different from Axel's.
And the air is fresh too.
Steamed buns. Anybody wants
to buy a steamed bun?
Those are their local specialties,
Arcan steamed buns.
I heard that they are delicious
and they are quite popular.
Megumin, you sure did your research.
Arcanretia is quite renowned among
adventurers as a healing spot.
The hot springs here bring
extraordinary results.
My father had brought me
to various cities in the past.
But this city is more
beautiful than any of them.
These healing hot springs
should be quite good.
If I'd known earlier,
we would have traveled to
various cities all this while.
My fellow customers,
have a wonderful holiday.
Thank you, Mister.
Jarippa, Jarippa is gone now.
She gave out a strange name again.
Where should we go, everybody?
You can go ahead and ask me
anything about this city.
The base camp of the Axis cult under
my protection is located right here.
The Axis Cult that is full of weirdos?
Their base camp is here?
No wonder she wants
to come here so badly.
Welcome to Arcanretia.
Are you here for a tour? To convert?
For adventures? Or to be baptized?
If you are looking for a job,
please visit the Axis Church.
We have a vacancy right now.
You can earn money by doing missionary
work for Axis Cult in other cities.
If you accept this job,
you will be privileged...
to call yourself a follower
of the Axis Cult.
Please! Join us! Quick!
Such beautiful blue-colored hair.
Is that your natural hair color?
I'm so jealous of you.
Your priest garment that looks exactly
like Goddess Aqua's suits you too.
Let's head to our inn first.
You are right.
We already have a priest
from the Axis Cult with us.
We shall take our leave then.
Goodbye, comrades.
Have a nice day ahead of you.
Konosuba.
Come here.
Over here.
Where am I?
Don't worry, we have reached Arcanretia.
It felt like Sir Beldia is
waving happily to me...
across a crystal clear river.
Thank you, Mr. Kazuma.
You should thank Darkness instead.
As long as you can come back safely.
I hope that Aqua hasn't brought us...
any trouble again.
I'm going to have some fun in the
headquarters of Axis Cult here.
Let them serve this archpriest properly.
I'm worried.
It should be no problem.
Megumin has tagged along too.
Is that so?
I'm fine now.
Why don't you go out and
walk around the city?
Let's go, Kazuma.
I would like to go sightseeing.
Look, Kazuma, a fountain.
You are right.
Such a beautiful statue of their Goddess.
This is fraud.
My apples.
Are you alright?
Thank you.
Thank you for your generous help.
Actually...
can you give me a chance
to thank you properly?
What? Is this some kind of hint?
There's a café run by upfront.
It's managed by the Axis Cult.
Let's have a talk over there.
No need for that.
Please wait for a while.
Actually, I'm a good fortune teller.
To express my gratitude,
please let me read your fortune.
It's alright. I don't need it.
Let go of me.
It's painful.
I've read your fortune. There will be
misfortunes waiting for you.
But you can avoid that
by joining the Axis Cult.
Join us!
That misfortune is standing
in front of me now.
Let go of me.
Darkness, help me.
I'm sorry.
I'm a follower of Eris.
If you wish to convert him,
you need to go through me first.
About that...
The relationship between the Axis Cult
and the Eris Cult is strained.
It's better if you keep
away your insignia.
Don't let it bother you.
Are you excited?
No.
But...
This is really the base camp
for the Axis Cult.
There are not many people here.
We should be fine.
Help.
Those two over there. Help me.
This vicious man, who is
probably an Eris Cult believer...
tried to force himself
on me in a dark alley.
The man over there,
you are not from the Axis Cult, right?
I would have run away
if you were a strong
and handsome Axis cult believer.
Since you are not, I shall do it my way.
If you stand in my way,
I, who is protected by Eris,
the Goddess of Darkness,
will have you subdued in no time.
What's this? In my hand are the
sign-in forms for Axis Cult.
If someone is willing to
sign their names on them,
this evil Eris believer
will definitely run away.
Both of you, please,
don't ignore my peril.
It's alright. You just need
to write your name on it.
Our powerful Goddess,
Aqua will bestow you
with strength and good looks.
That Eris believer will also run away...
when faced with her immense power.
Yes. After you join the cult,
you will be multi-talented.
And you will be loved by the undead.
There will be various kinds
of blessings as well.
Don't say that Eris is a Goddess
of Darkness in front of me.
Are all the believers of
the Axis Cult like this?
Don't tell me that all the believers
of Eris Cult are like her?
-You are excited, right?
-I'm not.
Congratulations!
You are the number one million
person that stepped on this road.
As a commemoration, I would like
to present you with this souvenir.
But the souvenir is actually
sponsored by Axis Cult.
This is just paperwork.
In order to redeem your souvenir,
can you sign here, please?
Oh my gosh!
Long time no see.
It's me. How are you?
I went to the same school as you,
I'm your classmate.
Do you remember me?
After I joined the Axis Cult,
I changed a lot.
I don't think you can recognize me now.
Wait.
Are you two newlyweds? How sweet.
Please accept this detergent.
No need to pay for it. It's my
blessing for you, newlyweds.
This detergent is really powerful.
Because it's blessed
by our Goddess, Aqua.
It can remove any tough stains.
And it's not harmful to the body.
It's true. You can even drink it.
What is wrong with this city?
This is a test for me in this pagan land.
It's so satisfying.
You are really unaffected.
Sorry for the wait.
For the customer of Eris Cult,
our shop has specially
prepared this for you.
Please enjoy.
Kazuma.
Let us all stay in this city.
Definitely no.
Konosuba.
Let's go back to the inn.
Are you alright?
How is it? Let me see.
It's just a scratch.
Thank you, brother and sister.
In this city that is full of
religious nutcases,
at least, this young girl
still blooms like a flower.
There.
How are you, are you still in pain?
I'm fine, thank you.
Kind brother, tell me your name.
Kazuma, Satou Kazuma.
And this fierce-looking
sister is called Darkness.
Don't make such a weird introduction.
Am I fierce looking?
How do you write "Satou Kazuma"?
Can you show me, brother?
Alright, my name is like...
What the hell!
Brother!
(Episode 9:
A Goddess for This Corrupt Hot Springs Town!)