Kill the Devils and the Devil King!
The witch who claims to be Lady Aqua!
Use the straw mat to wrap her up!
Who gave you permission
to dye your hair blue?
Imposter!
The imposter is getting away!
(Episode 10:
God's Blessing on This Wonderful Party!)
The source of the spring is suspicious.
Indeed. If we cleanse it,
the spring will be back to normal.
Cleansing starts from the source.
We found her! There is the imposter!
Since they scold you,
you don't have to save them.
But they are all my beloved worshippers.
I am the archpriest of the Axis Cult.
Take a good look at my Adventurer Card.
Being the archpriest
won't do you any good.
The manager told us on his way in,
he said not to let anyone through.
Manager?
My advent followers of the Axis Cult.
This is a serious matter.
It is the right thing to do.
Let us through and we can save...
I am from the Eris Cult.
What? Please, I beg of you,
let me through!
The spring source in there is in danger.
-I just want to save the town.
-Let's wait and see.
-No is no.
-That's enough, go back.
Hold on, I have a feeling that...
you have a mysterious charm with you.
Your side profile looks like
Red Dragon. That is so cool.
Do you mean I look like a salamander?
Fine, since you won't let me go in there,
I don't care what people
from the Eris Cult will say about me,
I must breach into
the building of Axis Cult.
What are you talking about?
That's right! All the people
from Axis Cult are crazy.
And your blue hair,
you must be the prankster that turned
the hot spring into hot water.
No, I simply cleansed the spring.
That's all.
So it is you!
We can't let someone like you get in.
-Just turn back!
-I knew this would happen.
-Wait!
-Darkness,
this is the rare chance
you have to do something.
My rare chance?
I have always been useful in the team.
Hey, stop pushing me. What are you doing?
Stop this bewilderment now!
Do you have any idea who she is?
She is the daughter of Dustiness.
Dustiness Ford Lalatina!
This is an emergency situation.
Come on, Miss. Show them the crest
you hide in your chest as proof.
Miss, stop resisting. Miss!
Miss, hand it over!
Kazuma, hold her right there.
I am right behind you.
It hurts! Darkness, it hurts!
Wiz, take the crest now!
Now is the chance to take it!
Wiz, come over here now!
Aqua will hold her arm.
-Hurry up!
-Miss!
-Resisting is futile.
-Wiz, quick!
-Wiz, come on!
-Miss!
I am sorry, Miss Darkness! I am sorry.
Stop it, all of you! The power of
the Dustiness must not be abused!
It's real. We apologize for the rudeness.
Konosuba.
What a bothersome woman you are.
Do you want us to see you as a noble
or a friend of ours? Tell us.
Don't call me bothersome!
I am older than you!
That's because I see you as my friend.
Yes. To me, you are not Lalatina
from the noble family.
You are a reliable crusader, Darkness.
Is that so?
Then, I think it's okay.
-She is easy to please.
-Very easy.
-So easy.
-Hello, everyone.
I can see it.
The water is black.
It's poisoned! There is no doubt at all!
Judging by the situation,
the source may have been contaminated.
Let's go now.
Wait, someone is here.
That is...
How can you drink that thing?
Good riddance.
Soap Detergent? Looks like he is
planning to end his life.
That man was troubled by
the people from Axis Cult.
Wait.
Watch out!
You can't just give up
on your life so easily!
Konosuba
Are you here for sightseeing?
The hot spring can treat waist pain
and shoulder sores and relieve fatigue.
It's good against anxiety, jinx
and all kinds of spell buffs.
It received good ratings
all over the land!
So...
This man seems familiar.
That is not possible.
We have never met before.
Mr. Hans? Mr. Hans, is that you?
What are you talking about?
I am the manager of this place.
Mr. Hans, long time no see!
It's me, Wiz the lich!
What are you talking about?
If I remember correctly,
you are a mutant of Deadly Slime, right?
Are you the one that has been
poisoning the spring?
-Slime?
-Deadly Slime?
Mr. Hans, why are you ignoring me?
It's me, Wiz!
-Mr. Hans!
-I don't know anything.
I don't know you at all.
Stop it, stop shaking me!
Did you really forget about me?
Do you remember?
Back in the Devil King's castle...
I have works to do.
I must go back to the town.
Where do you think you are going, Hans?
We won't let you leave so easily, Hans.
Do you really think a lousy
excuse can help you escape, Hans?
Stop resisting and show
your true form, Hans!
Hans!
Curse you, stop with the naming!
Wiz, didn't you say you
want to open a shop?
Stop wandering in this town
and get back to work!
That is so mean! I am working hard too.
But for some reason,
I am getting poorer by the minute.
I spent so much time
doing this with stealth.
Wiz, you said you would help to
reinforce the Devil King's barrier.
So, we have no reason to be enemies.
We shouldn't get involved
in each other's work.
Why do you have to get in my way?
Did I interrupt your work?
I was just greeting a friend
I hadn't seen in a long time.
And you ruined my work here!
Do you know how much I have been through?
You better get ready for this.
What's the matter, Wiz?
Are you trying to go against me?
These people are my friends.
Can't we just talk it through?
Same as always. You turned into
a coward after becoming a lich.
You are the mighty arch-wizard!
You never tried to talk it through...
while you were hunting us!
I couldn't see the surrounding
clearly back then.
Wiz, you know this man?
There is no need for you to fight him.
Stand down.
I am Satou Kazuma.
I have defeated many mighty foes!
Kazuma, I do want to
avoid any conflict, but...
Let's go, my partner.
-Chunchunmaru.
-No.
Very well.
Any who saw my true form have begged
for my mercy and surrendered.
You seem to have some guts in you.
A weakling-like slime
shouldn't be bluffing.
Judging by the name 'Deadly,'
I bet you use poison to attack.
We have Aqua with us
and she can cleanse it.
There is no way we could lose.
I am Hans.
I am the lieutenant of Devil King's army.
I am Hans, the Deadly Python Slime.
What did you say?
A lieutenant from Devil King's army?
The bounty on his head is higher
compared to other lieutenants.
He is very strong. Be careful.
Slimes are easy to kill, right?
Are they easy to kill?
Don't be silly.
Slimes are very powerful foes.
Physical attacks won't work on them.
You are as good as dead
if he got a hold of you.
You will be melted by digestive fluid.
You will be choked to death.
What? This is terrifying!
His venom can poison
the water of the whole town.
We might get killed instantly
if we touch him.
Instant kill?
It's okay, Kazuma.
You have me to help you if you die.
But don't get eaten. I can't
revive you if you are digested.
EMERGENCY MISSION:
Come on, brave adventurers!
DEFEAT THE DEVIL KING'S DEADLY SLIME
Let me have some fun!
I am sorry! I am truly sorry!
Why are you running away?
Are you stupid? Run for your life!
Oh no! He is the strongest enemy
we have ever met!
Slime.
Darkness!
This is about life and death here.
That is...
Kill the Devils and the Devil King!
Let's give up on the spring, shall we?
The people from Axis Cult
are useless anyway.
What did you say?
The Axis Cult from this town
will be burned to the ground!
That sounds nice.
Please, stop being so mean to Aqua.
I've had enough of this!
Is it really okay?
Things might get even worse.
We really don't have other options now.
Look at you.
You are a poisonous slime.
No one liked you, you are too gloomy.
You joined the Devil King's army
because you are an outcast.
-It's time for you to repent!
-What did you say?
Aqua!
Kazuma.
You bunch of worthless vermin
dare to come back here?
I won't have to stay here any longer
if I can finish tainting the spring.
Finally! I can finally bid
this cursed town farewell!
I can relate to that.
Right, what happened to the real manager?
I ate him.
What did you say?
I told you, I ate him.
I am a slime. Devouring is in my nature.
Wiz?
Cursed Crystal Prison!
The condition for me to remain neutral...
is that no life will be harmed.
-Right?
-Wiz, stop the spell.
It's normal if an adventurer
loses his life.
They took the lives of monsters
as a means of livelihood.
You should have the resolve
to be killed too.
As for the knights,
they collect taxes, and in return,
they will protect the people.
Nothing can be helped
if life is traded for rewards.
-However...
-The whole area will be contaminated.
The manager has done
nothing wrong, has he?
Wiz looks so scary.
If my opponent is the renowned lich,
that leaves me with no choice.
I will use my instinct
to consume all of you.
This is...
What a shame,
this is such a gorgeous slime!
If it wasn't venomous,
I would keep it as my pet.
Have you lost your brain?
It's too dangerous, come back here!
What is that? Is it poisoning our water?
Purification!
It's burning me!
Just leave it, we have to go now!
But if I don't save this place,
my beloved followers will...
Look, the girl with blue hair
was telling the truth.
Kill that thing!
Heal!
It's burning me!
Purification!
Keep it up, miss!
Watch out!
Fall back, it's too dangerous out here.
What are you talking about,
you Eris cultist?
You heathen!
I will use my explosion spell
and blow it to kingdom come!
No, the mountain would be contaminated!
Curse it! Wiz, is there any plan
that you can think of?
With my remaining power,
I can't freeze a monster of that size.
But I might be able to if it's smaller.
How dare you taint
our precious hot springs!
Cursed monster!
Even slime can be choosy.
-Kazuma.
-What?
Think of something smart as
you did before.
What do you mean by "something smart"?
Bones.
-It's the manager of the hot spring!
-He ate the old man.
That is unforgivable!
He is yet to be completely digested.
I have no other option now.
Aqua, can you revive me
as long as I am not digested?
Yes, I can.
Wiz, you can freeze it
if it's smaller, right?
Yes, about half of its current size.
Megumin, wait for my command.
You'll have your chance to use magic.
Really? I will do it!
I will just have to protect
everyone from the spilling slime.
Right, I leave that to you.
A lieutenant in the hot spring town?
Seriously, what is wrong with
the game balance in this world?
Purification!
I am your snack, right here!
Berserk...
I am the greatest magician
of the greatest explosion spells.
Megumin be my name, the strike I make...
in the name of my love for my comrades,
will use all its might to raze the world,
brace for the extreme tremor!
Coming to this town
is the worst fate you ever have.
Too bad you met us!
I leave everything to you now!
Pitiful being,
merge with the crimson smoke,
repent in your suffocating screams!
Pierce through, Explosion!
-Let go of me, heathen!
-Fall back!
Miss.
Cursed Crystal Prison!
I am able to stop Hans
before my power runs out.
That is a relief.
Did it work?
I never thought you could
push me back so far.
What?
It's not over yet.
I will devour all of you.
Kill the Devils and the Devil King.
Kill the Devil King!
God Blow!
I was expecting something stronger,
your feeble attack won't kill me.
You worthless archpriest!
Miss!
The code of Axis Cult!
You will make it if you work hard.
You are all capable people.
Failing is not your fault.
Failing is the world's fault.
Just run away from anything
that is unpleasant.
Running away is not a failure.
Running away is our victory!
Any answer after prolonged hesitation
will end in regret.
If you are going to regret it anyway,
just enjoy any happiness you have now!
What is this light?
Do not be concerned about your age.
Not even god can tell if you
are going to smile in the future.
Just enjoy the present!
Kill the Devils and the Devil King!
You tainted the hot springs
of my beloved worshippers.
You deserve endless deaths for this sin!
Repent, repent to your Goddess!
Kill the Devils and the Devil King!
What? Eris's chest is padded!
God Requiem!
The cursed goddess they worship...
is actually you?
The battle is over.
We were thanked for saving the day
in the commotion of tainted springs.
Or so we thought we will.
I worked so hard to cleanse it,
why is everyone so mad at me?
Aqua's God Requiem...
turned all the hot springs
in Arcanretia into hot water.
Hot water!
The attempt to cut off the Axis Cult's
income by the Devil King...
actually ended up in success.
We planned to use Wiz's
teleportation to go home,
but Purification took a toll on her.
She almost disappeared.
Come over here.
So, we had to call for a cart
to bring us home.
In the end, this wasn't
a healing trip at all.
Look, we can see Axel from here.
Did you go to the hot spring?
It must be nice.
Welcome back.
Kazuma, let's have a drink
at the Guild tonight.
Welcome back, you must be tired.
You look fresh.
Well.
No. My mind is playing tricks on me.
Welcome back, everyone.
Megumin, let's have a duel today!
You came here every day
while we were gone.
No! I just came by occasionally.
What a drag.
We haven't fought in a while.
I'll entertain your challenge.
-Really?
-Yes.
-I am back.
-We are back.
Home is the best, after all.
Winter leaves as spring arrives.
I fall asleep here
and wake up at the same place.
Now, my life here
is to bring blessing upon this
unreasonable, weird, cruel...
and wonderful world and you.
Kazuma, the hot water is not coming out!
I am coming!