It's so cold.
Someone, please give me warmth.
What's with the screaming?
Don't you understand?
Darkness went to the governor's mansion.
She hasn't come back the whole night.
She is now...
Megumin?
What's with the cat?
It won't cause you any trouble.
-You want to adopt it?
-Can I?
That hurts.
Why is it so fierce against me?
What's wrong with the cat?
With that black fur and
big-headed attitude,
I sense something sinister here.
What is the name of this monster?
Chomusuke.
-What did you say just now?
-Chomusuke.
What were you arguing about just now?
You sure look calm. Darkness is now...
I heard some rumors
about the governor too.
-But Darkness won't be so easily...
-Kid is so naive!
Don't you understand he is a pervert?
You can take away my body...
But you will never get my heart!
That's what she will say.
What? Darkness is in danger!
What should we do, Kazuma?
It's too late.
Listen, once she returns,
be nice to her like usual.
Okay.
Darkness has been to the adult world,
we can't ask her what happened.
-Darkness!
-Satou Kazuma, are you here?
(KONOSUBA:
God's Blessing on This Wonderful World! 2)
HUNTING QUEST: HUNT THE MONSTERS
THAT LURK NEAR AXEL
No!
(Episode 2)To save me from prison,
(A Friend For This Crimson Demon Girl!)Megumin cast explosion spells...
all over the place.
She woke up the giant toads
that were hibernating.
So, we are here to clean up the mess.
I don't want to be the toad's snack! No!
The toad is agile, as always,
even in this cold weather.
How stubborn is it?
We can't be left out
of the action either.
I must become stronger.
I have to survive...
in this cruel world.
-I'll save you now!
-No.
Save Aqua first.
The weather is cold, but
the inside of the toad is warm.
After exhausting myself
with the explosion spell,
I can only stall it.
I'll leave it to you then.
-Is that really okay?
-Kazuma!
I can't take it anymore! Hurry up!
Our team has Darkness
as our sturdy shield.
However, no one is effective
at ranged attacks.
So, I learned a new skill.
That skill is called Snipe.
Snipe.
Those with higher luck
have higher accuracy.
It suits me perfectly.
Kazuma!
Seriously? Your arrow went through
the charm point on my head!
Aqua!
Skill, my skill.
Is this how you usually operate?
Look, the toads!
Wait, we don't have enough snacks...
No, I mean bait for them!
Aqua, you will be the bait.
No, be the bait yourself!
Don't be stupid, you don't have
the power to defeat the toad.
If we can kill one, then
it will only be two left.
You and Sena will be able to stall them.
I am here to monitor you,
don't drag me into this.
Kazuma, this is the chance
to kill the toad!
You fools!
Excuse me, but I am
slowly being swallowed.
Can you save me from this thing now?
Seriously? I wish Darkness is here now!
This is the end!
Light of Saber!
Honestly, I would rather
not touch the slime.
You should be able to walk now.
I don't know who you are,
but you saved us back there.
No, I wasn't trying to help.
It would be embarrassing
if my rival is eaten by toads.
Rival?
Long time no see, Megumin.
We have to settle the score today.
Who are you?
Isn't it weird that you didn't
even tell us your name?
This must be a scamming plot
Kazuma told me about.
Fine!
This is embarrassing in front
of people I don't know.
I am Yunyun.
I am the arch-wizard that uses
the highest level of magic.
I will soon become the leader
of the Crimson Magic Clan!
Right, she is Yunyun.
Her father is the chief
of the Crimson Magic Clan.
She claims to be my rival.
You clearly remember everything.
I see.
I am her adventure partner, Kazuma.
Nice to meet you, Yunyun.
What? You didn't laugh at
my name after hearing it.
In this wonderful world,
some people have more
than just weird names.
Even their nicknames are strange.
For example, 'Explosion Girl
with Serious Mental Issue.'
Are you talking about me?
Is that what you mean?
That nickname was given
before I even realized it.
Not bad, Megumin.
You found a great partner.
This is how my rival should be.
I'll defeat you and be the champion
of the Crimson Magic Clan.
Come on, Megumin!
Let's have a duel right now!
No, it's so cold out here.
Why? Please, duel me!
-No.
-Come on, just once.
You finished the job today.
But it is possible you are
putting up an act to fool me.
Goodbye.
I'll head to the guild for paperwork
and have them remove the toads.
This can be a pain if I am
the only one left here.
What a drag.
I can't use any magic for today.
Let's fight with the martial art
you are specialized in.
Is that really okay?
But you never paid any attention
during the gym class.
You used petty tricks
once we had a break time.
You always took away my lunch
after you picked a fight with me.
-Hey.
-This was life and death for me too.
For family reasons, her lunch
was my hope of salvation.
Okay, we'll fight with martial arts.
-What? Really?
-Fine.
Come on, show me what you got!
Judging by their physique,
Yunyun has the advantage.
Megumin may act tough, but she is
not good at hand-to-hand combat.
Megumin,
your whole body is
flickering with shines.
Yes, the slime on my body is
the excretion from the toad.
Once you close in, I'll hold onto you
and slam you right to the ground.
What?
You are trying to diminish my spirit
and make me surrender.
Right?
We are friends.
As friends, we have to
carry each other's burden.
-No!
-Slime, slime, slime, slime!
I surrender! Don't come any closer!
I surrender!
I won again today.
Stop it!
You scoundrels!
I'll kill you!
She ran away in tears.
Kazuma, this is the trophy.
Use this to pay the mortgage.
Are you okay with that?
For an extraordinary magician like me,
this thing is completely useless.
Do you want to learn skills
other than explosion spells?
-No.
-I thought so.
What's wrong?
I feel like Megumin is much
prettier than the other girl.
Wait!
Thank you, let me hug you
as a token of my gratitude.
-Don't come any closer.
-Come on, cheer up.
There are others who would spend
money to hug a slimy girl.
The stench of a toad!
I had never experienced such
a terrible hug before.
Chomusuke, how are you?
I am going to take a bath.
What?
Lady first, don't you know that?
I am a man that pursues gender equality.
I won't allow anyone to use
feminism for her own convenience.
You ask the men to do everything
when it's inconvenient for you.
If you want to have
the privilege of being a lady,
you must first become a lady!
Do you take me as a mere kid?
Listen, only three parts of me
haven't gone through puberty.
You are just another kid to me.
Nothing you say can change that.
This man really started stripping.
I won't let you win, never!
Leave now if you understand what I mean.
Is that so? Fine.
You really don't see me as a woman.
Well, we can take a bath together!
Sure, that makes things a lot easier.
Wait, I am not a person that says
Fools, how could you do that
and get away by acting all shy.
Listen, normal logic won't work on me.
For example, if Megumin likes me
while another girl is wooing me,
I will not hesitate to retaliate
if you use an explosion spell on me...
simply because you are jealous.
I am a man that does what must be done!
Bear that in mind!
Doing what must be done
seems inappropriate here.
Forget it.
I said so much to provoke you,
and you're not taking a bath with me?
Coward.
What? Who are you calling a coward here?
-Yes.
-How dare you to say that!
I'll do it! It's just a bath!
Stop covering yourself
with the towel, get in there!
Stop it, pervert!
Can't you act like a girl?
Here it goes!
I thought cats hated water.
It likes to keep itself clean.
Can we really just leave her alone?
She will come again sooner or later.
She said I was her rival.
She will search everywhere for me.
You are the same age as her, right?
I dare you to tell me what's on
your mind while you stare at me.
Puberty goes differently for everyone.
-Stop, you'll cause a heart attack!
-Darker than the darkness...
One or two years from now, my figure
will make Yunyun jealous as well.
Don't stare at me like that!
Why am I taking a bath with Megumin?
You are acting all calm now?
This can be hard to explain
if anyone sees us.
I am back!
Is no one home?
I got the money for selling the toads.
The lock! Did you lock the dressing room?
No.
What should we do now?
Kazuma, Megumin, I am back!
Come on, say something to me!
Are you taking a bath?
Freeze!
Will I perish, or
will my magic hold it off?
This is the decisive moment!
Do not waver, my magical power!
If Aqua finds out about this,
she will tell everyone about
the nasty 'Lolicon Kazuma'!
I don't even have
the strength to stand now.
Megumin, let's have lunch together
after you finish the bath.
And be quick with it, I am all slimy too.
That was a close call.
I was almost mistaken for a Lolicon.
Megumin, excuse me.
I can't move, help me scrub my back.
Taking a bath with me
makes you a Lolicon?
You better explain what that means.
Stop, what do you want?
You will be seen as a maniac!
Wait, Aqua! I am being bullied by a Loli!
Nasty Lolicon.
TODAY'S ACHIEVEMENT:
KILLING 12 GIANT TOAD
The second day after I got
the loathsome nickname,
we went to Wiz's shop to discuss
settling the debt.
I am sorry, can we sell this here?
-This is...
-I am Yunyun.
What a coincidence!
This must be fate's planning.
We actually meet each other here.
We really are rivals.
She's been waiting the whole morning
after I told her you often come here.
What are you talking about, lady boss?
I am just here to buy magical equipment.
Please, I want to buy this.
I see.
You don't have to take a detour.
Just come straight to our house.
I can't go to other's house so suddenly.
You deserve to be alone
for being so whiny.
Really?
Yunyun is a freak.
She thinks her name invites mockery.
She always ate her lunch alone in school.
I purposely used petty moves on her,
but she still came here all
cheered up for a fight.
It's not as bad as you said.
I do have friends.
I heard the keyword. You have a friend?
Yes, I have friends and they are real.
Funifura and Dodonko are both my friends.
Then I bought both of them a meal.
That's enough,
we don't want to hear anything more.
I can only use explosion spells.
I would rather avoid any magical battle.
You can always learn other magic.
I am sure you earned
a lot of skill points.
I did earn a lot.
I spent them all on
upgrading explosion magic...
and high-speed incantations.
Fool, why are you so obsessed
with explosion spells?
Sure, keep her talking.
She is always so stubborn.
Duel, duel, duel. They are schoolmates,
yet she is so bloodthirsty.
Hey!
This can be useful.
The Crystal of Friendship.
If a magician doesn't have
the required skill,
she can't use this item to its fullest.
Can I make new friends
if I use it properly?
Yes.
Okay, let's try it out.
There is no reason for us
to be good friends.
Are you afraid, Megumin?
In other words,
any who can use it correctly
is the better magician.
Megumin, let's duel!
If you say so, I will have to show you...
the power of a true magician!
Let's settle it once and for all today!
Crimson Magic Clan sure is impressive.
Crystal, show me your power!
The crystal's energy is activating.
I have never seen so
many projections at once before.
They are both amazing.
What is this?
She is collecting bread crust.
Wait.
Happy Birthday!
She was all alone?
Stop!
Big Sister, you are awesome!
Not bad, how about this move?
You are amazing!
Big Sister, you are awesome!
Making friends with a demon
is not bad, either.
She worked odd jobs just
to buy her friends a meal?
What is that? They are eating bugs.
What is this thing?
Lady boss, I thought you say
this is the Crystal of Friendship.
This is a value-for-money item
that improves relationships...
by showing each other your darkest past.
Megumin, can we be friends?
Here it goes!
I will put this in Kazuma's bill.
Wait, Megumin is the one who broke it.
Yunyun wanted to use that item.
She should pay the bill.
A duel. A memorable duel.
When are you going to stop sobbing?
But in the end, we can't tell
who the winner is.
Can we make this a draw?
I am fine with that.
I am not a kid who will
grudge against this kind of thing.
Right, we once promised to see
who grew up faster.
Since you said you are not a kid,
we can have a match on that.
When I said I am not a kid,
I meant something else.
That's because...
I am so close to Kazuma that
we even shared the same bath.
-Wait!
-What?
What are you talking about?
This big mouth of yours!
Are you trying to spread rumors with it?
Today...
Today, I have completely lost to her!
Please, come again!
What a bothersome kid.
Speak of yourself.
Another victory today!
(Episode 3:
Peace for the Master of This Labyrinth!)