What the hell!
Ask the person in charge to come out.
I want to teach him a lesson!
How can I help you?
Are you here to convert?
Or to be baptized?
Or do you want me?
You? What do you mean by you?
I'm just kidding. Why are you so serious?
-Nothing wrong with your head, right?
-I feel like I want to hit her.
Our High Priest, Sir Zesta...
is out fooling around in
the name of preaching.
-I mean, he's out...
-What did you say?
spreading the glorious name
of our Goddess Aqua.
Please come back next time.
Did a magician and
an archpriest come by here?
Do you mean the two of them?
By the way, the one that
followed you here...
is being stoned by the children.
What are you doing, you little demons?
Kazuma, even the woman and
children in this city
are quite advanced in all aspects.
Tuck away your Eris insignia.
-Are you doing that on purpose?
-I refuse.
I refuse!
Aqua.
Welcome, stray soul.
Confess your sins to me truthfully.
God will listen.
And God will pardon you for your sins.
(KONOSUBA:
God's Blessing on This Wonderful World! 2)
(Episode 9:
A Goddess for This Corrupt Hot Springs Town!)
Listen, it's me.
What is wrong with this city?
Please control your believers.
I see. You are trying to scam me
by pretending that you know me.
Please repent of your sin.
If you do that, the kind-hearted
Goddess, Aqua, will pardon you.
Why are you feigning this madness?
Now I know. You are enjoying it.
You are happy that you can
try out this decent priest job.
Do you have any other confessions?
If not, please leave this room.
Continue your life with positivity.
Excuse me.
You are the archpriest worshipped
by the people in this city, right?
Give some instruction to your believer
and this can be solved right away.
Let them conduct themselves with dignity.
Looks like you are done.
I shall wait for the next stray soul.
Alright then, please leave.
What did you say?
Are you kicking me out of this room?
Get out! You should get out
after your confession.
That wench.
Actually, I have something to confess.
Tell me about it.
Confess your sins and repent.
Is it because you are interested
in the crusader's laundry?
Or is it because you desire to
smell a magician's black hair?
Or is it because you lust
for the beautiful...
and gracious priest even though
you are of different status?
Actually, I accidentally broke
my companion's party cup,
which is well-cherished and
is used especially for performance.
Besides that,
she was always bragging
about her rare wine.
I just wanted to sneak a try
out of curiosity.
But it was better than expected.
In the end, I finished it.
Then, I filled it back...
with cheap wine.
She can't tell them apart anyway.
What did you say, Kazuma?
What did you say?
That priest can cause
troubles way too easily.
So, before I came here,
I stuck a pamphlet about
an opening for a priest...
in the Eris Cult on the
adventurer guild's notice board.
Traitor.
Come on, I was just joking around.
So you aren't really looking
for a new priest?
Besides the first two,
the last one is fake.
Wait. Did you say besides the first two?
Quick. Let's go home now.
I beg of you. Please, listen to me.
I believe in the Axis Cult and
I've long worshipped Goddess Aqua.
But...
the well-filled-out chest on the
portrait of Goddess Eris...
has clouded my thoughts.
That chest is the devil's chest.
Please pardon me for my sinful
thoughts towards another Goddess.
Rest assured.
God will forgive you.
No matter your preference
for large breasts...
or your preference for small breasts,
Axis Cult teaches forgiveness
in all things.
No matter if you are a lolicon, NEET,
or a fan of girls with animal ears
that are neither human nor animal.
As long as you are not interested
in the undead or devil girls,
as long as you have love
and break no laws,
then everything can be forgiven.
My faithful believer,
I shall teach you a holy incantation
to help you avoid the devil's temptation.
Eris's chest is padded.
Next time, if you are tempted again,
chant these words.
If others are tempted as well,
it will be kind of you
to share this with them.
Eris's chest is padded.
I feel like I've been enlightened!
Let's chant it together again.
Eris's chest is padded.
Thank you for your holy incantation.
As a Goddess, how could you back-stab
another younger Goddess?
The number of believers and the heart
of faith are important to God.
Because they will directly
affect a God's power.
Although I don't have a
large number of believers,
but my believers have strong faith in me.
To protect these adorable believers,
I am willing to do anything.
Konosuba.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Are you well?
I've fully recovered after a bath.
Great.
There are no other people...
in the mixed bath. It feels like
I've booked the whole place.
Does that mean...
Anyway, how did your sightseeing go?
The believers of the Axis Cult
are too terrifying.
As for me,
I would like to go sightseeing
again tomorrow.
You...
Fine, do as you wish.
I am going to take a bath.
I am taking a bath.
We heard that.
Enjoy your bath.
-I am...
-Just go.
The water is nice.
It would be nice if I were you.
I am just here for
the hot spring treatment.
You seem rather exhausted.
This is the realm of the Devils.
You must have been through a lot.
So...
That man over there
has been staring at me.
It makes me feel so awkward
when you are staring at me.
Just ignore me.
Right.
This is a mixed bath, after all.
Just pretend I'm not here.
She is quite a shy lady.
I am just a traveler,
all the people I met kept
asking me to join their cult.
I have had enough of their
nonsensical gibberish!
He must have been through quite a lot.
This city is just...
I better not be so nosy.
How is it, sir?
Yes, right over there.
This soap I use is very foamy.
Yeah, you are right.
It can cure all kinds of sicknesses!
And this soap is even edible!
The ingredients are holy and natural!
-Join us and you will get one for free!
-No!
You will get double the points
for now! It's free!
Stop trying to sugar-coat it with points!
Konosuba.
I want to go back.
I really want to go back.
Megumin, swimming is prohibited here!
It's fine, stop nagging!
-What are you doing?
-Why are you acting so shy now?
Our jobs need us to be open,
we can't afford to be shy.
Your logic is simply twisted.
The towel!
I brought Kazuma along so
he could stop wasting his life at home.
While we are at it, we can kill
the undead that comes after Aqua.
That's why I brought him along.
That's what this is all about?
But what is going on with him?
I always thought he was a stuffy coward.
Yet he cares nothing
about the social gaps.
He would even confront
the nobles head-on.
Is this strange, or is it amazing?
The mixed bath is right next to us.
Which do you think he will choose
if there is a mixed bath
and a man-only bath?
He is cautious. He always
runs away when there is danger.
But with just reasons,
he will choose the mixed bath
without hesitation.
Kazuma, are you there?
I bet you are sticking
your ear to the wall,
imagining the scene of
Darkness taking a bath...
with a face of a total pervert.
Megumin, why did you drag me into this?
Kazuma, are you there?
You are there, aren't you?
It seems like he is not.
I must have wronged him this time.
Let's buy him juice and
pretend nothing happened.
This is a little inadequate.
Either way,
he is reliable.
He may look like a coward,
but when his friends are in need,
he never refuses to offer help.
He is a liar.
But his is undoubtedly good in nature.
I am blushing just by
eavesdropping on them.
By the way, Megumin,
that thing on your bottom is...
Even if it's you,
I won't show any mercy
if you pry on me about it.
Please, stop!
Seriously, these two things
on you are simply outrageous!
Now!
Did he see anything?
-He was there the whole time!
-He was really there!
I can always sense his perverted eyes.
There is no way a man warped by lust
won't go to the mixed bath!
Create Water!
It's so cold!
Don't toss your cat here!
As the punishment for eavesdropping,
you will clean him up!
Having a freak like you as the owner
must have been hard on the cat.
Konosuba.
They are too much!
I was just on a trip to the hot spring.
Aqua, your tears make me
feel a stinging pain.
Just how many troubles
have you caused today?
What is that supposed to mean?
Why must you point the finger at me?
After Aqua went to the secret
hot spring at the headquarters,
the warm water of
the spring became hot water.
And they chased me out!
Why do I have to be chased out
of the cult that worships me?
Why?
By the way, you purified the
tea into hot water.
The most outrageous
of them all is the manager.
I apologize for turning
the hot spring into hot water.
But this is not something
I can help with.
Yes, if anything,
that is because I am
the Goddess of Water.
Behold, I am Aqua herself!
I am a goddess!
This city is full of dangerous dangers.
What is a dangerous danger?
You cried the whole night.
Just like the manager said,
the quality of the hot spring
has gotten worse lately.
The Devil King must have thought
he had no chance against us,
that's why he went after our
income source, the hot spring.
-Is that so, he's good.
-Trust me on this!
But the Axis Cult is shunned
by the people of this town.
Having such an indirect approach
seems unnecessary.
To protect the city,
I must stand out and fight!
So, you will lend me your help, right?
I am busy, I plan to have
a walk around here.
I know how terrifying the Axis Cult is.
I don't want to have
anything to do with them.
Why?
Having a walk or not is
not important at all!
Megumin, don't hate the members
of the cult so much.
What about you, Darkness?
I have to do the...
Please!
Fine, I will go with you!
I will go with you,
don't cleanse my grape juice!
Wiz is always so nice to you,
I am sure she will go with you.
I was crying the whole night,
she was gone this morning.
Let her have some sleep for now.
Come. Come to me.
We should save Wiz now, not the city!
Come, over here!
Now that I see it,
this is a nice and normal place.
Yeah.
The scenery is nice,
and the foods are decent.
The only problem here is the people.
The weather is so good today!
This must be Lady Aqua's blessing!
-Here they go again.
-By the way,
this pot doesn't stick!
Join the cult now and you will get one!
Don't go! Don't be so shy!
Are you going for a stroll?
Take a look at this.
You too, miss.
Everyone can get an extra now!
Excuse me, why won't you
look me in the eyes?
This is all for your own good!
Can we drink the soap?
I don't have that much to wash...
-Liquid soap detergent...
-It's edible.
Liquid soap detergent...
How can you drink that thing?
Good riddance.
Kazuma!
Wiz, you are okay?
Yes, all thanks to you.
Some time ago, I saw my party
member, who are adventurers...
waving at me not to go over the border.
So, I recovered in an instant.
That is just...
What are you doing here?
Actually...
Where is the guy from just now?
There were liquid soap detergents.
There was a man.
-It's that so?
-Kill the Devils and the Devil King!
That voice...
I have a bad feeling about this.
Kill the Devils and the Devil King!
My beloved members of the Axis Cult,
the forces of the Devil King
are conducting sabotage here.
-Sabotage?
-What happened, you may ask.
The hot springs in this city
have been poisoned.
I confirmed it myself.
Many of our hot springs
are being sabotaged.
We confirmed it.
I was in the hot spring earlier,
but nothing happened to me.
That's because I purified the water.
That fool, did she go to
every spring in the city?
But don't celebrate too soon.
I need a favor from all of you.
Before this disaster is over,
do not go to any hot springs.
But Priestess, this is
a city of hot springs.
Do you want us to stop going to the
place that symbolizes the city?
That is simply unimaginable!
Besides, what does the Devil King
want with the springs?
He wants to cut off the financial
resource of the Axis Cult.
Yes, the Devil King fears
the members of the Axis Cult.
This is not about me not
having to enjoy the spring...
and making you suffer
the same bad luck as I had.
-My advent members of the cult...
-There you are!
She is the wicked woman that turned
all the springs into boiling water...
so no one can enjoy them!
-Wait a minute...
-Get her!
Beat her up with the straw mat!
-I knew something was strange.
-You were trying to trick us?
Another scamming plot?
What do you want from us?
We were making so many efforts
to make this world better!
How did things escalate so quickly?
No, I have a reason for this...
-Lady Aqua is going to cry.
-That's not it!
Please, calm down. Hear me out!
Darkness, stop standing there,
say something for me.
Just tell them what I told you.
Say this, "Please, Axis Cult."
Don't be shy, say it now!
Please, Axis Cult.
We can't hear what the blonde girl says.
Poor girl.
Fine, I have to reveal
my true identity now!
The advent members of Axis Cult
that are gathering here,
my name is Aqua.
Yes, I am the person you worship,
Aqua, the Goddess of Water.
I descended to this city
in order to help you.
Stop kidding around!
Did you claim to be Lady Aqua just
because of the blue hair and eyes?
You'll be punished for that!
By using the straw mat!
The straw mat fell into the lake.
If you are the Goddess of Water,
there should be no problem
if you fall into the water.
Liar!
I bet you are here to ruin
the hot springs industry.
You are working for the Devil King!
It's true! I really am
the Goddess of Water!
I am the Goddess of Water!
That was too much!
Why do I have to be stoned
by my own worshipers?
Lady Aqua. Have a drink and calm down.
The energy released from
your agitated cry is affecting me.
I need booze.
You didn't care that much, did you?
We know you are trying very hard.
But claiming to be a
Goddess is too reckless.
But people will get sick if
they use the tainted hot springs.
I see no reason to help them
after what they did to you.
But my beloved worshipers will be...
Kill the Devils and the Devil King!
-Kill the Devils and the Devil King!
-There is a mob.
What? Did they believe
my words and come to me?
There she is!
The witch who claims to be Lady Aqua!
Kill the witch!
(Episode 10:
God's Blessing on This Wonderful Party!)