I've prepared the highest quality
black tea, Mr. Kazuma.
Alright.
This is just hot water.
So careless of me.
Don't tell me that you have
purified the black tea.
I'm sorry, Mr. Kazuma.
You can just make the tea again.
Thank you, Aqua. I'll drink this.
Yes, this is hot water.
This is so disgusting!
(KONOSUBA:
God's Blessing on This Wonderful World! 2)
(Episode 7:
An Invitation for This Knucklehead!)
I apologize for the incident that
happened a few days ago.
So, please turn yourself back
to the previous Kazuma.
The incident that happened
a few days ago?
What do you mean by Excalibur,
the sacred sword?
Do you mean that incident?
As they say, rich people don't argue.
By the way, would you like
to drink some tea, Megumin?
I happened to have some
high-quality tea leaves.
It's my fault.
Please turn yourself back
to the previous Kazuma.
The Kazuma now is very disgusting.
What are you talking about?
I have always been like this.
I've prepared the highest quality
black tea again, Mr. Kazuma.
This is just hot water.
You have purified it again.
What's wrong with me? I'm so careless.
Never mind. You can make it again.
Thank you, Aqua.
I shall drink this then.
Actually...
That Lolita!
I'll skin her when she's back.
I'll definitely do it!
And then, even this competitive
girl will cry piteously...
and beg my forgiveness.
Can you be more specific about the
method that will make Megumin wail?
Why are you making such
a ruckus early in the morning?
Please stay as calm as me, everyone.
Yesterday after I came back,
besides bathing,
I chilled here all day long.
I don't wish to be criticized
by a good-for-nothing.
Darn it! I won't forgive her!
I can already imagine
her wailing face now.
Can you be more specific about
how you will make her wail?
Is she back?
-Can you be more specific?
-Megumin, you wench!
Are you expecting that abnormal girl
from the Crimson Magic Clan?
Pity. It's just me.
Instead of that useless shopkeeper,
you have me, a universally recognized
connoisseur, to negotiate with you.
Rejoice and worship my appearance.
Let me show you the products in our shop.
Excuse me,
how did you come in?
That useless junk?
You call that a barrier?
It is too weak.
I thought it was a failed barrier
cast by a newbie priest.
I'm sorry.
I am too powerful that the barrier just
fell away when I walk through it.
You are so out of shape from head to toe,
super powerful Mr. Demon.
What to do?
I heard that you are the Duke of Hell.
Did you suffer that much
from a mere barrier?
This body is made out of the dirt.
I can never run out of it.
I am quite interested in the thin veil
that covers this house.
It's quite well for a new priest.
For human. Yes, it's quite well
for a new human priest.
Calm down.
-Kazuma.
-Yes.
I heard something about kotatsu.
-Is he here to discuss this?
-Yes.
With this scum that lives on the
disgusted feelings of humans.
-Your expression are over the top.
-This joke is not funny at all.
But you are laughing.
We demons are circumspect
with our agreement.
So you need not worry.
We are different from
the fraudulent group that...
promises happiness with faith alone,
attracts those innocent
people with flattery,
and makes money in the name of donations.
What's their tenet again?
Oh, right.
God is always with you.
But then, what happened?
I saw the so-called God with my own eyes.
The peeping Tom that was
caught a few days ago,
the man that peeped around the
bathhouse and toilet lustfully...
happened to be a God.
Sacred Exorcism.
That's a close call.
A magnificent shedding.
This is it, this is your original form.
What should I do?
How should I get rid of it?
Even if you want to destroy this mask...
Don't try to take off the
mask while I'm still talking.
-Stay calmly.
-My body can't take it anymore.
Calm down. At least wait for me
to finish my sentence.
Konosuba.
We can start the negotiation now.
According to our agreement,
I will pay you 10% of the
benefits that I get after selling.
But how about this?
Are you willing to sell off your
ownership rights for these objects?
I'm willing to offer you
300 million Eris.
300 million?
This is an amount that can support me
for life without needing me to work.
The return interest on a monthly
basis is one million Eris per month.
One million per month?
There's no guarantee that
my products can be sold off.
Isn't it better for me to accept
the 300 million offer?
No. One million per month can help me
avoid currency fluctuation.
Think about it carefully.
I'm worried about my shop,
so I shall take my leave now.
My sacred home will be
contaminated by your stench.
Go out! Quick, go out!
This is just hot water.
What's wrong with me.
They have been continuing on
like this after that incident.
Now I know why they keep up
with the façade of nobility.
But it's good that we have money.
Alright, let's hunt for some monsters.
No, what are you talking about?
We have so much money.
Why do we need to work?
Besides,
I still died despite having
prepared the equipment
and set up the battle plan.
I've made up my mind. From now on,
I'll conduct business instead.
And give up this dangerous
career as an adventurer.
I'm going to live a satisfying life.
It'll be troublesome for me
if you do that, Mr. Kazuma.
It will be difficult for me if we
don't defeat the Devil King's army.
Then we shall earn more money...
and hire more highly skilled adventurers.
Then, they can help me battle
the Devil King's army.
We will lead an army of adventurers
and take down the Devil King's castle.
How about that?
Aren't you feeling hopeful?
That's right. You are really great,
Mr. Kazuma.
You can recklessly order those
adventurers around with lots of money.
When the Devil King is weakened,
you can use the opportunity
to strike the last blow.
That's right.
I don't need to waste my time
fighting long and hard with him.
Use the money to defeat the Devil King?
I won't agree to it.
Who do you think the Devil King is?
The Devil King...
is someone that we need to defeat
at the end of the final battle...
using the ultimate mysterious power
that awakes within us.
But all you want is to hire strong
adventurers to defeat him.
Darkness, talk some sense into them.
Darkness?
No, it's just that Kazuma is getting
more useless by the day.
So I'm curious about what kind
of scum he will turn into.
Gosh, what am I going to do?
Don't lump me together with this pervert.
Come to think of that, I just came
back to life after I snapped my neck.
At least let me rest until
my old wound is healed.
Alright.
Let's heal Kazuma's wound, then.
It's nothing. I just need
to chill for a while.
Let's go to the hot spring
to heal your wound.
Let's go to the city of
water and hot springs.
Arcanretia!
You needn't worry about my wound.
Did you say hot spring?
Are you talking about Arcanretia?
Are you saying that we are going to...
the city of water and
hot springs, Arcanretia?
Hot spring?
We are exhausted after our continuous
battle with strong enemies.
It's nice to relax in the
hot spring once in a while.
Why do you sound so reluctant, Kazuma?
Konosuba.
Are you ready, everyone?
Of course, I'm ready.
Seriously? Every day, the two of them
call us the good-for-nothing.
But how much longer are
they going to sleep?
I'll go wake them up.
Kazuma, head to the
carriage waiting area.
Make sure that we can get the best seats.
Of course. Leave it to me.
Welcome.
What brings you here
so early in the morning?
I'm going to the hot spring.
Another thing. About that deal,
I hope that you can wait
for me until I get back.
Is that so?
Then, go on and relax...
and look forward to the mixed bathing.
Mixed bathing? I wasn't thinking of that.
I just want to heal the old wound
on my neck that still throbs.
Wait, why is Wiz all burnt up?
What?
This is a very valuable object.
You can definitely resell it.
So, Mr. Vanir,
please don't come near me
while you are preparing that...
Murder Ray of yours!
That's the whole story.
I wanted to return these junks,
so I was just packaging them up.
Do you want to buy one?
What kind of magic item is this?
This is a portable toilet for
emergency use during a trip.
This flushable toilet will emit a sound to
provide the users some privacy
when they use it.
That's great!
The downside is the noise it emits
is loud enough to attract monsters.
And the mechanism for generating
water is too powerful...
that it will create a
terrible mess all around.
Does this shop own
any normal magic items?
Our useless owner...
has this unparalleled
talent when it comes to...
purchasing totally useless merchandise.
If I wasn't careful enough,
she would purchase all kinds
of bizarre merchandise.
Back to the previous topic.
You said that you are
going to the hot spring?
Welcome.
Didn't I tell you to get us
some good seats first?
What is it that you are carrying?
Konosuba.
I would like to buy this as a present.
Can you help me wrap it up?
Of course.
Please open the door.
We shall settle our score today, Megumin.
Be prepared for it!
Anybody home?
Do we have to take care of her?
That's fine with me.
But she's becoming more
and more transparent.
Are you alright? Healing Magic.
No, it won't work for the undead.
Traveling?
My father brought me to the
capital city when I was a child.
Aren't you Mr. Kazuma?
This is an emergency.
Among us, your vitality is the strongest.
Kazuma.
We are going to use this carriage.
Based on my good judgment,
this carriage is the comfiest one.
Another thing, I would like
to sit beside the window.
I would like to reserve a seat
with the best scenery view.
Kazuma, go and buy the tickets.
Before the tickets for that
carriage are sold out.
Quick, go and buy the tickets.
Mister, why is that seat occupied?
What is this?
That's a red baby dragon, Miss.
That seat was already paid for.
So one of you will have to...
sit with the luggage although
it's uncomfortable.
If that's the case...
Scissors-paper-stone.
This situation calls for a round
of rock paper scissors.
If that's the case,
I'll sit with the luggage.
No, Wiz. Let's do this fair and square.
Alright, Aqua, rock paper scissors then.
Let's start.
Rock paper scissors.
I won.
Wait, I didn't say that the
winner can walk away.
The five of us have to keep playing
until we have a loser.
How about just you and me?
Three times. If you win even once,
I'll go sit with the luggage.
-Truly?
-Yes.
Do you know how probability works?
It's impossible for you to win
three rounds straight, Kazuma.
I never lose in rock paper scissors.
This is too weird.
You've cheated. Please, again.
Just one more time.
Truly? Will this be the last time?
Do you accept? You have
accepted it, right, Kazuma?
Although I don't know what trick you used,
I have had a trick up
my sleeve since you did it.
Blessing.
This is so despicable. You used
magic to increase your luck.
Luck can be considered a strength too.
So, the magical capability
is a part of luck too.
Bring it on.
Rock paper scissors.
Why?
Even when I was young, I never
lost in rock paper scissors.
You are so despicable.
It doesn't count. It's not fair.
It's cheating. It's a cheating skill.
Are you born with that ability?
If that's the case, the utmost
gracious gift that...
I've bestowed upon you is invalid now.
Send me back. Send me back to heaven.
-You dirty swine!
-You wench!
Are you saying that my ability is in
winning rock paper scissors?
Are you dumb? How can
I use that to fight monsters?
But...
The most detesting thing is
you described yourself as the
utmost gracious gift?
What a joke.
Gracious gift?
I would have done it long ago
if I could give you back
in exchange for a special ability!
You shouldn't have said that, Kazuma!
Stop, don't pull on my face.
We will depart for Arcanretia now.
Even this scenery is new to her...
even though she is the
daughter of an aristocrat.
Chomusuke is cuter.
I've never thought that...
I could travel like this in this world.
It's quite nice.
Mr. Kazuma.
My backside is quite painful.
Someone, please exchange with me.
I'll change to you
when we stop for a break.
For now, you have to endure it.
No way!
Engage my farsight.
What is that?
I'm sorry, but there's a dust cloud
heading toward us.
Do you know what that is?
Well, I can't see it.
The thing that can kick up
a cloud of dust around here...
would be a pack of Lizard Runners.
But I heard that the Queen Runner
was defeated a while ago.
Or it could be a Sand Whale
that kicked up the dust.
The only other thing is the
Charging Ostriches.
-Charging ostriches.
-This is a serious matter, Mister.
They are dangerous monsters.
During the mating season,
in order to woo the females,
the males will court the females
through a race called...
"Chicken Race" to prove their bravery.
They will charge toward
the hardest thing...
and turn away when they almost hit it.
But usually, they will choose
some nearby rocks as targets.
So we should be fine.
Nothing to be worried about, then.
But looks like they are still heading
towards us quite menacingly.
That should be the charging ostriches.
But it's weird that they
are heading toward us.
Is it possible that we have...
really hard minerals in our carriage?
Minerals like adamantite?
Looks like they are heading here.
I should say,
heading towards our carriage.
Something as tough as adamantite?
-Dark...
-Kazuma!
A group of incredibly fast creatures
is charging toward us.
I can feel their heavy gaze.
Such intense looks.
Is that you?
Sir, we are going to stop our carriages.
Our fellow adventurer guards
will protect you and the carriage.
I'm sorry that our crusader is too tough.
Darkness, you are the monsters' target.
They like to charge hard objects.
And their target is your
rock-hard muscles!
Kazuma, I'm still a
young woman, after all.
It's not my rock-hard muscles,
it's my Armour.
My Armour is partly adamantite.
They must be here because of that.
It's true.
So don't look at me like that.
My body is not that hard.
Megumin, Aqua, you are up!
This really isn't our battle,
but we are the ones who
attracted them here.
We need to clean up our own mess.
Let me help too.
Wiz, stay in the carriage
to protect our driver.
Alright.
Sir, you have already paid for it.
Please find somewhere to hide.
I'm sorry, but this is
our companion's fault.
We shall leave this to you,
our fellow adventurers.
-Leave.
-This matter.
-To us.
-Step away.
Megumin, be prepared to release
your explosion magic.
Understood.
That crusader over there.
You are not one of the guards,
please step back!
The monsters are charging
toward that crusader.
She's a decoy.
That crusader is using her Decoy skill...
to become bait.
That crusader...
is not a guard, but she's willing
to take on all those monsters.
I'm sorry, but she
doesn't have that skill.
She won't budge even though she's
facing a large number of monsters.
She's so brave.
I'm sorry, but being brave
is not her reason at all.
She is a customer.
She is not a paid guard.
She can't be exposed to danger.
I'll back her up!
Bind!
What?
Are you worried that the monsters...
will target me instead if I use Bind?
Is that why you sacrificed yourself?
I'm sorry, I just want to help you.
But I've brought trouble to you instead.
Please forgive me.
Forgive me.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive my companion.
Truly, please forgive this pervert
for the trouble that she's caused.
(Episode 8:
Sightseeing in This Pitiful City!)