Satou Kazuma!
After investigating the case of
the monsters that emerged around town,
we realized they came from Keele's
Dungeon, which you visited a few days ago!
Why are you blaming everything on us?
Just to be sure, you all know
nothing about this, right?
I don't know about anything if
it doesn't relate to Explosion Magic.
Me too.
There shouldn't be a problem usually.
What about you?
Of course not!
You're too suspicious of me!
Regarding that dungeon, the monsters
can't go near it, thanks to me.
Thanks to you?
Come here for a bit.
Tell me more.
Actually, I especially made that
magic circle in the lich's room.
It's still perfectly
maintained there now.
It should be keeping away
all the evil things.
What did you say?
Why are you suddenly asking me?
I've told you.
The magic circle that
I seriously drew is still there.
That is why the monsters
can't go near it.
You idiot!
(Episode 5:
Servitude for This Masked Knight!)
It shouldn't be my fault.
You do this every time.
Do you have the 'agony if you don't
sabotage our reward' disease?
Let's not talk about monsters first.
As an adventurer, I can't just
ignore the people in danger.
Please let us help out.
We managed past that at last.
But we must erase that magic circle.
I see. They're unknown monsters indeed.
-Mr. Satou.
-Please call me Satou.
Thank you for your help.
It looks like someone is
summoning the monsters.
So, please defeat the magician,
and stick this in the
summoning magic circle.
This is a powerful Sealing Talisman.
I can't stand those dolls' masks
on a physiological level.
I wonder why. I feel so angry.
Wait. What?
What...
What's the matter?
Is it asking for attention?
Although the mask angers me a lot,
but it looks kind of cute now.
As you all can see,
this type of monster has the habit of
exploding after sticking onto a human.
-Is it?
-How could you all be this calm?
I'll lead and clear the path.
-Kazuma shall stay behind me.
-Alright.
Kazuma.
I'll only be a bother.
I'll just be on standby here.
-Then, me too.
-You must come with!
I've had enough of dungeons!
I'll definitely get abandoned again
if I enter the dungeon!
I don't want to enter the dungeon. No!
Then, it'll be just Darkness and me.
It'll be just Kazuma and me?
Compared to monsters,
I feel that Kazuma is more dangerous.
I can abandon you in the dungeon too.
So that you'll develop
the same trauma as Aqua.
EXPLORATION MISSION OF INVESTIGATING
KEELE'S DUNGEON'S PECULIARITIES.
The interior looks different
compared to before.
It's so bright.
It's like the owner is just inside.
Do the unknown monsters cause this too?
I got them!
Look, Kazuma! They're bumping
themselves against my sword!
You're really happy about it.
But, with these people around,
I can't secretly erase
Aqua's magic circle.
Wait! Slow down!
It sticks itself onto me!
Somebody get it off me!
Don't come here!
Alright, Darkness!
Just move on like this!
Just leave it to me!
This is so exciting!
As a crusader, I feel like this is...
the first time I'm utilizing
my true abilities!
Konosuba!
What's the matter?
He looks like the doll's master,
without a doubt.
Hey!
Are you the culprit?
You actually made it this far.
Welcome to my dungeon, adventurers!
I'm the root of sins,
the initiator of evil.
I'm also the Devil King's
army's general, the Duke of Hell.
I'm Vanir, the archdemon who
sees through the whole world.
THE EMERGENCY MISSION OF DEFEAT VANIR,
THE DEVIL KING'S ARMY'S GENERAL.
The Devil King's army's general?
Hey, let's escape!
As someone who serves Goddess Eris,
how can I yield in front of a demon?
Do you want to defeat me, who's
probably as strong as the Devil King?
Just calm down.
Although I'm the Devil King's
army's general,
I'm just maintaining the city's barriers.
You could say I'm a general only in name.
The Devil King asked me to
investigate Verdia's case.
Meanwhile, I came to Axel to look for...
that good-for-nothing shopkeeper...
who has a weird talent for becoming
poorer the more she works.
Moreover, I belong to the demon clan.
Demons' favorite food is...
humans' negative emotions
when they're disgusted.
We'd be so excited whenever one of you
was born that we'd run around!
These dolls kept appearing
from this dungeon.
-The humans are very much bothered.
-What?
I used them to get rid of
the monsters in this dungeon.
Since they're outside, it means that
there are no more monsters here.
Then...
I'll proceed to the next plan.
What's your intention?
How rude!
You're a guy who became uneasy
and worried so much...
just because the armored girl
didn't go back for a few days.
Shut up!
Why are you saying it as if
you witnessed it yourself?
And you, stop getting embarrassed too!
I have a sublime destruction wish.
I'll get a dungeon first.
Then, I'll let the demons await their
orders in each room and set up traps.
The skilled adventurers will
come for the challenge!
After they've passed the brutal trials,
the brave adventurers will
reach the innermost room!
Of course, I'll be waiting in that room!
Luckily, you're here, adventurers!
Defeat me and get your
incredible rewards!
The final battle will finally begin!
After a fierce battle,
I'm finally defeated!
A sealed treasure chest
appears at the back.
After all the trouble,
when the adventurers open it,
there's a paper with
"you failed" written on it.
While watching the confused looks
on the adventurers...
I die away.
In order to carry out this plan,
I planned to earn money through my
friend's shop to build a huge dungeon.
I passed by this place by chance.
It seemed like the owner was
not here anymore,
so I decided to use this dungeon.
But there's a very powerful
magic circle in there.
I can't enter.
It was her again!
Your comrade drew the magic circle?
What is it?
Let me see.
Incredible!
Your archpriest comrade has drawn
such a troublesome magic circle!
I see it. I can see it.
I can see that priest is resting
while drinking tea.
That brat!
You, the girl who has lost
her bet against that guy
and has been helplessly and shyly
anticipating his unduly request!
I'm not helpless or shy!
Don't say something ridiculous!
Don't say it!
And you, the guy who's
nervously thinking of...
your request for her
after everything's settled!
I'm not nervous!
-I'm not!
-Step aside!
Although not killing humans
is my principle,
yes, I don't kill humans.
But, it only applies to humans.
The one who made this
annoying magic circle,
let me teach you a lesson!
He knows Aqua's true identity!
Since you're going to harm Aqua,
we can't stand down!
The girl who has not only strong abs
but is also headstrong,
let me pass through right now!
Then, you both can carry on
with your unduly requested...
without any disturbance!
Don't listen to this demon's words!
Don't be deluded by him!
I won't be deluded by him!
You're the one who needs to
consider the time and place!
What? I was clearly tempted.
Enough! Talking to you
will only mess with my mind!
Then, you both shall rest well in that
magic circle room before you go back.
Kazuma, stop hesitating!
We live in the same house! How can we
have that kind of weird relationship?
Get a hold of yourself!
She's pretty and her body is my type,
but her inner beauty isn't flattering.
I must get a hold of myself.
You'll regret it when we get back!
You looked threatening,
but you're missing all your attacks.
Where did that random guy go?
Compared to this brainless crusader,
he should be harder to deal with.
Where are you looking at?
I'm your opponent!
-What a pity!
-This is my chance!
I got it!
What?
Am I really going to die here?
Is it settled?
Gosh! I can't believe
there's a ball there.
But we've really succeeded, right?
You both were anticipating it,
but now you're disappointed!
Did you think I'd been defeated?
What a pity! No harm was done at all.
The negative emotions of
both of you are very delicious.
Darkness!
Hey! Answer me!
Listen up, brat!
-With my power...
-What do I do, Kazuma?
My body has been taken over!
What now, brat?
If you're able to attack her...
Don't mind me at all.
Just attack me all you want.
Quick! This is the perfect opportunity!
This is so noisy! What's wrong with you?
How is this possible?
What's wrong with...
-Amazing.
-this woman?
-How headstrong is she?
-I'm a good example of a crusader.
This is so annoying!
She's extraordinary to be
able to resist my control.
-It was nothing.
-But the more you endure it,
-the more painful your body will be.
-What?
How much longer can you keep it up?
What's happening?
The feeling of joy?
Please excuse me.
-I won't yield to this mere pain!
-You're very bold!
But you'll go insane
if you endure it any longer.
Are you enjoying this feeling
by any chance?
Alright, Darkness. Let's meet up
with Aqua and escape quickly.
Stop right there, brat!
Kazuma, don't mind me and go first.
-Actually, in your heart...
-I've wanted to say that!
You don't want to harm
this cute girl too, right?
If she keeps on enduring my power...
Kazuma! This self-proclaimed
all-knowing demon said something...
-that I minded very much just now!
-This is so annoying!
This body is such a failure.
Hey! It's very rude to call
someone's body a failure!
This is so annoying!
-I'm getting out now.
-No, you're not.
What talisman is this?
Wait, Kazuma! This is...
It's the Sealing Talisman that Sena gave.
Just go out like this
and let Aqua purify him.
-What?
Konosuba!
Brat, this girl is resisting my control.
Her body is experiencing intense pain.
If this continues,
her heart won't be able to stand it.
This is it, Kazuma!
This is the first time
I've felt this intense feeling!
He's the Devil King's
army's general, indeed!
I'm about to give in!
Hang in there! We'll make you feel
better after we get to the surface!
There's no need to.
-What did you just say?
Darkness! Luckily, you didn't give up!
Darkness?
-I've completely taken over her.
-No way!
Your archpriest will be
welcoming us with her guard down.
I must let her suffer!
Darkness! Wake up!
-You can do better than this!
-It's useless, brat!
Now, the touching reunion scene
where the comrades returned safely.
What will my detestable arch-enemy do
when she faces the possessed
body of her comrade?
Sacred Exorcism!
Darkness!
Fool! Don't use your magic
all of a sudden!
I felt an evil aura heading my way,
so I used it.
The Devil King's army's general has taken
over Darkness's body!
The Devil King's army's general?
So smelly! Why is it so smelly?
That's right! It's the aura of a demon!
Darkness, don't come near me!
I'll introduce myself first.
The archpriest with the same name as...
the infamously detestable
Goddess of Water!
-My name is...
-Aqua! I can't smell myself!
-I'm Vanir!
-Kazuma should smell me, too!
-I shouldn't be smelly!
-This is so annoying!
I'm Vanir.
We just met and you've used
the Sacred Exorcism.
This is why Axis Cult's people
are so infamously detestable.
Don't you have any manners?
Gosh, we're talking about
"manners" with a demon?
You can't live without
humans' negative emotions.
Aren't you a parasite?
Sacred Highness Exorcism!
-You're too unskilled!
-That was close!
Darkness! Why did you dodge? Don't move!
-Easy for you to say!
-That's too sly!
I want that mask too!
My Crimson Magic Clan heart
is strongly induced by it!
Idiot! That mask is his main body!
He's that all-knowing demon
on the wanted notice indeed!
Everyone, arrest him quickly!
Darkness, don't move!
Do you want to be saved or not?
I can't believe Darkness is
so difficult to deal with!
I kept missing! She blocked us
with her sword so easily!
This body's condition is very good.
It has both strength and stamina.
Luckily, she can withstand the magic
of those detestable gods too.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Just come at me,
you incompetent adventurers!
Darkness! You're arrogant just because
your swordsmanship improved a little!
I've always thought you were the most
upright one at Kazuma's party!
Surround her!
Let's surround this lame crusader!
The adventurers who'd usually speak
to me nicely are looking down upon me!
I feel a vague sense of happiness.
What's happening?
Please think of something!
Mr. Satou, are you not
going to join the battle?
Kazuma!
It's a huge crisis now!
It's the largest crisis so far!
Kazuma!
I wanted to take this opportunity
to teach Sena a lesson!
It's not me who's
causing trouble every time!
I'm just being dragged into trouble!
Am I considered lucky like this?
Kazuma!
There's no other way!
Darkness! Why did you get tamed
by a demon so easily?
Are you a frivolous and wanton woman?
It's useless! She can't hear you!
Who are you calling frivolous and wanton?
I'm not tamed by him!
She has such a resolute spirit.
I'm going to remove
the seal on the mask now.
Then, take the opportunity to regain
control of your body from Vanir!
Take off and throw away the mask!
You're just a good-for-nothing.
And I've maximized her full potential.
How are you going to break the seal?
I feel like I won't lose to
anyone right now.
-If you really can overpower me...
-This talisman...
-Remove it...
-Then...
-If you can...
-Just come at me!
This is so annoying!
Don't steal my exclusive lines!
Steal! Kazuma will surely use
his signature 'Steal,' right?
Hey! You've exposed my moves!
What do I do?
Kazuma! You have me to back you up!
Be brave and just do it!
Hey, Darkness!
This time, too, let's make a bet!
If I win,
I'll add something more unreasonable
to last time's unduly request!
I can't believe you're saying this here!
You! Stop being deceived
by his flowery speech!
Boost your magic power
and beware of his "Steal"!
Darkness! You must keep on resisting
so that Vanir is stuck!
Do you think an adventurer's
"Steal" will work?
Here I go!
-Just do it!
Tinder!
That's too cunning,
you despicable Kazuma!
I can't believe you can deceive
an all-knowing demon.
Hey, Darkness! Show some willpower!
I can't take it off!
-What?
-Kazuma! What do we do?
-Can I attack now?
-No!
This way, Darkness can withstand it
even if we use magic.
Just do it.
If Aqua's magic won't work,
then that's fine too.
Just use Explosion Magic on me.
No way! Compared to before,
my Explosion Magic has become...
much stronger after continuous training!
Even if it's Darkness, she...
Vanir, although it was a short time,
but being together with
you wasn't bad at all.
So, at least,
please make a choice.
Leave my body and get purified,
or bear the Explosion Magic together?
For a destructionist,
this will be the best choice.
I can't believe my destruction wish
will come true like this.
For me, possessing your body
was quite fun.
I'm a demon!
I'll never choose to be purified
by my enemies, the gods!
Do it, Megumin!
If anything happens,
just say that it was my order.
You shall be the witness.
This time, I'll take
full responsibility too!
Megumin!
The upended skyscraper that
has been concealed in this world
rises before my still spirit.
The time has come!
Awake now,
prepare yourselves through my pride,
and link yourselves!
Explosion!
Adventurer Satou Kazuma,
to honor you, our town is presenting
you with a certificate of appreciation.
At the same time, we deeply apologize
for doubting you before this.
After battling Vanir,
someone who's related to
the Devil King's army...
wouldn't have risked his life
to defeat the general.
Based on this reason, my suspicion as
the Devil King's spy has been cleared.
Firstly, I'm very happy not to worry
about being executed anymore.
Next,
Dustiness Ford Lalatina.
You've made great sacrifices
regarding this case.
Your actions have lived up to
the name of the Dustiness indeed.
The royals are presenting you with
a certificate of appreciation.
Also, to make up for the Armour
that you've lost in the battle,
we're presenting you the Armour
that the top craftsmen made.
Due to Megumin's Explosion Magic,
Darkness was injured badly
and almost lost her life.
She lost her favorite Armour too.
After that, she recovered
thanks to Aqua's care.
-Congratulations, Lalatina!
-Lalatina, well done!
-It's Lalatina, indeed!
-Lalatina, you're too cute!
This is so embarrassing! This isn't
the "unduly request" I had in mind!
Hey, Darkness! I think the name
"Lalatina" is very cute!
Kazuma spread your name
"Lalatina" as a joke.
I'll teach him a lesson for you later on!
So, you must have faith in
the name "Lalatina"!
Next, adventurer Satou Kazuma
and his party...
have contributed a lot in defeating
the Mobile Fortress Destroyer.
This time, as for defeating the
Devil King's army's general, Vanir,
we won't be able to make it
without your excellent performance.
So, I hereby clear you of your debts...
and your compensation
regarding the manor house.
I present you the remaining
40 million Eris...
after all your debts are cleared,
in honor of your contribution!
It's really noisy.
But this kind of day is not bad too.
Nature is beautiful.
Now, I've been released from...
my heavy burden...
and gained my freedom at last!
DEFEATED THE DEVIL KING'S GENERAL,
VANIR. INVESTIGATED KEELE'S DUNGEON.
DEBTS CLEARED. GAINED 40 MILLION ERIS.
(Episode 6:
Goodbye to This Irritating Living World!)