No!
It's still so cold outside!
Why do you both want to
go outside so badly?
We can't use Explosion Magic
if we don't go outside!
The monsters are very active
when early spring comes.
It's time for the adventurers to show up!
You both are not children anymore!
Are you both on the same level
as the children who want to play outside?
Since you both really wanted to go
outside, you should both just go!
Who are you calling "children"?
Aqua was more like a child just now!
If this continues,
you'll turn into "that."
I don't want to turn into "that," too.
But before persuading me, do something
about that good-for-nothing!
Hey, you three. I might be easygoing,
but I get angry when it's necessary.
You all just called me "that" and
said I was "good-for-nothing."
That was too rude.
If you have an opinion,
come out and say it.
(KONOSUBA:
God's Blessing on This Wonderful World! 2)
(Episode 6:
Goodbye to This Irritating Living World!)
We defeated Devil King's general,
demon Vanir.
But, we couldn't enjoy
and celebrate our victory.
Wiz is one of Devil King's generals too.
We need to clarify the brutal truth
about us attacking her comrade.
I'll tell her about Vanir.
Although it wasn't long
we wreaked havoc together
while sharing one body too.
As a crusader who serves Goddess Eris,
I probably shouldn't be saying this.
But he wasn't hateful at all.
-Wiz, I have something to say to you!
-Welcome!
The girl with a distant look in her
eyes who said embarrassing things...
in front of the shop,
I want to tell you something.
"But he wasn't hateful at all."
However, demons have no gender.
Even if you confessed to me
so shyly, I can't accept it.
Such a strong negative emotion
of embarrassment!
Delicious!
What's wrong? You're crouching while
burying your face in your hands.
Did you really think that I've perished?
There, there.
Mr. Kazuma, I've heard about it!
You all defeated Mr. Vanir and
cleared your suspicion as a spy!
-Congratulations!
-Let's not talk about this.
Why is he still alright after
being blasted by Explosion Magic?
He's completely unharmed! What happened?
After that attack, even I
couldn't have been unharmed.
Take a good look at my mask.
I've lost one life.
I'm now the second generation.
Are you kidding me?
Mr. Vanir planned to resign as
the Devil King's army's general.
So now, Mr. Vanir isn't in charge of...
maintaining the barrier of
the Devil King's Castle﻿.
He's totally harmless.
Harmless?
You, the guy who traveled from afar,
helping us with our business
is beneficial.
There's a good opportunity.
Do you want to hear it?
Vanir's "moneymaking business" was...
to produce and sell the products
from my original world here in bulk.
I'm in charge of developing the products.
Vanir guarantees batch production
and the sales channel.
The first stage of this plan
is this kotatsu.
I know the heating system of
Kazuma's world is excellent,
but it's almost time
to begin our work, no?
That's right, Kazuma.
-Come out.
-Freeze!
This guy is retaliating!
Kazuma, that's just about enough!
Stop retaliating! Behave yourself!
My head!
Don't underestimate me.
I'm Kazuma, who has dealt with Devil
King's generals and other big shots.
Re-challenge me after
you've improved your skills!
I won't yield just because of
these petty tricks!
How dare you steal my magic!
You scoundrel!
I won't lose to anyone right now.
It's an emergency.
I might sound selfish, but
let's call it a ceasefire for a while.
Sorry, could you both lift
the mat under the kotatsu
and bring me to the toilet like this?
They're quite compliant.
Let's throw this guy outside together
with his kotatsu.
Alright. Aqua! Please open the door.
Stop! Are you all still human?
-Stop! Wait! No!
-One, two!
It's still so cold.
Fireplace. Sofa.
Kazuma, why are we taking it this way?
The guild is not this way.
Don't assume that I was just
nesting in the kotatsu.
-Hello!
-Welcome!
Sir, is it done?
My katana is almost done, right?
Yes, it's done.
I made it according to
the shape that you wanted.
Here.
I didn't understand the technical
things like quenching and so on.
But it was still quite
an interesting job.
Is that your new partner?
My new partner.
Kazuma, when did you
make a sword like this?
I let him here learn some
blacksmithing techniques before.
It's necessary for that moneymaking
opportunity before, right?
At the same time, I wanted to change
my equipment to new ones too.
So, I asked for his help.
To finish up,
you just need to write its name on
this paper and stick it onto the hilt.
Give it a cooler name.
Also,
this is the full-plate Armour.
It's considered very fancy equipment
even for this town's adventurers.
Wear it well.
-This is the true fantasy equipment!
-So cool!
Now, I might've witnessed
the birth of a new hero.
Clothes make the man indeed.
It's even difficult for us crusaders
to get awesome Armour like this.
Kazuma, raise your sword!
Kazuma?
Top-notch warriors won't show
their unique skills easily.
Looks like it's too heavy
that you can't move it, right?
Can someone remove the
metal components on my back?
It's best to use the equipment
that you're used to.
It's good to have made a new weapon too.
I'm counting on you, partner!
I'm sorry!
Well then, thank you.
It's different than what I imagined!
Your partner has shrunk a lot.
Shut up!
I wanted to at least give it a cool name.
Muramasa?
Masamune?
-Kotetsu?
-Kazuma! Megumin!
We have a great quest.
The monsters are called "Lizard Runners."
During mating season,
the Male Runners will gather around
the Princess Runner and...
form a huge lizard group, and start
competing for the Princess Runner.
Competing?
Racing.
A large group of lizards ran and
destroyed everything in their path.
The fastest male will become
the King Runner...
and mate with the Princess Runner.
This sounded really irritating.
The quest this time is to get rid
of the Lizard Runners.
Due to their large amount,
I know that it's very difficult...
It's alright.
No matter what monster it is,
it'll be no match for this guy and I.
Right? Partner...
-Kiku Ichimonji? Kogarasu Maru?
-Chunchunmaru.
-What did you just say?
-I said, "Chunchunmaru."
This sword's name is "Chunchunmaru".
Who would give it such a bizarre name?
As my favorite blade,
I must give it a cool name.
From today onwards, this sword
will be called "Chunchunmaru."
What have you done?
Say,
if I defeat the Devil King
with this katana,
"The legendary hero's sacred sword,
Chunchunmaru," or something similar,
will be written on its edge and
be displayed in the museum.
I especially gave it a cool name
for you. Why are you dissatisfied?
KILL QUEST TO GET RID OF
THE LIZARD RUNNERS ARMY.
Everyone! Are you ready?
I'm all set!
I've also let Aqua use
her Support Magic on me
so that I can handle them
regardless of their amount!
If there are any that escape,
just leave them to me.
I'll get rid of them.
Good! Let's start according to the plan!
First, I'll snipe at the King Runner
and the Princess Runner.
As long as those two are down,
the Lizard Runners' army will disperse.
We can ignore the rest of
the insignificant ones.
If the sniping fails
and they come this way
while Darkness is blocking them,
I'll snipe at the King Runner and
the Princess Runner again.
If this fails, too, we'll settle them all
before getting surrounded by
Megumin's Explosion Magic.
I'll shoot those that have escaped
from above.
Aqua will be in charge of
backing all of us up!
Here we go!
I can tell that this is
the Princess, but...
Hey, Aqua! Which one is the King?
The most stuck-up one
should be the King, no?
I was foolish to have asked you.
That's it! The King should
run the fastest, right?
I'll summon them with magic
that attracts monsters.
The one that gets here first is the King!
-What did you say?
-Force Fire!
No! You big idiot!
Are you not satisfied if you don't
mess things up every time?
We can easily settle it by secretly
dealing with the King and Princess!
Why did you attract them here?
Why are you suddenly saying this?
I did it because I wanted to help!
Don't be angry!
After this, it'll definitely be
the same as always, anyway!
I'll definitely be ravaged by
those Runners until I cry!
I know! It always happens this way!
Just kill me!
Don't just lie there!
You'll really die if you
get trampled by them!
I got it!
Hey! I clearly shot the one
that looked like the King!
But they've become more aggressive now!
If you kill the King first,
one of them can become the new King.
The lizards will, of course, be excited.
You need to settle
the Princess Runner first.
You should've said it sooner!
Leave it to me!
Megumin!
Have a taste of my Explosion Magic!
Explosion!
My magic power!
Kazuma! I don't have enough magic
power to activate my Explosion Magic!
Why now, when it's this urgent?
Was it my fault?
Just come at me!
Darkness!
Kazuma!
Darkness! Hang in there!
I'll take care of it right away!
Don't mind me! Take your time.
Snipe!
That was so close.
Kazuma! Are you alright?
Aqua! Kazuma fell down in a weird pose!
Quick! Use Healing Magic...
Please live more carefully.
I went through a lot last time when I
violated the rules to resurrect you.
I'm sorry. I'm speechless this time.
As an adventurer,
I know that you'll be in danger anytime.
You're too careless this time.
Um, was everyone okay after I died?
Yes. The senior who was lying there...
get trampled by the lizards
and started crying midway.
But, when Darkness was holding them back,
the lizards dispersed after
they'd lost their Princess Runner.
Megumin was fine, too,
thanks to Darkness's protection.
Right now, senior is healing your body.
That's great!
Since that's the case, could you
let me wait here for a while?
That's fine. But you're really calm.
I've been through this kind of thing
multiple times.
It must be boring to stay in
this empty room all the time, right?
If I'm bored,
it means that everyone's safe.
There's nothing better than being bored.
What is this? Oh, no. My chest is aching.
Is it?
I've always felt that...
there's something missing
in my parallel world life.
Everyone is actually quite good-looking.
Although they're not bad,
however, what I'm after is not sexiness.
But, a gentle and knowledgeable girl!
That's right! The heroine is right here!
Actually, I'm not always here too.
I'll secretly go to the surface
to have fun every once in a while.
Regarding this,
you must keep it a secret.
Kazuma! Can you hear me?
I've used Resurrection!
You can come back now!
Please ask Eris to open the gate!
Wait for a while!
I want to chat with Goddess Eris
for a little longer!
Take good care of my body!
Stop talking nonsense! Come back quickly!
Level up and defeat the Devil King
sooner, then I can go back to heaven!
The Devil King?
After resurrecting,
I'll need to go defeat the Devil King
with those three.
-Kazuma!
-Should I continue to work hard?
-Will my special powers be awakened?
-Are you listening?
-Will I also defeat the Devil King?
-Eris! What are you doing?
This harsh world won't be so easy.
I'll surely die again, multiple times.
I've worked this hard,
but what did I get?
Her words are as fake as her chest!
Be careful!
-I'll tell you something crazier!
-Mr. Kazuma!
That just another pretty-face
goddess is, actually...
Hey, Aqua! I'm tired of living too!
I want to be reborn as a baby
and start a new life!
Say hi to everyone for me!
What nonsense are you saying? Wait!
So, this is it. I'll leave it to you.
I won't ask for much.
I just want to be a male, too,
in my next life.
Also, I want a pretty older stepsister
and a cute younger stepsister!
-Please wait for a second!
-Kazuma!
Darkness said that she'll draw on your
face if you're still not coming back!
She's already excited
with a pen in her hand!
I won't be bothered by this puny matter.
I'm dead anyway! Whatever.
What is Megumin doing?
What are you going to do
with Kazuma's clothes?
-Megumin! Wait!
-Hey! Stop it!
What are you all doing to my body?
Don't mess around with the dead!
You'll get your karma!
Megumin! Kazuma! Quick! Come back!
Hey! Stop it! Aqua!
Stop Megumin quickly! Stop...
Goddess Eris, please, open the gate!
Well then, Mr. Kazuma,
I wholeheartedly wish that
you won't come here again.
Goddess Eris! I...
Please take care.
I like just a pretty face too!
Hey, what are you doing?
Apart from your name and
being an explosion freak,
you're supposed to be the only
knowledgeable one here.
What actually did you do to me?
Hey! Just say it if you have
something against my name!
It's your fault for making that
stupid joke about not coming back.
If you repeat something stupid
like this the next time,
I'll do something worse for you.
You. What do you want a
sacred goddess like me to say?
What actually have they done to me?
What's actually happening?
Megumin! Where's Megumin?
Megumin said she wanted to
stay over at Yunyun's for a few days.
-Hey, Kazuma.
-What?
It's a good thing to
have self-confidence.
But it's also bad to show off too much.
Idiot! Weren't you there too when
Megumin wrote this on my body?
This is an abomination!
What did she mean by the
sacred sword, Excalibur?
(Episode 7:
An Invitation for This Knucklehead!)