Explode, explode, lalala...
Although the suspicion is still there,
Megumin and I carry on
with our daily tasks.
Explosion.
Rainy day.
Losion.
Snowy day.
A peaceful afternoon.
What do you think about
such a beautiful rainbow?
120 marks!
What am I doing?
I can't continue like this.
(KONOSUBA:
God's Blessing on This Wonderful World! 2)
(Episode 3:
Peace for the Master of This Labyrinth!)
The food and booze here are the best!
-We're going to the dungeon tomorrow.
-No.
We are going.
-No!
-We are going!
My existence is worthless in the dungeon!
I can't utilize my explosion magic.
I will become a totally
normal human being.
Remember when you first join the team?
You said you're willing to do anything,
including carrying luggage.
Can't we wait for Darkness before
we make any decision?
Don't you know? Our external debt
is as high as the state budget.
If this continues,
we will die of starvation.
The unit price for stacking
milk cartons has increased.
Besides that, we have been out
to sell vegetables.
The little income we gained
by doing these odd jobs...
is not enough to pay off the debt.
Keele's Dungeon, especially
for new recruits.
I thought there was nothing left
after it was looted.
Actually,
a new passage was found.
I'm about to post the drafted
investigation mission notice.
I implored her to make an exception
and assign the task to us.
That is why she hasn't told
the other adventurers yet.
I see.
There must be quite a few treasures
left in the unchecked areas.
Treasures?
What is it? A profitable job?
This is a severe problem.
I wouldn't want to drag you down.
This is a discount voucher,
expiring today.
Cherish it.
Leave this to me.
It's not easy for me to acquire
this chance to make some cash.
I'm not foolish enough
to let others join in too.
We have no idea how dangerous
it might be. Be careful.
EXPLORATION MISSION: EXPLORE THE NEWLY
DISCOVERED ROUTE IN KEELE'S DUNGEON
LEVEL OF DIFFICULTY: UNKNOWN
This is especially for newbies,
yet, it's so far, such bravery.
This is a secluded place.
We can just leave them here.
We need to go to the bottom.
Never leave them behind.
A long time ago,
the country's most powerful
wizard built the dungeon.
Why would he hide inside here?
Who knows?
After his death, this place
is turned upside down.
It's hard to imagine.
Alright, I will scout it out first.
Wait here, both of you.
By using the skills of bandits, skills
of sensing enemies and concealment,
I can avoid any encounter with enemies
and properly investigate this dungeon.
Then, I can use my farsight skill...
to master the space and location
of the dungeon, even in darkness.
This is a rare skill among adventurers.
Meanwhile, I have the privilege of
learning various professional abilities.
During this critical moment, I need to
use my only specialty well.
Can you really see everything?
Yes, I can.
Have you forgotten about what I said?
You can't see anything even
if you follow me into this dark place.
Have you forgotten who I am?
Archpriest is just a fake identity.
Tell me.
Although Megumin and Darkness
wouldn't believe it no matter what,
tell me, what's my profession?
The Goddess of Debt.
No! It's the Goddess of Water.
I am a Goddess, after all.
Although I've become weaker
after I drop down to earth,
I still possess a few of my divine powers.
Even though I can't
see through everything,
this level of darkness is nothing to me.
But it seems like only
some empty boxes are left.
-You might be able to see,
-It's so painful.
but who knows what
silly things you might do.
There is a lot of undead in the dungeon.
They can locate the living
through their life force.
Thus, your lie-low technique
won't work on the undead.
That's why I have to come with you.
-Treasures.-I only have bad feelings about this.
Treasures.
My power.
My blade.
My wild arrogance.
No one will get past me
and my wild arrogance!
Is it here?
It will be uncharted
territory starting here.
There must be a mountainous
worth of treasures.
It'll be worrisome otherwise.
Let's go.
With my crystal clear eyesight,
I can see your shivering body
walking down the stairs clearly.
Same with me.
Your pitiful shivering form whenever
there's a tiniest noise is as clear.
I can still escape even from here.
If you can feel any monster
nearing us, tell me.
And don't molest my butt
because it's dark.
Let me tell you what I am thinking now.
I'm seriously contemplating
how to dump you...
into the deepest part of the
dungeon and return by myself.
You are so funny, Kazuma.
You are so silly, Aqua.
We have known each other for so long.
You should know that
I'm just telling the truth.
Something is approaching.
My ability to sense enemies is triggered.
What is it?
Are you playing shadow hand with me?
Give me some light.
I'm not going to do some low-end
shadows like fox or rabbit.
I'm going to show you the
Mobile Fortress Destroyer.
It's not that!
I'm hand signaling you to run away
because an enemy is approaching!
What creature is that?
I can only see the outline but not
its true form using my farsight.
It's a low-class demon called Gremlin.
Some weak demons will pop out
in the dungeon occasionally.
You can see quite clearly in the dark.
About as clear as day.
Before this, you told me you
saw me creeping around the stables.
I didn't see anything.
I'll just turn to my back and continue
sleeping when there is noise.
Thank you, Lady Aqua.
What is it? The remains
of the adventurers?
Did someone else come to this place?
What's that in front?
Wait, Kazuma.
The soul that perished
with unresolved grievances.
Rest in peace.
Alright, it's done.
Aqua, today, you...
Kazuma, why did you yell so loudly?
The one who puts on airs and
insists on coming to this dungeon...
is yelping so loudly.
It's better if I leave her here.
Stab through! Explosion!
We should be looking for traps,
but after being terrified
by the monsters,
she's drawing maps...
while gingerly treading forward.
This is such an underhanded meaning
for those who came here...
with a serious intent
to explore this place.
There's nothing valuable here.
-Kazuma.
-I'm here.
Your words make me feel like I'm a thief.
Don't say it like that.
I have the same thought too,
and now I feel guilty.
Look! Treasures.
A treasure chest.
I've found it.
Wait.
Such an obvious treasure chest.
As expected.
My enemy-sensing ability is triggered.
This is so disgusting.
Come to think of it,
I've heard from the guild to be aware of
the shape-shifting monster in the dungeon.
Sometimes, they will shape-shift into
humanoid forms to hunt for monsters.
They even eat monsters?
This is too disgusting.
The survival of the fittest law...
applies in this dungeon too?
It's such a hardship
living in this world.
Stop!
Stop it. Hand over this
disgraceful thing to me.
Wench! I'll kill you all.
Turn Undead.
To all the lost souls in
this cold and dark dungeon.
Rest in peace.
Aqua is quite different today.
She's a very presentable and
outstanding Goddess.
-Teacher.
-Turn Undead.
Teacher.
Turn Undead.
The power of flowers, birds,
wind and moon, God's Blow!
I'm saved.
It'd be very dangerous
if I were to come alone.
Finally, you are appraising me
with the correct value.
You can admire me a little bit more.
But don't you think this is too strange?
Why is it?
There is too many undead around.
Without a team of archpriests,
It'll be troublesome...
-to deal with them.
-Wait.
I can feel the presence of
the undead over there.
Smell.
There's nothing.
Strange. I did feel the
presence of the undead.
Are you alright?
A priest is present?
I am Keele.
I am the evil wizard that
built this dungeon and...
kidnapped the aristocrat's daughter.
Wizard Keele.
You are devoted to our country.
I'll fulfill one of your wishes.
I have only one wish.
I wish for happiness and no more
bullying toward the girl I love.
You...
She is married here to
appease you, my King.
But she wasn't favored and was
bullied by the people in the palace.
If...
If you don't need her,
please bestow her to me.
Just like that, I took away the daughter.
In other words,
you are not an evil wizard
but a kind one?
That was before.
After I proposed to the lady
that I had kidnapped,
she agreed immediately.
Thus, the lady and I began the
fleeing game of love while...
playing the grand banquet
of magic with the king.
It was a happy time.
By the way, that's the lady
that I have kidnapped.
What do you think?
She has a very nice collarbone, right?
What is happening here?
-She is resting in peace.
-So pretty.
And then, I need to ask you a favor.
A favor?
Can you purify me?
This priest has that ability, right?
Keele was seriously injured
while protecting her.
But in order to guard her forever,
he forsook his identity as human
and became a lich.
I can't help but...
think that this lich is very handsome.
Everything is prepared.
That's great.
It's too unrealistic for
the undead to commit suicide.
Before that, I plan to just wait
until my spirit vanishes.
But I felt a surge of
extraordinary sacred power.
That's why I woke up
from my deep slumber.
The wizard discarded the law of
deity and chose the path of the lich.
Keele.
I shall pardon your sins in the
name of the Goddess of Water, Aqua.
Who is she really?
When you awake,
the one who appears in front of you...
should be Goddess Eris with
an unnaturally large chest.
If you are willing to disregard age,
disregard any possible relationship...
and in any other forms,
please beg her.
Tell her that you want to see
this lady for one last time.
She will definitely fulfill your wish.
Thank you.
Sacred Turn Undead.
Darling, I'm coming to accompany you now.
Let's go back.
With the treasures left by Keele for us,
we left the room.
-Aqua.
-What is it?
That guy said that he woke up because
he felt an extraordinary divine power.
We've repeatedly encountered
much undead in the dungeon.
Are you the reason behind it?
No way.
It's impossible.
I think so.
Now that I've thought about it,
when Dullahan attacked us last time,
you were also chased by
his undead minions, right?
Kazuma.
Why do you distance yourself from me so?
We should walk together more closely
to prevent a sudden attack from monsters.
You want to leave me here
and go back by yourself.
-I won't let you succeed.
-Let go.
Without me to defeat the undead,
you can't go back by yourself, Kazuma.
Please, don't leave me.
As I said, you are the one
who lured the undead here.
No, there are other monsters,
don't leave me behind.
Conceal.
Wait, Kazuma.
How can you conceal yourself only?
Seriously? Don't joke around with me.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
I was wrong. Please give me
some of your concealment power.
I'm sorry, Kazuma.
Master Kazuma.
Can I ask what happened?
-Kazuma...
-Don't blame me.
You are the one who easily
attracted those undead.
But I am born brimming
with such divine life force.
You can't blame me for it.
Are you saying that...
I should dim down my divine halo...
and end up like Kazuma, who stays
at home and lives off his parents?
If that happens,
my devoted Axis Cult worldwide
will be devastated.
You are not repenting at all.
Learn properly from those two and...
try to understand that kind of purity.
How dare you ask a goddess
to learn from the undead?
You home-bound-living-off-
your-parents brat.
TODAY'S ACHIEVEMENT: KEELE'S DUNGEON
INVESTIGATION COMPLETE
SPECIAL PRIZE: KEELE'S TREASURES
Cheers!
I wish I could experience it too.
Thanks to me, this time,
the mission was successful.
We can split it nine to one.
Stupid, we need to use it
to pay off our debt.
But today, I can order
another drink, right?
Excuse me, please bring me
more of the foamy beer.
All I did was wait outside.
It wouldn't do for me
to accept the payment.
-Give me more.
-It's too early, kid.
-You are too cunning.
-Let me drink it.
Let me drink it.
It's nothing, drink more foamy beer.
I can't continue with the odd jobs,
I want to do missions.
With the power of flowers,
birds, wind and moon.
There it is!
Sister, you've saved us this time.
This is on me, please enjoy the drink.
Alright.
What? A treat?
Is it true? Everybody,
Kazuma is going to treat us today.
It's great!
Kazuma is the man.
Your generosity is on point.
You are the man, Brother Kazuma.
-Kazuma.
Alright then, drink to your
heart's content, everyone.
Kazuma, do that trick.
Alright, since you insisted.
-Steal.
Steal.
I heard it's your treat tonight.
No!
Give me back my panties.
-Steal.
-Stop it.
I know how to do it too. Steal.
They've gone too far.
Megumin.
It is such a coincidence
to meet you here.
Just the right time.
I'll challenge you to these drinks today.
Alright, I accept.
Gutter Belt.
Our external debt is still there
and we are still under suspicion.
But this feels nice.
I guess I'm an adventurer, after all.
Drink till you drop today!
What am I doing here?
I'll be doomed if this continues.
(Episode 4:
A Betrothed for This Noble Daughter!)