ENTER REVIVAL SPELL
KAZUMA IS INVINCIBLE IN WONDERFUL WORLD
SPELL INCORRECT
THE ADVENTURE BOOK IS FADING AWAY
GOD'S BLESSING ON THIS WONDERFUL WORLD
My name is Satou Kazuma,
I am the Etranger who is
fated to defeat the Devil.
The Goddess of Fate led and
reincarnated my soul in another world.
I am in an unknown world
of destruction and chaos.
However, I have fellows bond
with strong ties.
They are the greatest witch,
the noble and beautiful knight,
and the pretty Goddess willingly
joined to the journey.
The fate of the Gear has been
spinning faster and faster.
To save this wonderful world,
our adventure starts again!
Arrest him!
This can't be it!
(Episode 1)
I want to go home,
(Give Me Deliverance from this Judicial Injustice!)
I want to go back to Japan.
I am Sena,
the prosecutor of this kingdom.
Adventurer Satou Kazuma,
you are now suspected of treason.
Hold on, Kazuma.
What have you done again?
Apologize now.
We'll apologize together.
Say sorry right away!
What do you mean by 'again'?
You know I didn't do anything.
The teleportation spell you ordered
blew up the Governor's mansion.
What?
Fortunately, there were no casualties.
We suspect you are a terrorist
and a spy for the Devil King.
Hold on a moment!
In the battle with Destroyer,
if it wasn't for Kazuma's idea,
the outcome could have been much worse.
Megumin.
The worst crimes he committed
are mere harassments.
Ma'am, there must be a misunderstanding.
Darkness?
This man here doesn't have the guts.
He stared at me like a hungry beast
in the inn, yet he never asked me out.
He is nothing but a coward.
No! I wasn't staring at you!
Don't get so arrogant just because
you have a nice figure!
I have the right to choose too!
You! You did that nasty thing to me
at the bathing pool.
That's because I was being controlled
by the dream spirit!
You used that chance to
scrub my back as well.
How easy can you possibly be?
So you do remember everything!
I am the guardian knight of Lord Eris,
I am even a virgin!
How dare you label me as easy.
I will kill you!
Come on!
Right, Kazuma is an adventurer,
not a criminal.
You are abusing the law of this kingdom.
The adventurers are free!
Freedom!
The treason charge...
also applies to those
who are not the main perpetrators.
If you wish to join this man
in prison, I won't stop you.
Are you kidding me? Come on, rally up!
Right, Kazuma did say this back then.
It's okay, I will take full
responsibility for this.
Don't look down on me,
I am quite lucky, you know.
Yes!
Seriously?
-If...
-If?
If I was at the scene,
I'd definitely stop him.
But I couldn't do anything
since I wasn't there.
Yes, there was nothing I could do.
You traitors.
Wait, that's it!
I am the main perpetrator,
I gave him the order.
So, there must be a
prison sentence for me!
No. I mean, please, I deserve
a cruel punishment!
What? You just made yourself
the human shield.
I haven't seen that in a while.
So,
-we used teleportation...
-Wiz, no.
It's best to just let him
take the blame alone.
It's cruel, but just hold on.
You have to bear with this.
Let's wait for him to
serve safely and come out.
Don't say it like I am
going to jail for sure!
Besides, I have the comrades from
the guild even if you abandon me.
Look, there is dust here.
Take him down!
Damn it, they call this
a town for newcomers?
If this were a game, the rebels
would have come to my rescue by now.
-What?
-Kazuma!
Aqua!
Why did you come here?
I am here to save you.
You are our important comrade.
You should have defended me just now.
Megumin is casting an
explosion spell nearby.
All the security guards are scattered.
Darkness is now carrying Megumin,
who has just finished her spell...
out of that place.
But escaping will only make things worse.
The punishment for treason
is the death sentence.
Even a no-name like you can
be wronged and executed.
This is undoubtedly a
medieval fantasy world.
But how do I get out of here?
Use this pin to open the lock.
Then, use your stealth magic
to run away from here.
Once you return to the inn,
we'll plan for your escape.
I will wait for you
in front of the building.
But this is a combination lock.
Off you go!
Back to sleep.
Kazuma! Wake up, Kazuma.
You are here again?
What happened yesterday?
Is everyone okay?
They came back without
being seen by anyone.
But they are being accused of
causing the explosion.
Well...
Their investigation is rather efficient.
-But don't worry.
-What?
I forced them to cover
their faces with bags.
Things should go well tonight.
But that was for casting
the explosion spell.
I was waiting for you all night,
why didn't you come out?
I had layers of snow on my head
and was questioned so many times.
What a drag.
The lock is a combination lock.
Not bad.
I didn't see this coming in
our flawless escape plan.
But not tonight.
A saw? You want me to use that?
Smart boy. There isn't much time left.
We have to work together.
Hurry up.
I am not tall enough to reach.
It's okay. I am not a fool.
I brought you a footrest.
I see.
But how do you get that in here?
Hold on a minute.
No!
I brought this because
Kazuma really needs it.
I've never heard anyone bring
a footrest as a gift.
Besides, how did you
come up with this idea?
-You were here yesterday too.
-That fool is so optimistic,
I am actually impressed.
Off you go!
Back to sleep.
Do you know what this is?
It's a magic item that detects lies.
First of all,
tell me your birthplace and job
before becoming an adventurer.
She started with the tough questions.
I was born in Japan
and went to school there.
Why did it ring?
Faking birthplace and experience.
Write them down.
Wait, I didn't lie!
I was born in Japan.
I stayed home every day
and lived a wasted life.
Why did you bluff that you are a student?
I wasn't bluffing.
That's enough.
Curse that magic item!
I have never heard of
a place called Japan.
So, why did you become an adventurer?
To save the people who are
tormented by the Devil King.
Adventurer looks cool.
I wanted to make a lot of money...
and be surrounded by ladies.
Very well, next question.
What is your grudge against the governor?
I heard you were complaining
everywhere when you were in debt.
The money we earned from defeating
Beldia is used as a mortgage...
for the repair of the streets,
that's why we were in debt.
We said we would save the town,
but I know if we destroyed the town
it would become pointless.
Yes, I used this reason to
persuade my angry friends.
Honestly, I saved the town but
am now treated like a sinner,
I sure want to kill that guy.
Is that so? Next question.
Hold on a moment.
Just be straightforward
with the questions.
I told you many times
I did it to save the town.
It seems like I was right.
All the rumors about you
are bad and loathsome.
I am sorry for that.
That was gentle.
Was her harsh tone only for criminals?
Seriously?
Judging a man on rumors?
What a lousy prosecutor you are.
I am sorry.
Do you know about my splendid records?
I contributed the most in
the battle against Beldia.
I was a great commander in
the battle against Destroyer.
I got no gratitude but
accusations for that!
I am sorry, but this is my job.
Of course, I know about your records.
However...
However what?
Right, I am yet to be proven guilty,
but I didn't even get a cup of tea.
If possible, I would like
a nice bowl of rice with meat.
Rice with meat?
I am sorry, but we don't have that.
I will get you the tea right away.
This is awful!
A prosecutor can't even
make a good cup of tea?
I am sorry.
I bet you don't have a boyfriend
because of your bad temper.
Tell me now.
I am sure you have something
that can be attractive.
None at all.
Yes, I can't get a boyfriend
despite my age...
all because of my bad temper.
Are you satisfied with that answer?
Don't be too arrogant.
I am sorry.
Do you know what
the people say about you?
-What?
-Human filth and dirtbag.
That is too much! Who gave me such names?
As a precaution, I will ask you again.
Are you really not
one of the Devil King's men?
Have you been in contact with
the Devil King's officers?
Of course not!
I am...
Do I really look like
I am capable of such a thing?
Oh no, Wiz is one of
the Devil King's generals!
We will now start the trial
of the suspect Satou Kazuma.
Are you nervous?
Don't worry, I will make
that prosecutor cry like a baby.
Relax, Kazuma.
You have done nothing wrong.
Reliable, they are really reliable.
However...
It's okay, just leave everything to me.
She is the real problem.
Hey, I think he is looking at us.
That is the governor, Alderp.
Prosecutor, please come forth.
Anything that threatens
the governor's life
is a matter that will cause
disruption to the land.
So, I hereby charge the suspect
Satou Kazuma of treason.
Witness, come forth.
Chris?
For some reason, I was brought here.
SATOU KAZUMA ROBBED THE PANTIES
He took Chris' panties with Steal
in front of everyone?
Is that correct?
That was what happened, but...
I saw it!
He was waving the panties on the street!
Who is the man you speak of?
We just need to verify
the truth from the witness.
Thank you.
SATOU KAZUMA STOLE
THE DEMON SWORD AND RESOLD IT
I heard Kazuma stole your sword
and sold it to someone else.
Yes, that's what happened.
But I was the one that started...
-Thank you.
-I have something else to say!
SATOU KAZUMA THREATENED THE LADIES
When the two ladies there
took the sword back,
he threatened you to show
your panties in public?
Yes, he threatened us!
He said he is a feminist and didn't
hold back even if we are girls.
You filthy pervert!
Yes! He said his Steal will
go amok in front of everyone!
I saw his hand, it was very suspicious.
The gesture of his hand
is very suspicious!
Thank you.
-Pervert.-That is awful.
Worthless scum.
This is bad!
Things are getting real bad here!
That is enough, execute him now.
Objections!
I admit Kazuma has a twisted personality.
But mere statements cannot
be used as evidence.
Megumin.
If you say he is a terrorist,
you need more proof for such a claim.
That's right, we want proof!
Proof?
Very well.
First of all,
he defeated Beldia, yet
he flooded the whole town.
Secondly,
the explosions near the town changed
the landscape and Eco-system.
They even caused unease
during the nights lately.
My advocates are no good at all.
And thirdly,
someone saw him use a skill
only the Undead can use.
That particular skill is Drain Touch.
I won't answer that!
I'll retain my right to remain silent!
These are hard facts even
if you close your ears.
And for the most obvious evidence,
when I asked you if you were in
contact with the Devil King's men,
the magical lie detector
caught you lying.
Are these not the evidence?
No! All hope is lost!
Kazuma is the criminal!
My Lord, what should I do now?
-That is enough.
-He is always so wasted,
-he must be connected to the Devil.
-And now he is a criminal!
-He is now a criminal!
-Good, this is my chance.
He blew up my mansion. Execute him now.
No.
I am not the Devil King's man,
nor am I a terrorist.
Still trying to buy your way out?
I have confirmed
your statements are lies.
Good, watch this!
Here I go.
I am neither the Devil King's spy
nor a terrorist!
How could that happen? Your Excellency...
With that said, I can't take the
prosecutor's statement as evidence.
Suspect Satou Kazuma,
the evidence against your crimes
is insufficient.
-You are hereby declared...
-Hold on, Your Excellency.
Lord Alderp?
Are you trying to humiliate me?
That is such a dirty trick!
Only an adventurer will fall for that.
That is why I hate medieval time.
The suspect is guilty
and shall now be sentenced to death.
This is totally wrong!
Your Excellency, please hear me out.
Darkness?
That is the family crest
of House of Dustiness!
House of Dustiness?
The noble family was known by
the name 'King's Blade'.
That lady seems to have
a tale to tell all along.
But I never see this coming.
I kept the secret for you.
He is very crafty.
You would be dead by now
if I hadn't said that.
Can I have the authority
to handle this case?
I am not asking you to pretend
nothing has happened.
Give me time, and
I will prove his innocence.
Even with your background of Dustiness...
I will owe you once for this.
I will do anything you ask
that is within my capability.
-Anything I want?
-Yes, anything.
-Lady Darkness.
-Darkness.
Yes, Kazuma didn't do anything bad!
He gave me a voucher!
Go to hell, judge.
Kazuma!
-Order!
-Kazuma!
Order! I order you to shut it, you dirt!
Since this is the request
from Miss Dustiness,
we will trust you with this case.
The suspect, Satou Kazuma, shall
remain innocent for now.
That is great, Kazuma!
I may not understand much,
but not having a death sentence...
is worth celebrating.
Here are the elements for the celebration!
My mind and defense have worked well too.
You gave up a long time ago.
SATOU KAZUMA REMAINS INNOCENT
AND BE MONITORED AS A SUSPECT
I must thank you for today.
Don't celebrate so soon.
But I will handle Alderp.
Are you sure about that old man?
The way he looked at you was weird.
He might ask something nasty from you.
Nasty stuff?
-I may have worried too much.
-No, it's okay.
I will take my leave now.
-Lalatina.
-Don't call me that!
I'll kill you!
I have two missions.
One is to prove that I am
not with the Devil King.
The second one is to pay for
the damage to the mansion.
This may seem unreasonable,
but Darkness, who spoke for me,
had to agree to the terms.
Next, the second chapter
of my adventure...
will now begin!
As per the order from
the Justice Department,
the debt owed to the victim
will be paid with your personal items.
The second chapter of my
adventure will soon begin.
SUSPECT SATOU KAZUMA
TOTAL DEBT: 1.24 BILLION
(KONOSUBA:
God's Blessing on This Wonderful World! 2)
(Episode 2:
A Friend For This Crimson Demon Girl!)