Do you have the flu?
You need to take care of your health.
You too, Kazuma, your voice sounds nasal.
I'll be done with the sewing
of your sweater soon.
You are the one who
burnt it in the fireplace.
Are you hungry already?
Come to think of it,
I haven't had my breakfast.
It's because you got carried away
and spent all the money on booze.
It's because everybody
is drinking so merrily.
This looks like high-quality
bubbly booze...
that I had hidden under my bed.
The pawnshop is still open, right?
Come here, Chomusuke.
Give that back. It's the last bottle.
My last hope.
I'm going to exchange it for money now.
Or I shall finish it now to
warm my cold body.
No, I can't sleep without
hugging it to me.
Coming from you who burnt
the sweater of others.
Then I shall sell off
your priest garment.
What are you talking about?
This garment represents
my identity as a goddess.
How can you sell it?
Are you dumb? What foolishness
are you spewing about?
Steal.
Master Kazuma, I'm the one
who got carried away.
-Don't sell it.
-You are so noisy.
Our debt is still as much as before
and Darkness has yet to return.
Can you be more aware of our crisis?
Something bad had happened, Kazuma.
Who are you?
(KONOSUBA:
God's Blessing on This Wonderful World! 2)
(Episode 4:
A Betrothed for This Noble Daughter!)
Who are you?
Are you enjoying yourself?
-Kazuma, continues this play later.
-So terrifying.
Are you Darkness? You have made us worry.
Darkness.
Kazuma, he...
forcefully took off my most
important garment to sell it.
How can you say it like that?
Darkness, welcome back.
Megumin, I'm back.
This cat...
I won't ask.
Go and take a bath first...
to settle down and relax your body.
What are you talking about?
Actually, I'm more curious
about Aqua's peculiar play.
The ultimate...
top-notch woman.
You must have been through a lot.
What have you misunderstood?
Are you thinking that the Governor
is toying with me?
All is well as long as you are back.
Quickly take a hot bath
and cry to your heart's content.
That's not it.
The Governor doesn't have
enough guts to ask that from me.
Take a look at this.
What is it?
Who is this handsome man?
-I'm pissed.
-What are you doing?
Uncontrollable hands.
That handsome man is
the son of the Governor.
In exchange for Kazuma's pardon,
he asked for my hand to marry his son.
I didn't come back before that...
because I was doing my best
to prevent the marriage.
Him aside, my father
speaks highly of him.
My father approves of
this proposal the most.
Please, let us together
convince my father otherwise.
It's done.
How is it? Isn't it perfect?
You are quite talented
in this kind of thing.
But, if we don't take this matter
into our own hands,
our team's vital crusader will be
married off as somebody's wife.
More importantly...
Thank you, Aqua.
-Marry off as somebody's wife?
-I almost can't get out of it.
It means that she almost
can't break off the marriage.
Our team's crusader with poor aims
will have to quit to get married.
It's not that I want to chase her away
because she is completely useless.
Such a miracle. You can
worship me a little bit more.
-Kazuma.
-Worship me a little bit more.
This is a great chance.
I am Kazuma.
You want me to accept this proposal? Why?
Are you okay with it if Darkness
can no longer be an adventurer?
Even if you reject the proposal,
that Governor will do his best to
deliberately make things difficult.
That's right.
That's why we have to accept it first
and wreak havoc later.
But this will affect the reputation
of Darkness's family.
You are right. Let's do this.
If this goes well,
I won't need to pain myself...
dealing with my father every time
the subject of marriage comes up.
I pity your father.
Satou Kazuma.
Is Satou Kazuma here?
What is wrong with today?
The borders of the city are filled
with unidentified monsters.
Do you have any idea about it?
Please follow me immediately.
I must reject.
Now, our important companion
is in a critical situation.
We can't turn a blind eye
to her situation.
Megumin.
Calm down.
Wait, I can deal with Aqua.
But at odd times,
Megumin can be smart too.
Truthfully, it's better
if she's not here.
Megumin.
You can go.
Go and take care of those monsters.
This is high time for you to
use your Explosion Magic.
It'll be alright.
Aqua and I will take care
of Darkness's situation.
But...
Only you can do this.
Only me.
I shall leave it to you,
the strongest magician!
I'll let you experience my true power!
Konosuba!
Is it true, Lalatina?
Yes, Father.
This time, Lalatina would like
to accept the proposal.
These two are?
They are my adventure companion.
I would like them to accompany me
as the temporary butler and maid
for my marriage.
Is it the right size?
It feels all right to me.
It's quite fitting.
You look like first-class errand girl.
So are you.
Straighten your back and assume the
impression of a butler in training.
How very interesting.
I'll make you pay for it...
if we are not in the
residence of an aristocrat,
am I right, Lady Lalatina?
Don't call me Lady Lalatina.
Your father has requested for me...
to help you along and to make sure
you don't make a fool out of yourself.
And, if the marriage is successful,
I will be rewarded.
Thus, I'm driven even though
I'm not willing to do it.
You know the plan.
I'll leave it to you then.
I'm pleased that you are willing
to accept this marriage.
Be happy, Lalatina.
What are you talking about, Father?
I just said that I would
consider this proposal.
What?
After my consideration,
I've decided that it is still
too early for me to get married.
It's too late now.
Although I have accepted the proposal,
I haven't accepted the marriage.
Destroy it.
Destroy this marriage!
Lalatina.
Please don't use such boorish words.
They might not like it.
Are you going to betray me?
I am the temporary butler
of the Darkness family now.
My only wish for you
is to find happiness.
Kazuma.
Kazuma, you...
Walter.
You are here. Are you the one who
is going to be my marriage partner?
I am Dustiness Ford Lalatina.
You may call me Lady Dustiness.
Mistress, please be
mindful of where you step.
Aren't you supposed to help me?
Did you forget all about not ruining
your family's reputation?
If someone talks bad about me
and scares my partner,
I can continue my adventurous
undertaking without hesitancy.
I'm prepared to sever my family's
relationship if it comes to that.
But I still grit my teeth and get on
with this impossible task.
Then, I got caught by the gaze of...
the Devil King and was
pressed flat to the floor.
-It's a crusader, not Devil King.
-That is the life that I want.
Finally, you speak of the truth.
Besides that, he is not my type.
First of all, he has a good personality.
He is an even-tempered man.
Very diligent.
He is the youngest person ever to be
awarded the knight's medal.
-He sounded fine to me.
-Fine?
An aristocrat should act
like an aristocrat.
He should maintain
a vulgar smile at all times.
And what about his pure, clear
and penetrating gaze?
He should look at me...
with a more indecent gaze,
like the one given by Kazuma.
I didn't look at you like that.
Won't he ever get mad?
Who is he trying to fool?
When a maid has done something wrong,
as an aristocrat,
he should do this and that to her
in the name of punishment.
My type of man...
is totally opposite from the man who
likes me even though I ignore him.
The man I like can look ordinary,
slim, weak, or even fat.
Although I like him with all my heart,
he will succumb to his lust...
when he is seduced.
I prefer that kind of weak-willed man.
He should be wild, dissipated
and lecherous at all times.
The one who wishes
to be gluttonous, lazy...
and looks down on life is the best.
It'll be better if he
has an external debt.
He should lose himself in a drink
every day and refuse to work.
And he will complain and blame
society for his degradation.
Then he will throw me
the empty bottle and tell me this.
Darkness, use your lewd body...
to earn some coins for me.
Darn it. This woman is too far gone.
Please let me introduce myself.
I am Alexei Barnes Walter.
I am Dustiness Ford Lalatina.
Let's not go into details about
our family background.
I'm sure the son of the nouveau riche
governor will understand it as well.
What happened?
It's nothing.
I'm just having a bad mood whenever
I see your face, Sir Walter.
Our Mistress is excited...
because she can finally meet you.
Come to think of it,
your face is very red.
I'm sorry for that.
Mistress, if you utter more
of those unnecessary things,
it will be more and more chilling.
This is a reward.
Our Mistress is really unyielding.
I'll only be in your way
with my presence.
Let's take a stroll in the garden.
How about that?
What kind of trick is that? Awesome.
I'll ask her to teach me later.
May I ask what your hobby is?
I like to hunt goblins once in a while.
You two are quite close.
Did I overdo it?
Yes, my butler and I are inseparable.
We eat together and bathe together.
Of course, during the night, we...
This shrewd woman has no sense of shame?
I'm not going to continue this anymore.
Am I right, Walter?
Follow me to the
training ground right now.
We shall see about your
natural endowments.
Darkness.
Look, as an aristocrat,
you should learn from Kazuma and
have this kind of vulgar gaze daily.
Miss Lalatina, I am a knight.
I won't raise my sword against a lady.
You are so annoying.
Kazuma over there...
is an advocate of gender equality.
He said he would even high-kick a woman.
Actually,
I came here...
to reject this marriage proposal.
But I changed my mind after I saw you.
You are bold and uninhibited
but, at the same time, cute.
You are frank and straightforward.
And you did not treat
your butler with arrogance.
I'm intrigued by you.
It's enough.
Why won't you stop?
What is it?
Don't hold back, make your move.
Show me your true strength.
Just now, Darkness's wooden
sword can't even touch him.
No matter how I see it,
Walter is in the upper hand.
I lost.
Although I'm more skillful,
but my heart is not as tough as yours.
I cannot fight with you anymore.
You are very strong.
It feels like he has lost to
Darkness's strong will.
But knowing Darkness's true colors,
I'm not touched at all.
You are so annoying.
Come, Kazuma.
Let's show Walter your ruthless
and heterodox ways.
What is she blabbering about?
I would like to see it too.
How would you,
the confidante of Lalatina...
fight with her.
Busybody Walter.
Since the marriage is a failure...
and you wouldn't slander or spread
deceitful rumors about her.
Good, come on, Kazuma.
Actually, I've been wanting
to fight with you for a long time.
-Create Water.
-Bring it on.
What is it?
You can't use magic in
a wooden sword sparring.
Is that so?
So terrifying. No one can beat Kazuma...
in the field of sexual harassment.
-It wasn't my intention.
-Did you see, Walter?
Look at this man's shameful manner.
Enough, you are the one who
asked me to bring it on.
I shall do my best then.
Freeze.
Demon.
Not only have you sprayed her with
water in this bitterly cold winter,
you even used freeze magic on her.
His nicknames are Devilman Kazuma
and Kazuma Scum, after all.
You are really ruthless.
This...
is great!
Great, Darkness.
When it comes to wrestling,
Kazuma is an unworthy opponent.
I'll sell off her priest's garment later.
Do you think you can win me by force?
Don't underestimate me.
I am a crusader and
you are an adventurer.
There's a large gap between
our physical strength.
It's impossible that I will
meet force with force.
We are long-time friends.
You should know.
It's so painful.
Drain Touch?
But, before you suck away my strength,
I will snap off your wrists.
You can try.
It's so painful.
This is bad, this weirdo's
strength is limitless.
Let's make a bet.
The term is the loser has to
fulfill the winner's request.
Alright.
If I win, I'll ask you to
kneel down before me.
I have hope.
Is that so? Then we have a deal.
If I win, I won't listen,
even if you plead with me in tears.
What are you doing?
Something so abashed that
it will bring you to tears.
I can imagine the way you cry
and beg for mercy.
You will scream for my mercy
and ask for my forgiveness.
You are too impatient.
Such a greedy fellow.
I'll command you to do things
that even you can't imagine.
Stop it.
I want to resist, but my strength is
sucked away by Drain Touch.
She's the one who has
diminished her power.
-I'll lose if this continues.
-He's good.
I'll deplete you of your strength
until you lose consciousness.
Look forward to the sufferings that
you have to endure when you wake up.
No matter how you humiliate me,
my heart won't be subdued.
Torment?
Torment.
Quick, go take a hot bath...
and cry to your heart's content.
Kazuma.
What are you going to do with the
water that I've used to bathe myself?
Tor...
Torment!
I won!
Kazuma Scum really suits you.
You are too rude.
I've brought you some drinks.
Please enjoy it.
-It's done by both of them.
-Alright, begin the punishment.
No, it's a misunderstanding.
Konosuba.
My daughter finds socializing difficult.
She was alone even after
she became a crusader.
She went to Eris's church every day.
And she prayed that she could find
some adventurer companions.
One day, she came back happily.
She said she finally had found a friend,
she's a female bandit.
My wife passed away in her early age.
As a man, although I did pamper her,
I still gave her plenty of freedom.
She shouldn't be like this.
No, that's her natural instinct.
Miss Lalatina is an outstanding woman.
If it wasn't because of Kazuma,
I would take her as my wife.
I'm sorry, but I don't understand.
Miss Lalatina will be happier with you.
Come over here.
I don't care if you are
the son of the Governor.
Stop, Kazuma.
Don't drag me down.
Kazuma, from now on,
I shall leave my daughter to you.
Help me look after her.
Don't let her act foolishly.
I beg of you.
Alright.
Are you awake?
Is this the after-effect?
We did lewd things after
I lost consciousness?
No, I didn't do anything to you.
While you were sleeping,
this baffling atmosphere set upon us.
Father, Sir Walter.
Please discard this idea of marriage.
Although I've hidden the truth from you,
actually, I am carrying Kazuma's baby.
What are you talking about?
I am still a virgin.
Is that so? You are with Kazuma's child?
I'll tell father that I'm the one who
rejected this marriage proposal.
This way, it'll be more
convenient for you.
He is such a good man.
Truthfully, please do me a favor
and take away Darkness.
Grandchild. My first grandchild.
Am I going to have a cute grandchild?
I've never thought that you two
have this kind of relationship.
I need to be quick.
I need to tell everybody in this town.
-Kazuma and Darkness.
-How could you believe that?
Satou Kazuma.
Is Satou Kazuma here?
(Episode 5:
Servitude for This Masked Knight!)