Capture Quest
Collect Migrating Tuna
Quest Failed
Did you hear? Starting next year,
there won't be any more tuna.
Some crazy mage screwed
up the entire landscape.
I always look forward to tuna season...
Zero points.
What?! Come on, today's Explosion magic
was worth at least worth 120 points!
It was worth nothing,
and that's being generous!
—sion!
You let loose an Explosion
because you thought
a monster was going to take our tuna?!
What's the point if you blow up the fish, too?!
—sion!
Would it kill you to learn some
other advanced magic already?!
Kazuma, that's going too far.
You reek of fish.
As soon as we got on the water,
they were gnawing on you!
Hey, are we in debt again now?
What are we gonna do?!
I don't wanna work part-time anymore!
The arch priest who makes everything a pain.
The arch wizard who makes
everything go to waste.
And the crusader who makes
everything smell like wild game.
It seems my adventure with these useless
comrades is headed for its climax!
Isn't stealing underwear
the only thing he's good at?
He's the kind of scumbag who'd dropkick
a woman without a second thought!
Scumzuma! Scumzuma! Scumzuma!
If this was an anime or a video game,
I'd probably have some
romantic interests by now...
Hey, it's Yunyun.
What's got you so looking so intense?
K-Kazuma-san...
Uh, yeah?
I... I...
I want to have your baby!
And thus begins my popular phase!
God's Blessing on this Wonderful World!
Legend of Crimson
The Movie
Ow!
Why'd you scratch me?!
Could you say that again for me?
I-I said I want to have a baby with you!
I've always wanted to start with a daughter...
N-No! The first child has to be a boy!
I thought she was on the meek side,
but she actually knows how to speak her mind!
What is wrong with you, Yunyun?!
Stop! Chomusuke!
Do you realize what kind of man he is?!
You need to snap out of it!
What in the world's gotten into you?
If Kazuma and I don't have a baby,
the world will... And the Devil King...
The Devil King?
I see. The fate of the world, huh?
It's all right, dear. You can leave
the world and the Devil King to me.
Once we have this baby,
the Devil King will be dealt with
and the world saved, right?
How could I possibly refuse someone in need?
B-But you always try to get out
of monster extermination quests!
Seriously!
Shut it!
Keep your noses out of our
relationship, got it?!
I'm finally in my popular phase! So buzz off!
He's mad at us?
But if an acquaintance of mine is
getting involved with a shady guy,
it's only natural that I'd speak up!
C-Calm down, everyone!
I'm sorry! This is my fault!
Please, just calm down!
Wonderful! Magnificent!
For the first time ever,
I'm glad I came to this world!
And what is with you two?
Do you secretly like me or something?
Are you jealous because of my
romantic developments with Yunyun?
Then you should've just
said so, you tsundere duo!
How dare you?!
Megumin, the Crimson Demon Village...
Why would anyone be jealous about that?!
The Crimson Demon Village
is going to be wiped out!
You must think—
KONOSUBA!
Your tea.
Th-Thank you...
Now, what exactly is going on?
I got this letter from my father...
"By the time you receive this letter,
I will surely have passed on."
It says the Crimson Demon Village is
under attack by the Devil King's forces.
"A fortune-teller saw a future where
the village would be devastated...
But they also saw a light of hope.
That light was the only survivor of
the Crimson Demons, Yunyun."
How is she the only survivor?
Forget that, just keep reading!
But what happened to me?!
"As the only survivor,
she would meet a certain man
in the town of beginners.
This man, though unremarkable
and with no special power,
will become her spouse."
Why'd you look at me after reading that?
And was that seriously all it
took to convince you it was me?!
"Then, as time passes,
the son born to her and this
man would go on a journey.
But the boy did not know...
that he would be the one to avenge
his clan and slay the Devil King..."
O-Our little boy's gonna beat the Devil King?!
Wait a second, Kazuma!
Hey, that doesn't work for me!
That seriously isn't gonna cut it!
I can't wait that long!
I want the Devil King defeated
as soon as possible!
Do you really expect me to
wait until your kid grows up?!
Can't we wrap this up in three years or so?
Because if not, then I want you
to forget about this prophecy!
You seriously want a toddler
to take on the Devil King?
Our village has very skilled
fortune-tellers. So...
I understand. In that case,
you can count on me.
It's to save the world. It must be done.
I-I can't believe you!
You're usually so wishy-washy!
Why the sudden streak of manliness?!
Shut up! Stop talking, boobs!
"Heroic Tales of the
Crimson Demons, Chapter 1."
Boobs?!
It's just having a kid!
Or is that a crime now?!
"Written by Arue."
Arue, you dummy!
Wait, what does that mean?! Explain!
What happens to my kid?! What do I do?!
Do I strip here? Or in my room?!
Arue is a classmate of ours from the
village who wants to be an author.
So it was just a story, then...
But what about that first letter?
I believe this one is genuine.
The Crimson Demons have
been a thorn in the side
of the Devil King's army for a long time.
Wait, hold up! What do I do about
my masculine obligation now?!
Hey, Yunyun?
Aren't we supposed to start a
bittersweet relationship now?
You are not!
Megumin, why are you so calm about this?
Aren't you worried about
your family and classmates?
Th-That's right!
What should we do, Megumin?!
The Crimson Demons are feared
by the Devil King for a reason.
I have a hard time believing our
village will go down without a fight.
Besides, as long as the chief's
daughter, Yunyun, is safe,
we won't die out, even if
the village is destroyed.
So we need only think of it in these terms:
"Our friends from the village will
always live on... in our hearts."
Megumin, you monster!
KONOSU—bahck!
I am so, so sorry!
H-Hey, it's no big deal.
But what are you gonna do?
Well, I think I'll head back to the village.
I have... f-friends... there.
She sure hesitated to use
the word "friends" there.
Everyone, if you'll excuse me.
Teleporting?
You need me to send you near
the Crimson Demon Village, then?
Yeah, the tsundere here feels homesick.
Wh-Who are you calling a tsundere?!
Well, look who it is!
The man with the easiest-to-level class,
who somehow still manages
to be under-leveled!
The girl who's been useless as of late,
except at calling in familial favors!
The small-time priest who's
overflowing with obnoxious light,
and the girl from the joke race who
can only use joke magic! Welcome, all!
I was actually hoping to run into you.
I've drawn up our little contract.
You're really gonna go
through with this, right?
But of course!
I'll buy the rights to Satou Kazuma's intellectual
property library for 300 million eris.
O-Okay!
That said, my debt-ridden fellow,
the deal hasn't been completed yet.
Here you are.
Drink up.
I haven't settled on a craftsman to
build the products you've dreamed up.
Hey, man!
Hands off the merchandise,
you walking blight!
Excuse me?! I thought the
customer was always right!
And I'm a goddess, so I'm extra right!
So show me the respect a goddess deserves!
How dare you try and lecture me
after damaging my merchandise,
you poverty-stricken goddess?!
Wiz, transport them out of here immediately!
So irritating!
Okay, I'll send you to the vicinity
of the Crimson Demon Village now.
I wish you a wonderful
journey and experience.
Teleport!
We're off!
What is it?
Isn't the Crimson Demon Village near...
Emergency quest!!
Survive! Defend yourselves!!
Where the hell did you teleport us, Wiz?!
Hold it right there!
Hey there, handsome!
Wanna have some fun with me?
Why is there a mob of lady orcs?!
Kazuma, there aren't any
male orcs left in the world!
They were wiped out ages ago!
And on the rare occasion that one is born,
they're usually overworked by the females
and die before they can fully mature!
The surviving female orcs are known
for capturing males of other races,
dragging them back to their communities,
and doing all kinds of crazy stuff to them!
They're natural-born predators of men!
Come spend a few days in our village
and you'll have a harem, baby!
We'll give you a taste of heaven on earth!
No, thank you!
I just turned down a lady's
invitation for the first time!
Wait! Orcs are supposed to be the
natural predators of lady knights!
Male orcs! Renowned for their libido,
attacking women the second they see them!
They're all dead.
Darkness!
I'm gonna have your babies!
No, me!
I think I'd like a son first!
And then 60 boys, and 40 girls!
We'll move into a white house by the sea
and spend every day all over each other!
Let me go! I just wanna go home!
Kazuma!
Okay, this won't take long!
Just close your eyes!
Save me, Megumin! Do the thing!
The thing you always do!
I can't use it at this range!
Darkness, stop being depressed!
Can we talk?! Let's talk!
Pillow talk?! I'd love to!
Go ahead and tell me all the dirtiest
fantasies you've kept bottled up!
P-Please stop!
Wait, your name! I don't even
know your name or age yet!
This might be my first time!
Can we maybe start with introductions?!
I'm Satou Kazuma!
I'm Swatti the orc, and
I'm a sweet 16-year-old!
Now, how about you introduce me
to what you've got down here?
Let me meet your big little boy!
But he's so shy!
We made our introductions, so could
we call it a wrap for today?!
Aqua! Aqua, save me!
Bottomless Swamp!
Orcs who live near the Crimson Demon Village!
I'm willing to overlook this
because we're neighbors!
Now, begone!
Yunyun! It's Yunyun!
Kazuma!
Kazuma-san!
Yunyun! Oh, Yunyun!
Thank you so much!
It's all right, don't worry.
Um... Y-You're covering my robe in snot!
Quest Failed
Kazuma was psychologically scarred
Orc (♀)
There, there.
That was scary, wasn't it, Kazuma?
You're okay now, though. It's all right.
What exactly happened
while I was passed out?
We only just started this journey.
I am so grateful, Yunyun.
To be specific, from now on, if anyone
asks me, "Who do you look up to?"
I'm going to answer "Yunyun!" right away.
P-Please don't do that!
It almost sounds sarcastic!
What are you all doing here, anyway?
Megumin, were you worried
about the village after all?
I just remembered some
business I had back home.
You just won't admit it!
You really are worried about everyone!
Aren't you?
Kazuma, would you like to hear an
embarrassing secret about Yunyun?
We Crimson Demons are born with
a tattoo somewhere on our bodies.
And in the case of Yunyun,
if you can believe it...
Hey, cut it out!
How do you even know where my tattoo is?!
You can't use your joke Explosion
magic around here, anyway!
So I can easily restrain you if I have to!
Aqua, I need support magic.
I think this girl needs to
be taught a painful lesson.
Y-You coward!
You never play fair, Megumin!
Never once, ever!
Hey, over here! I hear human voices!
Do you suppose they're with
the Devil King's army?
This is because of your short
temper and shouting, Yunyun!
But Megumin, you've got
a shorter fuse than me!
Say that again!
Enough, you two!
If you're too loud, they'll find us.
Kazuma, say something!
Hey, who gives a damn?!
Tell me where Yunyun's tattoo is!
Found them! They're over here!
They were hiding in the bushes!
What in the world is wrong with you?!
There's even some Crimson Demon brats!
Well, if it isn't a bunch of discount,
wannabe demons!
Oh, my!
What might a bunch of ogre-looking wash-outs
who couldn't even cut it as
lesser demons want with us?
Look, I'll let you walk away
this one time, so scram.
Go on, get!
Hey, priest lady, what gives?
The Crimson Demons put us through hell,
and you've got two of them!
You really think we're
gonna just let them walk?!
I seem to recall you saying
my magic is a joke.
Perhaps I should remind you
of just how serious it can be.
W-Wait a second... You're not gonna...
Explosion!
Did you see that?!
My ultimate spell, Explosion magic!
Well, would you still call that a joke spell?!
How about it, Kazuma?!
What score would you give that Explosion?!
You get negative 90 points!
What now?! Because we're in no
condition to carry you away now!
H-H-Holy crap, that was scary...
But now my reinforcements are here.
Say your prayers, people!
Time to cry and beg for mercy,
not that it's gonna help!
Not even a scrap of flesh will remain!
The dark flame born from my
ebon heart will scorch you!
Slumber for eternity in the
frozen embrace of my ice!
I... kill... you.
Now... it is born!
Aw, crap!
Light of Saber!
...Saber!
...ber!
Wait, what happened to the dark
flames and frozen embraces?
No doubt about it, though.
Those red eyes...
We heard an explosion in the distance...
and here we find Megumin and Yunyun.
We were told that the village
might be in danger.
I'm curious, Megumin. Are these
people your adventuring party?
I am called Bukkororii!
The son of the foremost cobbler
among the Crimson Demons!
Arch wizard, and wielder of advanced magic!
Hey there. I'm called Satou Kazuma.
From my home in Axel,
I have mastered countless skills
and used them to battle
the Devil King's generals.
No outsider has been able to
properly return a greeting before!
Megumin, your friends seem really nice.
The village is still some distance away.
Let us take you there.
Teleport!
Welcome to the
Crimson Demon Village, outsiders.
And it's good to have you
back, Megumin, Yunyun.
D-Dad? Could you repeat that?
That was just me sending you an update!
Uh, sir, what exactly do you mean?
But it said, "By the time you receive
this letter, I will surely have passed on."
That's the traditional Crimson Demon greeting!
But you said you wouldn't be able
to destroy the Devil King's fortress!
Yeah.
The village can't decide whether to destroy
it or leave it as a tourist attraction.
Yunyun, can I punch your dad in the face?
Go ahead.
Yunyun?!
If the Devil King's army is nearby,
then is a general...
Sure, there's one with them.
Strong with magic, I believe.
Should be showing up anytime now.
Devil King Army alert.
Anyone available, please assemble
at the entrance to the village.
The enemy force numbers around 1,000.
A thousand?!
Devil King Forces Approaching!
Sylvia-sama! Retreat!
You have to survive,
even if the rest of us don't!
Damn it! Damn it!
If we could just get close enough—
I said we never should've
attacked the Crimson Demons!
Nobody ever listens to me!
Suck on this boulder!
Holy crap...
This is... so impressive, it's freaky, honestly.
What do you think?
We've been wondering if the light
show might attract tourists!
KONOSUBA...
So, those are real Crimson Demons, huh?
When you put it that way, it makes
it sound like you know a fake one.
Why don't you explain exactly
what you mean by that?
Hey, Megumin, is that your stable?
That's not a stable. It's the house.
Is this your little sister, Megumin?
She's pretty cute!
It's like having a mini Megumin!
Hey, want some candy?
I'm back, Komekko.
Dad! Megumin's back, and she's snared a man!
Hey, little missy!
Could we perhaps discuss this?!
KONOSUBA!
What do I do?
The one who's supposed to smooth
a situation like this over is...
Damn you!
Look at this!
See how the mug moves around
once I've flipped it over?
Oh, wow! How'd you do it?!
How are you doing that?
It's a magnet!
It must be some kind of magnet!
No, there are no magnets or magic involved!
So...
What exactly is the nature of your
relationship with our daughter?
Like I've been saying, we're just frie—
Honey!
Stop! No more flipping
the table and breaking it!
We don't have that kind of money! Stop!
Forgive me. I lost my composure.
It's just that you kept insisting so
shamelessly that you're only friends...
This isn't much, but here...
Dear, I believe Kazuma-san
meant to give this to me.
Oh, really? After all that bluster just now,
you're being polite enough
to call him Kazuma-san?
You really shouldn't. It's embarrassing.
This is going to be our dinner tonight.
I'm not going to let you
snack on it with your booze.
Ma'am, those are just dumplings...
They don't make much of
a snack, let alone a meal.
Hey, is this the kind of food
that actually fills you up,
instead of the watery rice
porridge we usually eat?!
It really isn't much, but here...
We're so glad to have you, Kazuma-san!
Dear, bring out some of the good tea!
We only have one type of tea, honey.
KONOSUBA!
I don't care what you feed us!
You can't have Komekko!
I don't want her!
That's not what I'm trying to do!
Komekko, you can have the rest.
I can?! Yay!
You seem nice enough, so I won't object...
But I really think you should pay off
your debts before taking in our daughter.
I just told you that we're only friends!
But in her letters...
Can I ask you what she wrote, exactly?
Well, for starters...
You left her covered in a sticky
fluid and made sport of her.
When she depleted her magic power,
you carried her on your back while
pressing her chest against you.
You bathed together.
As she napped innocently on the sofa,
you stared up her skirt while sitting
across from her and holding your knees.
You feed Chomusuke and say,
"This is what I want. Bring me more of this!
Then I'll feed you even more!"
while showing her some underwear...
I am so sorry!
But in spite of it all, she says
you're an important friend...
And that even if you're a debt-ridden,
perverted foul-mouth
without a lick of sense,
you'd die without her, so she'll stay with you.
Considering she said all that, I'm sure
there's more to you than it seems.
There are parts of that I'd argue against,
but being called an important
friend does make me kind of happy.
Since you're in the same party as her,
we'd love to help you out...
No, it's all right! I'm on the verge
of making a fair bit of money.
Oh? Exactly how much are we talking?
I think it was 300 million eris.
300 million?!
Huh? Should I have not said that?
I've got a great idea, Kazuma-san!
You should spend the night here!
As my daughter's comrade
and friend, it's only natural!
I mean, as an adventurer, you don't
have a home of your own, right?!
N-No, I actually have a mansion in Axel...
Mansion?!
The second I brought up the
mansion and the 300 million,
the reception got a lot warmer...
But this place seems pretty safe,
so once Megumin's rested up,
we should get out of here
before we get caught up in any trouble.
How can you suggest such a thing?!
Don't you care what happens
to your daughter?!
It's perfectly fine.
She's old enough to get married,
and Kazuma-san is an adult
with good judgment.
Even if something were to happen...
What are you—
Sleep.
She actually did it!
Is this...
Oh, Kazuma-san. All done with the bath?
Everyone's already asleep,
so would you help me move
them into their rooms?
Well, enjoy yourselves!
This is no time to be enchanted!
I think those orcs might
have traumatized me...
I'm gonna need some emotional care from
those nice succubi when I get back to Axel.
Lock.
I know I slipped up by talking
about the money that was coming in,
but this lady is pretty intense...
Hang on a sec.
Aqua got hammered and fell asleep,
and Hyoizaburo-san and Darkness
were both put to sleep by her mom!
The door's been locked
from outside with magic!
No one can get in here, and I can't get out!
What a setup!
There's only one futon. It's spring,
but nights are still cold.
If I sleep without any cover,
I might get sick.
And what if it develops into pneumonia?
Given these factors, there should be no
problem with me sleeping next to Megumin.
But if I made a move on her while
she was sleeping so peacefully,
that'd rob me of any pretense
that I could use to deny
when Darkness or Aqua call
me a creep or a scumbag!
I'm a gentlemen! That's not like me!
However, her parents have
signed off on this situation.
I bet if Megumin sued me, I could win!
Wait, could I?
Damn it! I should have
studied up more on law!
If I had known this would happen, I would've!
Wait, that's not it!
What am I, stupid?!
This isn't about getting sued!
My entire perspective is off-base!
No good. I think the situation
has me all mixed up.
Calm down! Settle yourself, Satou Kazuma!
Let's calm down and think this through.
Spring or not, it's cold at night.
Too cold to think straight.
First, let's crawl into
the futon and calm down!
Wait, no! What a devious trap I've fallen for!
Without realizing it, I've ended
up sleeping next to Megumin!
Let's say I panic and jump out of the futon.
Wouldn't that be the exact
moment that she'd wake up?!
Exactly! The kind of situation where
I get punished no matter what I do!
If that happens, even if I say, "I didn't do
anything!" or "It was your parents' idea!"
I could have the best excuses in
the world, and no one would care!
Oh, bitter injustice!
It's a false accusation, that's what it is.
And if that's going to be how things
turn out, no matter what I do...
I may as well turn it around and remove
the "false" part of the equation.
You can't put me in the same futon as a
beautiful girl and expect nothing to happen.
More than anything, this situation
was cooked up by Megumin's mother.
It's fine! I can win!
In this kind of situation, I bet I could
even beat Sena in a court of law!
Good morning.
Oh... good morning.
Uh, how long was I asleep?
About eight hours?
I see...
And... why am I sleeping
in the same futon as you?
C'mon, don't make me spell it out.
Spell what out?!
Hey, don't flip the cover up. It's cold.
I just woke up in my old room next
to you, Kazuma! What happened?!
Come on, you really think
I'd try to pull something?
I haven't up until now, have I?
That's a good point. Sorry.
I think I was a bit confused,
since I just woke up...
You're not the kind of person who would
take advantage of a situation like this.
Of course not!
I'll have you know your mom locked
the door and trapped me in here!
She did?! Honestly...
That being the case, saddle up!
It's cold, so into the futon with you!
It's fine! I won't do! A thing!
You won't?
You really won't do... anything?
Even though we're all alone...
Say what?
I-Is she saying I should try something?
Is this really my popular phase?!
Fool! I'm obviously gonna try
something if we're all alone!
I've even got your parents' approval!
You idiot! I suspected as much!
I'm going to spend the
night at Yunyun's house!
Damn you! You tricked me!
Death to perverts!
Die, die, die, die, die!
Megumin, Megumin!
Could you show us the sights around here?
That's a good idea.
Why don't we have a nice, leisurely day,
and then stay one more night?
Yay!
I'm going to have Megumin show me around.
What are you going to do, Kreeperma-san?
Good question. Maybe I'll join...
Wait. What did you just call me?
Did I say something strange?
No... Maybe I imagined it?
Well, whatever. What about you, Darkness?
There's a place I'd like to visit.
You and the others should enjoy
your sightseeing, Kazutrash.
Okay, sounds— Wait, what did you just say?
So I'll be showing Aqua
and Kursedma around, then?
There are lots of things to see in town—
Hang on a second!
Is something wrong, Kazuma-san-who-tried-to-
mess-with-Megumin-while-she-was-sleeping?
I'm sorry.
This is the mysterious facility where the
Crimson Demons' natural enemy is sealed away.
What do you mean, mysterious facility?
Just what I said. It's a mysterious facility.
No one knows what else is inside,
who built it, or for what reason.
Hey, Megumin.
Are there any other places with
cool things hidden inside?
Well, there was a tomb where
an evil god was sealed away,
and a piece of land where a
nameless goddess was sealed away,
but eventually, they ended up being released.
Are you guys bad at keeping
things sealed or what?!
Well, if it isn't Megumin!
You're back in town?
Are these folks from out of town?
Does he have... problems with outsiders?
I am called Cheekera! Arch wizard
and wielder of advanced magic!
And owner of the foremost clothing
store among the Crimson Demons!
Welcome, folks! It's been a while
since I've had outsiders in the shop.
Having the foremost store
is pretty impressive!
Well, this is also the only
clothing store in the village.
Are you mocking us?!
I was actually hoping to
replace my current robe.
Do you have another just like this?
All of them?
Wow, our little Megumin's gone all bourgeois!
I'm honestly surprised the village
hasn't heard of my exploits yet!
And since the robes are
what I wear into action,
it can't hurt to have a few
more in my wardrobe.
That being said, future millionaire
Kazuma, lend me some money.
You...
I mean, fine, but...
Thank you very much!
Hey...
What is it?
Isn't this...
I mean, what the hell?
You're hanging clothes from that?
Oh, sir, do you recognize it?
This is the clothes-drying pole that's been
passed down through my family for ages.
It never rusts, so it's super handy.
That's pretty clearly a rifle.
That's what I thought.
What is up with this village?
Kazuma! Aqua!
Now that you know the charms
of the Crimson Demon Village,
allow me to show you even finer splendor!
Welcome...
to our magic academy, the Red Prison!
W-Welcome...
What're you doing here, Yunyun?
When I stayed over at her house last night,
the friendless wonder seemed lonely,
so I invited her to come along.
I-I-I never said I was lonely!
You even dug out your old uniform.
Why try and hide it?
So this is your uniform? It's cute!
Isn't it, though?!
It's only natural that I get changed
to show you around our
distinguished magical academy!
I bet you just wanted to wear it
because you felt nostalgic.
Kazuma always gets prickly when
the subject of school comes up.
He's probably still bitter
about not fitting in.
Hey, cut it out! That's a
confidentiality violation!
I am called Arue...
The most voluptuous among the
Crimson Demons, and a future author!
I am called Funifura!
The foremost among Crimson Demons
who love their brothers,
known for her brother complex!
I am called Dodonko!
Foremost among the Crimson Demons at...
At... what was it again?
You've got a brother complex, huh?
I-I just don't have a cool nickname yet!
Arue... Dodonko, Funikura.
It's Funifura! You did that on purpose!
You totally did, didn't you?!
We heard you were back in town.
Who're they?
Classmates from when we
attended the magic academy.
Welcome home. I'm glad to
see you made it back safely.
People might believe the things you write,
so please don't send "letters"
like that anymore.
And you people are the members
of Yunyun's party?
I'm surprised you actually exist!
Yunyun's party, I mean.
L-Let me introduce you!
Th-This guy is a rookie adventurer,
and the girl is an arch priest!
There's also a very durable lady
who's not with us at the moment!
And Megumin was sad on her own,
so we recently invited her to join us!
That sounds like a lovely party.
Yunyun's not actually a member of
the party, but she helps us out a lot,
despite not being a member!
Uh...
Yes, in spite of her not being a member.
We figured.
I've given Yunyun the nickname
"frog slayer" in my heart.
What are you talking about?
Light of Saber!
Come on, remember how she
took out those Giant Toads
with that sparkly sword-like spell?
Isn't that...
That's an actual advanced spell.
Yunyun, I thought you could
only do intermediate magic!
She picked it up at an awkward time,
so she wasn't able to learn
advanced magic before graduation.
C-Come on, it's not like I needed to know it.
What's wrong, Kazuma? Are you still torn
up about not having friends in school?
That's not it!
I was just wondering about Yunyun.
You mean what they said earlier?
I thought Crimson Demons were a bunch of
OP weirdos who all used advanced magic.
Well...
When I was a student, in order
to learn Explosion magic,
I was storing up my skill points.
I endured it day after day,
to make sure I could someday
learn Explosion magic.
But one day...
Give me my food back!
Komekko!
To save Komekko when she
was attacked by monsters,
Yunyun used her own points in
order to learn intermediate magic,
while I was hesitating...
You mean she covered for you
so you could learn Explosion magic?
Not that I asked her to, but yes.
Well, she's a more established
mage than you are now,
so it worked out all right!
True enough.
How dare you?!
The Devil King's forces have appeared!!
Emergency Quest
What is it with this woman?!
What is she trying to do?!
Lady Sylvia! There's no telling
what she's after! Please, stand back!
She's a real freak! Her attacks are
worthless, but she's sturdy as they come!
As long as there is light in my eyes,
you will not pass!
Darkness! Good job hanging in there!
We brought help from the village!
K-Kazuma? You're already here?
I was sad that only female orcs are left,
so I came here to see what I could find,
and even the Devil King's general is a woman!
What is wrong with this journey?!
Could you shut up for a second?!
You're ruining that impressive performance!
I see. Buying time until
your allies arrived, then?
From the way you endured those attacks,
you must be a fairly high-level crusader.
Was not being able to land
any attacks part of your act?
I-I suppose there's no point
in maintaining the facade...
Glance...
Look, you're Sylvia, right?
That crusader is an accomplished warrior
who fought the Devil King's general, Vanir!
Vanir?!
I heard he never returned
from the town of Axel...
Was that because of you people?
Yeah! Megumin here finished him off.
Vanir-sama is dead?!
That's awesome!
And that's not all!
The Dullahan, Verdia,
and Hans the Deadly Poison...
And even the mobile fortress, Destroyer.
The four of us took them all down.
Verdia and Hans, too?!
But when I think about how
we lost contact with Hans
after he infiltrated Arcanretia,
it seems plausible.
I take it you're the leader?
Why don't you tell me your name?
M-My name?
It's Mitsurugi.
Mitsurugi Kyouya. Remember it.
Someone just chickened out.
He must've been feeling cocky with all
these Crimson Demons backing him up.
So you're Mitsurugi of the Cursed Sword...
I didn't expect to encounter
such a powerful party.
Taking you down right here with
the Crimson Demons' help
wouldn't be much of an accomplishment.
I appreciate that, Mitsurugi.
Let's meet again. When we do,
we'll see who comes out on top.
Retreat!
Don't let them escape! Lightning Strike!
Light of Saber!
Time to test my magic on you all!
I should buy Mitsurugi some
bubbly next time I see him.
Good morning.
Did you get a good night's rest?
Good... morn...ing.
Did you finally cross the line?!
You beast! Kazuma, you beast!
Dummy.
I was just holding your
hand because it's cold.
R-Really?
I suppose I got the wrong idea.
I'm sorry.
H-Hey, it's fine.
But it's about time you
did seriously thank me.
I'm always cleaning up
after you guys, after all.
Thanking you?
You've got a point.
Back then, you accepted an aimless wizard
who could only cast
Explosion magic. Thank you.
You always carry me home on your back
when I can't move after
casting it. Thank you.
I always cause so much trouble,
but you keep me in the party. Thank you.
I was just thanking you.
Why are you embarrassed when
you're the one who demanded it?
O-Oh...
Well, in spite of it all,
you guys do help out a lot.
To put it in your terms...
I am called Satou Kazuma!
Axel's weakest adventurer,
and foremost at getting into trouble!
He who will obtain the wealth to spend
his days having fun with the rest of you!
And I'm looking forward to it.
So am I. Here's to a bright future.
I-It really is cold today.
As if we're trapped... in... ice...
Kazuma, care to explain what this is?
I think maybe there was a freak blizzard
that froze the window
shut before blowing away.
Let me out! Let me out, please!
Open! Open! Open up, now!
Mom! Kazuma froze the window shut!
Look, I'm sorry, and I'm
not gonna do anything!
It's cold, so let's go to bed.
I want my gratitude back!
Look, I'm sorry. My bad.
I'm really regretting all
those nice things I said.
And after she was the one who held my hand.
Feels like we're an old couple in a cold stretch.
Freeze...
Did you just use ice magic again?!
Do you want me to cling to you that badly?!
H-Hey! If you start clinging
to me like that...
I can see why Darkness says that
every time you've had a chance
to do something with her,
you laugh it off and never do anything.
You really are a wimp.
Huh?
Is this... Does Megumin...
Is she open to the idea?!
This really is my popular phase!
The Devil King Army is attacking!
They've already breached the village!
Yeah, that's what I figured.
How dare you interrupt just
when it was getting good?!
What the hell, man?!
You ever think about the trouble
you cause other people, dumbass?!
You want an ass whooping?!
I'm sorry!
Wait, no!
I didn't think I'd run into you out here.
Oh, dear!
Did I interrupt something?
No!
Hell yeah, you did!
Do you know how late it is?
Could you quiet down?
Aqua! One of the Devil King's
generals is out here!
Get Megumin's parents!
Okay!
You better not expect any
mercy just because you're hot!
In the name of true gender equality,
I will dropkick any rotten
woman who deserves it!
Are you actually the famous Mitsurugi?
You mean to tell me this little
thing is the Cursed Sword Gram?
It's Chunchunmaru.
I said that sword's name is Chunchunmaru.
Please don't compare it to some cursed
sword nobody's heard of, like Gram!
You're not Mitsurugi, are you?
My name is Satou Kazuma!
I thought if you people knew my name,
you'd put a bounty on my head or something!
I think I like you!
Kazuma!
You! The people of this house have left
to gather the other Crimson Demons!
Surrender now!
Settle down, now.
Thank you very—
Wait, no, that's wrong! This is a trap.
I shouldn't be happy just because
sh'es exposing skin, busty,
and a statuesque beauty in spite of
her huge frame thank you very much!
I'll get you out of there, Kazuma!
You'll blow Kazuma away, too,
if you use Explosion magic!
I'm taking him as a hostage.
Wait! If you need a hostage, take me!
You're a naughty one, aren't you?
What has been up with me lately?
It starts with Yunyun saying
she wants to have my baby,
then the orcs, Megumin, and now Sylvia...
Even if the orcs weren't really a positive.
But this is the kind of luck where
I'd expect some kind of backlash.
Have I actually entered a popular phase?
Or has my high luck stat, my only
saving grace, kicked into overdrive?
Now, sweetie, stop breathing so heavily...
You're heating me up.
Sacred Exorcism!
A sneak attack...
But I've got bad news.
I'm not a pure demon,
so it's not going to kill me.
I am called Sylvia!
I am the chief of the Enhanced
Monster Development Bureau,
she who has synthesized
and modified her own body!
Yes, Sylvia, the Growth Chimera!
And I'm taking this boy with me!
Let's become one again.
Kazuma!
Did... Did he just let himself be taken?
Of course not.
This is strange. It's such a perfect fit,
and I feel so safe.
Like I've finally found the sanctuary
I've been searching for.
Hold on, Kazuma! I'll get you out of there!
I'd rather you didn't.
I said I'd rather you didn't.
You guys have been kind of taking
me for granted lately, haven't you?
See, Sylvia-san here...
She actually appreciates me.
It's enough to make me...
defect to the Devil King's army.
So apologize!
It's about time I got an apology,
since I always try so hard for you all!
E-Enough with the jokes, Kazuma...
There's a time and place for these things.
T-True enough, you have
accomplished some great feats.
When we get back to Axel, I'll talk to
my father about giving you a medal...
I want sincerity!
Stop trying to buy me off with stuff!
I want genuine contrition!
Just look at what's happening here.
Miss Sylvia of the Devil King's army is
giving me the billowy pillowy treatment!
Darkness! What is your greatest strength?
Tell me! Go on, spit it out!
M-My defensive strength?
Obviously not!
Your only strength is your
needlessy seductive body
that brings men to their knees!
How can you be so oblivious?!
I-I don't seduce anybody!
You clearly do!
Your body is luscious,
and for no good reason!
What you don't realize is that my high
luck stat is at its apex tonight!
I've never been a bigger hit with the chicks!
Now apologize!
Give me a proper apology so I
don't waltz off with Sylvia-san,
thanks to my awesome popular phase!
You are just delightful.
But don't be too harsh on the ladies, okay?
I need to teach you how to
understand women a bit better.
As if a demonic beast could
understand how human women feel...
Well, of course I can understand
how they feel. Men and women.
Just what I'd expect from a demonic beauty.
She's got bewitching charisma that
lets her understand men and women!
After all, I'm partially a man myself.
Say that again?
Oh, you didn't hear me?
I'm a chimera, after all.
Even these boobs you're so fond of
were something I added to my body.
K-Kazuma... s-stay calm...
I-It's fine! Don't panic! Don't panic.
You really are a fine man, though.
Just holding you like this has my breasts
and lower body feeling all tingly!
Sylvia-san! Sylvia-san!
Why do I feel something
pressing into my butt?
Because something is!
Something is! Something is! Something is!
No!
Quest Failed
Orc (♀)
Kazuma was psychologically scarred
Sylvia (♂)
Cut it out! Get your dick
off of me! You wanna die?!
Settle down!
You don't have to worry.
I'm not going to try anything.
I managed to shake the others off
my tail, so you're free to go.
Where are we?
This is the Crimson Demon Village's
underground storage facility.
My objective is to find the ancient
magic weapon that's hidden here.
A magic weapon?
The Mage Killer.
It can neutralize any magic...
A perfect counter to the Crimson Demons.
Something like that is down here?
I've finally gotten this close.
The barrier breaker isn't working?
What exactly is this?
It's not sealed with magic?
Are those... controller inputs?
You can read that ancient text?!
Nah, I think they just used a famous
cheat code as the password for the—
You're even better than I'd hoped.
I'm still an adventurer, y'know!
Don't expect me to give in that easily!
There's more to getting someone to talk
than threats and violence, you know.
You'll find my technique
is on par with a succubus.
I wonder how much ecstasy you'll be able to—
Up, up, down, down, left, right,
left, right! There you go!
Do the things you do not bother you?
Not that it matters. Now the weapon is mine.
Crap.
I got so anxious, I put the password in.
Still...
It's so dark. I can't see a thing.
I think she might be taking me too lightly
just because I don't have a weapon.
Hey, do you have anything
I can use for light?
Hey! What do you think you're—
Up, up, down, down, left, right,
left, right, and away you go!
Hey, you, stop that! Hold it right there!
Wait, damn it!
KONOSUBA...
Kazuma! Are you all right?
Where's Sylvia?
I managed to trap Sylvia in here
with a bit of skillful deceit.
Hey, damn it!
Open this door right now!
You hear me?!
If we leave her in there for a month
or so, she's bound to quiet down.
(Heavy breathing)
Ah! <3
A Devil King general...
killed by starvation?
It hurts!
Ow, ow, ow!
Oh!
Well done, outsider!
My breasts!
I think my boobies
are stuck in the door!
You managed to capture Sylvia,
after she evaded us every time!
Ah!
I can't move!
Come on, Satou Kazuma.
Isn't there some kind of scary
weapon sealed in this place?
Won't you please open the door?
Even we couldn't figure out
how to use it. It'll be fine.
Hahh! Hahh!
Aw, come on!
Say something, damn it!
If Sylvia is able to activate the weapon,
At least respond, you piece of crap!
I'll run a lap around the village
while doing a handstand!
Because if you're not gonna poke at me,
Whoa, don't set flags!
I'm gonna poke you hard, damn it!
Come on, what are you worried about, Kazuma?
You hear me?!
You defeated one of
the Devil King's generals!
I am going
to poke you!
You basically did it by yourself this time,
but since we're a party,
we split the reward, right?
What should I buy when we get back to Axel?
Why do you do this every damn time?!
We need to get out of here, fast!
Did you think I was just going
to take the weapon with me?
This is my power.
I can assimilate anything into
my body, weapons or otherwise!
My name is Sylvia!
Sylvia the Growth Chimera,
who has obtained ultimate power!
K-K-Kazuma, this is bad!
That's the Mage Killer!
Let's run! We need to get out of here, fast!
Abandon the village! It's doomed!
We've had our ups and downs,
but I have this power because of you.
So I'll spare you.
You can stand there and watch as
I wipe this village off the map!
Hey, look!
Isn't that the legendary Mage Killer?!
Time for some well-deserved payback!
It's Sylvia-sama!
Sylvia-sama managed to get
a hold of the Mage Killer!
Sylvia! Sylvia!
I never thought the seal would be broken...
Village Chief!
Oh, our visitors.
It's a shame this happened
while you were here.
I-It's okay...
I'm so sorry. It was me
who let that thing out!
The village... is burning.
I-Is there seriously nothing we can do?
The Mage Killer does have...
a secret countermeasure.
There are ruins with an inscription that
no one has been able to decipher...
There are?!
O-Okay, let's head there right now!
What did she hit?!
That was near your house!
Komekko's there!
Megumin, take Kazuma and
the others to those ruins!
Don't worry. I'll protect your family.
That's a knight's duty, right?
Please, save Komekko.
Okay, this is do-or-die. Let's go!
"Do-or-die," eh?
For outsiders, you definitely
understand our culture!
Not bad. If anything,
things like this are our style!
All right, why don't we show her what
we can do to defend the village?
Yeah!
I think this disaster might be the kind
of thing they look forward to...
Hey, sorry to interrupt during the big
speeches, but I don't like any of this.
My job is providing support
from a safe position.
Stop whining and move!
You're in this party, too!
No!
KONOSUBA!
Here we are, Vanir-san.
I'm sure the craftsman I know can help you!
That confidence only makes me anxious,
considering it's coming from you.
It'll be fine!
He's very skill—
This is screwed up.
Kazuma, this way!
Hey...
This is Japanese!
Japa... what?
Uh, don't worry about it.
"I now leave this record
of what has transpired.
One day, the king trampled
into my paradise
demanding a weapon that
could defeat the Devil King."
But nothing can be gained from war...
I tried to brush it off with that,
but a lady researcher slapped me.
I kinda think I already contributed
enough to this country
using the cheat ability I got
when I came to this world!
I'm all out of ideas!
I managed to come up with a weapon
to deal with the Devil King.
I say that, but they're just
humans that I modified...
Master, please give us our new names.
Master who?
Boy, they're really acting the part.
Between asking for red eyes and wanting
identifying numbers on each of their bodies...
Is everyone in this country a nutcase?
I randomly came up with
the name "Crimson Demons,"
and they absolutely loved it for some reason!
Kazuma, what are you doing?!
Take your hands off my ears!
The Crimson Demons found out about the
Mage Killer that I made a prototype of,
and they called it "our natural enemy!"
Fight sorcerer technology
with sorcerer technology.
We desire a deterrent to
prevent it from running amok.
I honestly don't hate their whole
"pretentious but nerdy" aesthetic.
For something I threw together, this
deterrent turned out pretty awesome!
It's only about as big
as a clothes-drying pole,
but it's got enough firepower
to wreck the planet!
I can't think of a better name,
so I'll just call it the Railgun (TBD), for now.
Baby!
What the hell do you mean, Railgun (TBD)?!
I feel like... I should apologize.
Quit sending dumbasses into this world!
Between the Destroyer and the Mage Killer,
do you realize how many times
this guy has screwed up?!
What did it say?!
Well, do you?!
They took a dangerous weapon
and used it for laundry!
Is there something wrong
with the Crimson Demons?!
Burn! Burn!
Let this village of lunatics
be reduced to ash!
Sylvia-sama! You look incredible!
So cool!
Stylish!
You boys...
I'm sorry you had it so rough until now.
I only made it this far because of you all.
Thank you! You're the best
army I could've asked for!
We'll follow you wherever
you lead us, Sylvia-sama!
Sylvia! Sylvia!
This ends now!
I am called Hiropon!
The chief of this village,
and he who leads the Crimson Demons!
I am called Pucchin! The foremost
educator among the Crimson Demons,
and he who will one day be headmaster!
I am called Shikobei! The foremost
fisherman among the Crimson Demons,
and he who will one day catch a kraken!
I am called Chakamiya!
Owner of the foremost bakery
among the Crimson Demons,
and master of yeast!
I am called—
Burning Flash!
Sylvia-sama!
It seems...
...this won't be that easy.
Hey! You didn't even get rid of the goblins!
This magic weapon is magnificent.
The Crimson Demons will be destroyed
by the very power they've safeguarded!
Now, despair...
Ancient Dispel!
That scared me!
What the heck did she do?
Don't stop now! Keep lighting her up!
Diabolic flames, run wild! Inferno!
Our magic...
It's not casting!
W-We can't teleport, either!
This is bad! Run for it!
We can't take on the Mage Killer after all!
If the Crimson Demons are just a
bunch of oafs without their magic...
We've got them now!
Get your scrawny butts back here!
Hurry!
Hey, slow down!
Funifura!
Whatever's the matter, ladies?
How unlucky for you. If you were
cute boys, I might've spared you...
But your people have made a
mockery of us for too long.
Oh, no!
Light of Saber!
You've done enough,
Devil King Army General Sylvia!
That's the chief's daughter!
Yunyun?!
Idiot! What are you doing?!
I'm can't abandon my friends.
Yunyun...
I am called Yunyun!
Arch wizard, and wielder of advanced magic!
The foremost mage among the Crimson Demons,
and future leader of this village!
My daughter!
She used to act so embarrassed
about giving her introduction...
That's my student!
I'm the one who taught her!
Yunyun!
You can do it!
Yunyun! Yunyun!
Yunyun!
I challenge you to a duel, Sylvia!
If you want to destroy the village,
you'll have to beat me first!
How adorable.
But I actually hate cute
young things like you!
My crimson eyes will overlook no evil!
Yunyun!
That is my crimson fate!
The scope is set!
Yay! Yay!
Sacred Exorcism! Sacred Exorcism!
Sacred Exorcism!
We made it in time!
Time to put an end to this!
Huh, and I thought it was just
a pole for hanging clothes.
So that's my son-in-law...
Sylvia... It's been fun,
but this is goodbye!
Snipe.
What the hell?! It's broken!
Here, let me see.
With things like this, if you just smack it...
Stop it!
Hey, I charged that thing with
plenty of magic power! What gives?
I need to hit it!
Shut up! We need to help Yunyun
before she's really in trouble!
We need to hit it!
And now, the star arrives!
F-Forgive me! Just forget I said anything!
Not happening!
I am called Megumin!
I am supreme and almighty in my dominion!
She who calls down the power
of the very heavens themselves!
Stop using that joke magic!
You're old enough to know better!
Sorry! I'm so sorry!
It comes! It comes! The hordes of flame...
Now display your force, by my command!
Explosion!
Well, as a goddess,
I have an obligation to protect
Komekko's young life,
so I'm going to run off.
Hey, it's glowing now.
It wasn't broken after all!
It just didn't have enough magic power!
Seems like you've got some
kind of scheme in mind.
Sylvia!
Remember my name!
And when you're on the other side,
tell your buddies I said hi!
I am Sa—
Boom!
Wha...
A-Am I... done?
I am called Komekko!
The foremost lovable little sister
among the Crimson Demons!
And she who is stronger
than a Devil King general!
KONOSUBA.
What happened to me?
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Come on! Come join us!
I'm all clean now.
Verdia and Hans?!
No! Is this place—
Come on. Come with us, and we can
all hang out like we used to.
Soap, detergent, soap,
detergent, soap, detergent...
No! I don't want this!
I don't wanna go to the other side!
Come... with us...
That was a brutal battle.
I swear to never hurt another person again.
Seriously, stop saying stuff that sets flags!
Life...
Join us... Come with us!
I'm all clean now...
Life!
What is that?!
Isn't that the slime we fought before?!
And over there...
The Dullahan!
I won't let it end like this!
My life has only just begun!
I'm going to continue living!
Crap, crap, crap, crap!
Slow down! Kazuma-san, wait for me!
Faster! You need to run faster!
Megumin, stop squirming!
She revived?!
What the hell is that?!
My soul nearly passed on...
I'm going to crush all of you!
Cursed Crystal Prison!
K-Kazuma-san, what in the world is going on?
Wiz?! What are you doing here?
My boy, who is so gifted in
living a cowardly life...
In order to produce your
designs as merchandise,
we came to visit a craftsman in
this village, but it seems...
You've unleashed a magical weapon
out of fear for your own life?
Wha?!
You can't hide the truth from
a demon that reads minds.
That said, if the village is destroyed,
our arrangement can't be completed...
My, my, what a mess.
Hey! I thought you were going to use
your stolen ideas to make us all rich?!
Wiz?! And Vanir?!
Hello again, Sylvia-san.
Can I convince you to take
a diplomatic approach here?
Hell no!
The Devil King's forces learning of my
survival would be more trouble than I'd like...
You damned traitors!
I don't understand what just happened,
other than you screwed up again, Kazuma!
Well, I'm not going back
to sleeping in stables!
After the taste of luxury I've had,
I can't go back to living where I work!
Sylvia-san! I can't believe you'd turn
yourself into... that! Seriously!
I'm so sure, Wiz!
Someone like you could never understand
what it's like for those
of us on the front lines!
The way you ditz through life,
nothing ever goes wrong!
It pisses me off!
Kazuma, don't you have some kind of plan?!
Also, I demand you return my Explosion.
Is now really the time?!
She's fighting Wiz and Vanir
and still has the edge!
Damn it!
My magic...
It seems physical damage
isn't doing much, either.
How is she so strong?! It's totally unfair!
Damn it! Maybe there's a weakness? Like what?!
Like... like... like...
Like? Like...
Like? Like... My popular phase?
Kazuma?
Damn it, fine!
Traitors deserve death.
You okay, Wiz?!
Kazuma-san!
The real battle starts now!
The pervert knight with the terrible attacks!
What's become of her?
You! Vanir, the Mind-Reading Demon!
We meet again, Verdia the Hero Slayer.
What's going on?
What are they planning to do?
Hey, look!
Megumin?!
Yunyun?!
Those two can't even use Teleport!
Could it be...
They intend to die.
What?!
My daughter... You can't die, Megumin!
Megumin! Yunyun!
Everyone!
I need your help!
Blessing. Blessing. Blessing.
I've known you for a while now, Kazuma-san,
and you never run out of crazy ideas.
It'll be fine.
I've got a goddess on my side, right?
Give me all you've got, partner!
Leave it to me!
Is this...
She's a dark one...
But... twists like this are kind of my thing.
Right! You understand our culture
pretty well, for an outsider!
Thank you!
Now, everyone, while Kazuma
and the others are buying time,
give me your magic power!
I'm sick of wasting my time with this village
full of maniacs with nothing to show for it!
I've fought this entire time with my pride
as a general in the Devil King's army!
And my men, who admire me,
have fought loyally in my name!
But...
When I was on the verge of death,
I realized something!
That I was wrong!
Satisfaction and happiness
aren't the same thing!
No matter how hard I try, the only
people who notice are goblins!
Sylvia-sama! I love you!
I have relationships, but no love!
I've never wanted romance
as badly as I do now!
My life won't shine until
I finally have love in it!
You idiot!
That's not true.
Sylvia, from the moment I met you...
You were already shining!
N-No one's ever scolded
me like that before...
Sylvia.
I can't believe you...
I love you.
I love you...
...so much!
I love you!
The rest is up to you guys!
S-So much magic power!
Megumin-san, Yunyun-san,
it's all yours!
The magic power...
of everyone in the village!
This is crazy! I've never heard
of a gamble with worse odds!
Kazuma becoming Sylvia's weakness...
because she'll like him?
If only I knew advanced magic...
Megumin.
Kazuma-san has faith in your Explosion magic.
He wouldn't come up with a
plan like this if he didn't.
Megumin, have you lost
faith in Explosion magic?
Power... surging!
I am called Yunyun!
The foremost and greatest mage
among the Crimson Demons!
I am called Megumin!
The foremost and greatest mage
among the Crimson Demons!
Because Yunyun allowed me to pursue
Explosion magic on that day,
I became who I am now!
And because I had Megumin as my
rival, I became who I am now!
Light of Saber!
Let the storm blow! Let the flames roar!
Explosion magic is the stuff of dreams!
It is the ultimate magic that
turns the impossible possible!
Explosion!
Love!
A barrier?!
Dreams!
Hope!
Don't give up, Megumin!
You can do it, Yunyun!
My students!
That magic can't take my life!
I'm moving forward! Into the future!
Sylvia.
Let's go...
Together!
I love you...
I love you!
Kazuma was able to bring down
the barrier in her heart!
Satou Kazuma... y-you... toyed with me,
but I still love you!
This... is... my popular phase!
And so, my popular phase came to an end.
If Aqua hadn't used Blessing to
buff my luck dozens of times over,
I would've probably been blasted
beyond even smithereens.
Even with my higher than average luck stat,
this was an incredibly risky move.
Welcome back, Kazuma-san.
I see. Sounds like you've been through hell.
But ain't that what adventuring's all about?
A toast to your adventure!
Let's all cheer for Kazuma!
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
Warriors deserve cheers every now and then.
There's no telling when my next
popular phase will kick in.
There we go!
It's perfect weather for a picnic today.
Man, yet another brutal adventure...
I'm sorry.
If I knew advanced magic,
you wouldn't have died...
You've got that right.
The whole process is pretty unpleasant,
until you're fully revived.
Plus, the moment you die... hurts super bad.
What's wrong?
Can I ask you to do something terrible?
I want to be a mage who doesn't
get in the way from now on.
You want me to press the button
so you can learn advanced magic?
What happened to your talk about dreams?
It's time to wake up. I'll be sealing
my Explosion magic away.
The foremost mage among the Crimson Demons,
and the wielder of advanced magic!
From now on, that'll be my calling card.
Since I have higher magic potential
than Yunyun, with advanced magic,
I know I'll be number one
among the Crimson Demons!
I'm not going to let her take that title.
This is so dumb.
Here.
Thanks...
Well, let's get going.
Hey, Megumin. Light one up for me.
You haven't done your daily
Explosion today, right?
I can't believe you...
To ask me to use it as soon
as I decided to stop...
What are you thinking?
Very well!
This will be my final Explosion magic.
I'll make it one to remember!
Goodbye...
Explosion!
What the...
I am called Megumin!
Arch wizard and wielder of Explosion magic!
Axel's foremost mage,
and she who will one day
master Explosion magic!
Do I need a talented mage?
I've got one who can toy with and defeat the
Devil King's generals with a single Explosion.
If you know one who can do better
than that, I'd like to meet them.
Up you go.
Kazuma! Megumin! The tea's ready!
I'm gonna eat your lunches!
Isn't it just leftovers they gave us?
Well, I packed them for the picnic,
so now they're lunch!
Yeah, yeah...
That one gets 120 points!